id,speaker_nm,conversation_id,reply_to_id,reply_to_nm,timestamp,text,likes,shares,num_comments,cleaned_text,named_entities,sentiment,tokens
1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,1535939117313167361,0,None,2022-06-12 10:56:36,"In India Nupur Sharma gets police protection after insulting Prophet Muhammed (pbuh) while those protesting the hate get their homes bulldozed. Unreal misuse of power and state machinery!

#StandWithAfreenFatima
#StopBulldozingMuslimHouses",2000,1100,379,india nupur sharma gets police protection insulting prophet muhammed pbuh protesting hate homes bulldozed unreal misuse power state machinery standwithafreenfatima stopbulldozingmuslimhouses,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Nupur Sharma', 'PERSON'), ('Prophet Muhammed', 'PERSON')]",-1.0,"[101, 2634, 16371, 5311, 14654, 4152, 2610, 3860, 23979, 12168, 14163, 3511, 7583, 1052, 8569, 2232, 21248, 5223, 5014, 7087, 3527, 5422, 4895, 22852, 28616, 8557, 2373, 2110, 10394, 3233, 24415, 10354, 28029, 27753, 9581, 2644, 8569, 3363, 3527, 6774, 7606, 17960, 15666, 102]"
1536044824775708673,IndiaUnleashed_,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 17:56:39,In India stone thrower arsonists are called protestors by Salman.,3,0,0,india stone thrower arsonists called protestors salman,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Salman', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 2634, 2962, 5466, 2121, 24912, 5130, 2170, 6186, 5668, 28542, 102]"
1535940002403995648,georgysthomas,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 11:00:07,Very sad state of affairs.,0,1,2,sad state affairs,[],-0.65,"[101, 6517, 2110, 3821, 102]"
1535952471218077696,yogisach1,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 11:49:40,"You are a politician your only job is to divide and rule , that’s what britishers gifted to inc",0,0,0,politician job divide rule thats britishers gifted,[],0.25,"[101, 3761, 3105, 11443, 3627, 2008, 2015, 2329, 2545, 12785, 102]"
1535943192108888066,uZruuDohin5gTKW,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 11:12:48,Nupur is not indulged in violence. If you hurt can go to court.,56,4,0,nupur indulged violence hurt court,"[('Nupur', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 16371, 5311, 27427, 5313, 5999, 4808, 3480, 2457, 102]"
1535942274839814150,abhyuday_abh,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 11:09:09,What kind of protest is this?,57,3,0,kind protest,[],0.6,"[101, 2785, 6186, 102]"
1535957935636959232,RowdyPappu,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 12:11:23,"Nobody From India Doesn't Respect A P J Abdul Kalam Sir. So If Every Muslim Of India Makes Themselves As Abdul Kalam Sir, So No Buldozar Will Run Over Their Home. Be A Human At First. Love India. Respect Hinduism Of India. Because It's Not Pakistan.",41,3,1,india doesnt respect p j abdul kalam sir muslim india makes abdul kalam sir buldozar run home human love india respect hinduism india pakistan,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('Abdul Kalam', 'PERSON'), ('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]",0.25,"[101, 2634, 2987, 2102, 4847, 1052, 1046, 10298, 26209, 2213, 2909, 5152, 2634, 3084, 10298, 26209, 2213, 2909, 20934, 6392, 25036, 2099, 2448, 2188, 2529, 2293, 2634, 4847, 19632, 2634, 4501, 102]"
1536084208069668864,Mahakaa56515400,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 20:33:08,"Pls stop using bulldozer.  It's bad as it's messy, creates problems for neighbours. 

Better use dynamides for controlled explosion.",33,3,3,pls stop using bulldozer bad messy creates problems neighbours better use dynamides controlled explosion,[],-0.1333333333333333,"[101, 20228, 2015, 2644, 2478, 7087, 3527, 6290, 2919, 18307, 9005, 3471, 14754, 2488, 2224, 1040, 18279, 24284, 2015, 4758, 7738, 102]"
1535947788747689985,ThaakorPathak1,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 11:31:04,Pelting stones is protesting???,31,2,0,pelting stones protesting,[],0.0,"[101, 21877, 7096, 2075, 6386, 21248, 102]"
1535981662986678273,RajeshNavyug,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 13:45:40,Nupur Sharma hasn't insulted prophet Muhammad.She said whatever written in your holy book.The same has been told by many muslims scholar.,15,1,1,nupur sharma insulted prophet muhammadshe said written holy bookthe told muslims scholar,"[('Nupur Sharma', 'PERSON'), ('Muhammad', 'PERSON'), ('muslims', 'NORP')]",0.25,"[101, 16371, 5311, 14654, 23637, 12168, 7187, 4095, 2063, 2056, 2517, 4151, 2338, 10760, 2409, 7486, 6288, 102]"
1536029673880031232,sdattanayak,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 16:56:26,"Still we say the same what your holy book say about mohammad and ayesha. You can not hide the truth. 
 54-9 is the truth..... 
#IsupportNupurSharma 
#FactsMatter",2,0,1,say holy book say mohammad ayesha hide truth 549 truth isupportnupursharma factsmatter,"[('54', 'CARDINAL')]",0.0,"[101, 2360, 4151, 2338, 2360, 12050, 13442, 7377, 5342, 3606, 5139, 2683, 3606, 2003, 6279, 6442, 11231, 5311, 7377, 17830, 8866, 18900, 3334, 102]"
1535945258294358017,newbie_hope,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 11:21:00,Protest or riot?? Rioters will get punished..,2,0,0,protest riot rioters punished,[],0.0,"[101, 6186, 11421, 11421, 2545, 14248, 102]"
1535946970107260928,sri_hindu,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 11:27:48,Congress mukt bharath,2,0,0,congress mukt bharath,"[('Congress', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 3519, 14163, 25509, 1038, 28074, 2232, 102]"
1535958084417228800,sandeshruge,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 12:11:58,Can u prove it that she the facts nupur sharma stated is wrong n not written in ur holy book,2,0,2,u prove facts nupur sharma stated wrong n written ur holy book,"[('nupur sharma', 'PERSON')]",-0.5,"[101, 1057, 6011, 8866, 16371, 5311, 14654, 3090, 3308, 1050, 2517, 24471, 4151, 2338, 102]"
1536245493658857472,Vijayafourth,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-13 07:14:02,"Yes, I agree. One ( true) comment sets the country on fire,, but demolition of encroachment is overreaction.  Very strange.",1,0,0,yes agree true comment sets country demolition encroachment overreaction strange,"[('One', 'CARDINAL')]",0.1425,"[101, 2748, 5993, 2995, 7615, 4520, 2406, 12451, 4372, 26775, 10441, 22729, 2058, 16416, 7542, 4326, 102]"
1535953701298270210,RishiTi58397091,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 11:54:33,Peaceful protest is fundamental right but pelting stones and destroying public and private property is crime. Constitution is above all religions.,1,0,1,peaceful protest fundamental right pelting stones destroying public private property crime constitution religions,[],0.05595238095238095,"[101, 9379, 6186, 8050, 2157, 21877, 7096, 2075, 6386, 9846, 2270, 2797, 3200, 4126, 4552, 11822, 102]"
1535969579909795841,Esa_Faraz,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 12:57:39,"#StandWithAfreenFathima
#StopBulldozingMuslimHouses
#IndianMuslimsUnderAttack 
@OIC_OCI
 @Abdulla_Alamadi
 @ajmubasher
 @Mufti_Yasir
 @AJEnglish
 @AIMPLB_Official
 @MJALSHRIKA
 @steve_hanke",1,0,0,standwithafreenfathima stopbulldozingmuslimhouses indianmuslimsunderattack oicoci abdullaalamadi ajmubasher muftiyasir ajenglish aimplbofficial mjalshrika stevehanke,"[('#StandWithAfreenFathima\n', 'MONEY'), ('@OIC_OCI\n @Abdulla_Alamadi\n @ajmubasher', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 3233, 24415, 10354, 28029, 27753, 16369, 2644, 8569, 3363, 3527, 6774, 7606, 17960, 15666, 2796, 7606, 17960, 25168, 6906, 5946, 3600, 1051, 11261, 6895, 10298, 2721, 7911, 25666, 2072, 19128, 12274, 22083, 5886, 14163, 6199, 8717, 29481, 19128, 13159, 13602, 6614, 24759, 5092, 26989, 13247, 1049, 25787, 4095, 23778, 3889, 4819, 3489, 102]"
1536011851313475585,raaghu81,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 15:45:37,What was the insult....? And r ubtelling stone pelting is a peaceful protest ??,1,0,0,insult r ubtelling stone pelting peaceful protest,[],0.25,"[101, 15301, 1054, 1057, 19279, 23918, 2962, 21877, 7096, 2075, 9379, 6186, 102]"
1535994120799649792,IshikaRathore45,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 14:35:10,Stop doing violence first,1,0,0,stop doing violence,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]",0.25,"[101, 2644, 2725, 4808, 102]"
1535965500798554113,Iamsachinsky,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 12:41:26,Now India is only the country when we can't speak the truth and can't digest the truth too.,1,0,0,india country speak truth digest truth,"[('India', 'GPE')]",0.0,"[101, 2634, 2406, 3713, 3606, 17886, 3606, 102]"
1535944962336227328,IntelleCosmos,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 11:19:50,"Why you pissful made illegal construction ? You stone pelters breed make home from same stone , every single day Muslim make fun of other religion and customs , curse to humanity",1,0,0,pissful illegal construction stone pelters breed make home stone single day muslim make fun religion customs curse humanity,"[('every single day', 'DATE'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]",-0.07928571428571428,"[101, 18138, 3993, 6206, 2810, 2962, 21877, 21928, 2015, 8843, 2191, 2188, 2962, 2309, 2154, 5152, 2191, 4569, 4676, 8205, 8364, 8438, 102]"
1536179561121333248,Jit_indian,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-13 02:52:02,"Protesting ? They were rioting and pelting stones and demanding sir tan se juda , all learned from same book which nupoor quoted",1,0,0,protesting rioting pelting stones demanding sir tan se juda learned book nupoor quoted,"[('tan se juda', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 21248, 11421, 2075, 21877, 7096, 2075, 6386, 9694, 2909, 9092, 7367, 18414, 2850, 4342, 2338, 16371, 24667, 2099, 9339, 102]"
1535966367668912130,chouhaan,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 12:44:53,What is pbuh,1,0,2,pbuh,[],0.0,"[101, 1052, 8569, 2232, 102]"
1536174667118936064,ashoknathan,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-13 02:32:36,First advice your people not disturb or throw stones … you stop the terror act .. this cos reaction from your action .. every wrong action your will equal and opposite reaction it’s law of science,1,0,0,advice people disturb throw stones stop terror act cos reaction action wrong action equal opposite reaction law science,"[('First', 'ORDINAL')]",-0.008333333333333337,"[101, 6040, 2111, 22995, 5466, 6386, 2644, 7404, 2552, 2522, 2015, 4668, 2895, 3308, 2895, 5020, 4500, 4668, 2375, 2671, 102]"
1535961593820827649,tweet_freely7,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 12:25:55,#NupurSharama real hero,0,0,0,nupursharama real hero,"[('NupurSharama', 'PERSON')]",0.2,"[101, 16371, 5311, 7377, 14672, 2613, 5394, 102]"
1536009817822613504,vishalbarge75,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 15:37:32,Tell your brothers to stop violence.... Cant you see what are they doing,0,0,0,tell brothers stop violence doing,[],0.0,"[101, 2425, 3428, 2644, 4808, 2725, 102]"
1536591424455872512,kwl_una,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-14 06:08:38,And what any STONE PELTERS & gun shots on Police.,0,0,1,stone pelters gun shots police,"[('STONE PELTERS &', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 2962, 21877, 21928, 2015, 3282, 7171, 2610, 102]"
1536060547560796160,mishravinod202,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 18:59:07,"I am unable to understand it, why homes are getting bulldozed. They were only pelting stones peacefully. Our constitution give these rights to us. Right?",0,0,0,unable understand homes getting bulldozed pelting stones peacefully constitution rights right,[],0.008928571428571425,"[101, 4039, 3305, 5014, 2893, 7087, 3527, 5422, 21877, 7096, 2075, 6386, 21614, 4552, 2916, 2157, 102]"
1536266805110788096,arjunvenktesh,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-13 08:38:43,Using sophistry and getting rich. And einstein told Indians were stupid. Seeing your your would give it another thought,0,0,0,using sophistry getting rich einstein told indians stupid seeing thought,"[('einstein', 'PERSON'), ('Indians', 'NORP')]",-0.21249999999999997,"[101, 2478, 2061, 21850, 3367, 2854, 2893, 4138, 15313, 2409, 6505, 5236, 3773, 2245, 102]"
1535944496671625217,shyammeranaam,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 11:17:59,"So whats your expectations? Throw Nupur to the wolfs or give medals to rioters? Though its not your problem, you have been appeased for decades and now waking up!! This is not an Islamic state",0,0,0,whats expectations throw nupur wolfs medals rioters problem appeased decades waking islamic state,"[('Nupur', 'PERSON'), ('decades', 'DATE'), ('Islamic', 'NORP')]",0.0,"[101, 2054, 2015, 10908, 5466, 16371, 5311, 4702, 2015, 6665, 11421, 2545, 3291, 10439, 25063, 5109, 12447, 5499, 2110, 102]"
1536203769729363968,chandan_spal,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-13 04:28:14,"They were not protestors , they are called rioters.",0,0,0,protestors called rioters,[],0.0,"[101, 6186, 5668, 2170, 11421, 2545, 102]"
1536418689397837824,adilmullancp,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-13 18:42:15,"@indSupremeCourt
 @PMO
 : Is this justice.",0,0,0,indsupremecourt pmo justice,[],0.0,"[101, 27427, 6342, 28139, 4168, 13421, 7610, 2080, 3425, 102]"
1536033402033303552,yamar2189,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 17:11:15,"As you sow, so you shall reap ..,... Love Yogi ",0,0,0,sow shall reap love yogi,"[('Yogi', 'PERSON')]",0.5,"[101, 2061, 2860, 4618, 2128, 9331, 2293, 10930, 5856, 102]"
1536060303749697536,karanko90834123,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 18:58:09,"Protestby throwing stone,petrol bombs",0,0,0,protestby throwing stonepetrol bombs,[],0.0,"[101, 6186, 3762, 6886, 2962, 22327, 13153, 9767, 102]"
1535950509269721088,Surya20279088,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 11:41:52,fringe eliments of the indian society,0,0,0,fringe eliments indian society,"[('indian', 'NORP')]",0.0,"[101, 13548, 12005, 8163, 2796, 2554, 102]"
1536097253286326272,mohdsameer_786,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 21:24:59,"Agree  = Rt 

#StandWithAfreenFatima",0,0,0,agree rt standwithafreenfatima,[],0.0,"[101, 5993, 19387, 3233, 24415, 10354, 28029, 27753, 9581, 102]"
1536105661846540288,Vr4uAmit,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 21:58:23,53 + 6,0,0,0,53 6,"[('53 + 6', 'DATE')]",0.0,"[101, 5187, 1020, 102]"
1536105331985526784,Vr4uAmit,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 21:57:05,Most of the Countries is bad for Muslims. Please Analyze yourself.,0,0,0,countries bad muslims analyze,"[('Countries', 'ORG'), ('Muslims', 'NORP')]",-0.09999999999999992,"[101, 3032, 2919, 7486, 17908, 102]"
1536040880204746752,chiranjivising5,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 17:40:58,Ya you are right because this is our hindustan.,0,0,0,ya right hindustan,[],0.2857142857142857,"[101, 8038, 2157, 18221, 5794, 102]"
1537528384917360640,BribaKhan,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-16 20:11:47,"Shame on india 
#StopBulldozingMuslimHouses",0,0,0,shame india stopbulldozingmuslimhouses,[],0.0,"[101, 9467, 2634, 2644, 8569, 3363, 3527, 6774, 7606, 17960, 15666, 102]"
1536220375511535616,rajkiran_india,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-13 05:34:13,Muslims can go to Pakistan... No one will stop! ,0,0,0,muslims pakistan stop,"[('Muslims', 'NORP'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]",0.0,"[101, 7486, 4501, 2644, 102]"
1536207961151795202,SubhaPrasadsa12,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-13 04:44:53,"How did she insulted prophet Muhammad? She just  told what is written in quran,the same words were also told by islamic scholar you can check it on any social media channels,before questioning / blaming nupur sharma first go and read the Quran, 
#IsupportNupurSharma",0,0,0,did insulted prophet muhammad just told written quranthe words told islamic scholar check social media channelsbefore questioning blaming nupur sharma read quran isupportnupursharma,"[('Muhammad', 'PERSON'), ('quran', 'GPE'), ('islamic', 'NORP'), ('nupur sharma', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Quran', 'GPE')]",0.09444444444444444,"[101, 2106, 23637, 12168, 7187, 2074, 2409, 2517, 21288, 10760, 2616, 2409, 5499, 6288, 4638, 2591, 2865, 6833, 4783, 29278, 2063, 11242, 24114, 16371, 5311, 14654, 3191, 21288, 2003, 6279, 6442, 11231, 5311, 7377, 17830, 102]"
1536185261645627397,IitDaksh,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-13 03:14:41,So you guys want muslim to throw stone peacefully without any interaction?? lol,0,0,0,guys want muslim throw stone peacefully interaction lol,"[('muslim', 'NORP')]",0.525,"[101, 4364, 2215, 5152, 5466, 2962, 21614, 8290, 8840, 2140, 102]"
1536395631022858240,lorddeepu,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-13 17:10:37,Think positive now u have more stone available,0,0,0,think positive u stone available,[],0.3757575757575758,"[101, 2228, 3893, 1057, 2962, 2800, 102]"
1536389329131409408,GLokeshwar_,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-13 16:45:35,Don't interfere in matters when u r not from this country....looks like u enjoy stirring up conflict and making trouble ,0,0,0,dont interfere matters u r countrylooks like u enjoy stirring conflict making trouble,[],0.1,"[101, 2123, 2102, 15115, 5609, 1057, 1054, 2406, 4135, 6559, 2015, 2066, 1057, 5959, 18385, 4736, 2437, 4390, 102]"
1535975853271617537,Shubham26890225,1535939117313167361,1535939117313167361,SalmanNizami_,2022-06-12 13:22:35,This is not insult of prophet actually written in your religion if owaisi or Zakir naik insult Hindus god then you not take action .#sach bolna chubta hai,0,0,0,insult prophet actually written religion owaisi zakir naik insult hindus god action sach bolna chubta hai,"[('Zakir', 'FAC'), ('Hindus', 'NORP'), ('bolna', 'GPE'), ('hai', 'GPE')]",0.05,"[101, 15301, 12168, 2941, 2517, 4676, 27593, 15593, 2072, 23564, 23630, 6583, 5480, 15301, 18221, 2643, 2895, 17266, 2232, 8945, 19666, 2050, 14684, 19279, 2050, 15030, 102]"
1534124145109516288,iam_shimorekato,1534124145109516288,0,None,2022-06-07 10:44:33,"Hi shoorpanakha 
@MahuaMoitra
, Nupur Sharma got security because she is getting death threats and rape threats.

You made fun of Hindus and now if you have the courage then show it by tweeting against Islam. Then let's see what happens",402,154,11,hi shoorpanakha mahuamoitra nupur sharma got security getting death threats rape threats fun hindus courage tweeting islam lets happens,"[('Nupur Sharma', 'PERSON'), ('Hindus', 'NORP'), ('Islam', 'ORG')]",0.3,"[101, 7632, 26822, 2953, 9739, 27573, 2050, 5003, 14691, 5302, 4183, 2527, 16371, 5311, 14654, 2288, 3036, 2893, 2331, 8767, 9040, 8767, 4569, 18221, 8424, 1056, 28394, 3436, 7025, 11082, 6433, 102]"
1534167559481610241,Shiv119711,1534124145109516288,1534124145109516288,iam_shimorekato,2022-06-07 13:37:04,"If Islamists threaten her... She will convert to Islam  

to show that how big hearted they become for a criminal who adopts Islam by leaving Kafirana.

Just formality is left... Just name is hindu in a body of Islamist.",2,1,0,islamists threaten convert islam big hearted criminal adopts islam leaving kafirana just formality left just hindu body islamist,"[('Islamists', 'NORP'), ('Islam', 'NORP'), ('Islam', 'NORP'), ('Kafirana', 'PERSON'), ('Islamist', 'NORP')]",-0.13333333333333333,"[101, 27256, 2015, 15686, 10463, 7025, 2502, 18627, 4735, 11092, 2015, 7025, 2975, 10556, 8873, 16737, 2074, 5337, 3012, 2187, 2074, 7560, 2303, 27256, 102]"
1534132965000720384,imystic7,1534124145109516288,1534124145109516288,iam_shimorekato,2022-06-07 11:19:36,"Mahua, are you a MP ? How can you insult Hindu gods ?? 
@HMOIndia
 
@PMOIndia
 

Parliamentary panel is sleeping ?",2,0,0,mahua mp insult hindu gods hmoindia pmoindia parliamentary panel sleeping,"[('Mahua', 'PERSON'), ('Hindu', 'NORP'), ('@HMOIndia\n \n', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 5003, 14691, 6131, 15301, 7560, 5932, 20287, 28765, 9032, 7610, 28765, 9032, 5768, 5997, 5777, 102]"
1534244330344357888,Subodh1010,1534124145109516288,1534124145109516288,iam_shimorekato,2022-06-07 18:42:07,"Utni himmat in mein nahi hai ...saara Gyan hindu ke liye he hai ... By the way,which religion she belongs to?",0,0,0,utni himmat mein nahi hai saara gyan hindu ke liye hai waywhich religion belongs,"[('mein nahi', 'GPE'), ('hai', 'GPE'), ('saara Gyan', 'PERSON'), ('ke liye', 'PERSON'), ('hai', 'GPE')]",0.0,"[101, 21183, 3490, 2032, 18900, 24182, 20976, 2072, 15030, 7842, 5400, 1043, 7054, 7560, 17710, 5622, 6672, 15030, 2126, 2860, 16066, 2232, 4676, 7460, 102]"
1534204719987429376,Prasant06838470,1534124145109516288,1534124145109516288,iam_shimorekato,2022-06-07 16:04:44,Someone should tell Didi to forget about national politics with foul-mouthed member in party,0,0,0,tell didi forget national politics foulmouthed member party,"[('Didi', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 2425, 2106, 2072, 5293, 2120, 4331, 12487, 14359, 2098, 2266, 2283, 102]"
1534130197829586944,Middletruthless,1534124145109516288,1534124145109516288,iam_shimorekato,2022-06-07 11:08:36,#NupurSharma is correct,0,0,0,nupursharma correct,"[('NupurSharma', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 16371, 5311, 7377, 17830, 6149, 102]"
1534124676087025664,Selvaku47689680,1534124145109516288,1534124145109516288,iam_shimorekato,2022-06-07 10:46:40,https://x.com/Selvaku47689680/status/1532644514396942337?t=6x1-_TGXeAwgRKe6vfeinQ&s=19…,0,0,0,,[],0.0,"[101, 102]"
1536599352252108800,Abhishekkkk10,1536599352252108800,0,None,2022-06-14 06:40:08,"The person who instigated people against Nupur Sharma, the person who is responsible for ""AlQaeda threatens teππor attacks in India"" has now deleted his Facebook page where he has been abusing our Hindu Gods. 

I demand #ArrestZubair",311,240,4,person instigated people nupur sharma person responsible alqaeda threatens teor attacks india deleted facebook page abusing hindu gods demand arrestzubair,"[('Nupur Sharma', 'PERSON'), ('AlQaeda', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Hindu', 'NORP')]",0.2,"[101, 2711, 16021, 3775, 11644, 2111, 16371, 5311, 14654, 2711, 3625, 2632, 19062, 11960, 17016, 8915, 2953, 4491, 2634, 17159, 9130, 3931, 8273, 7741, 7560, 5932, 5157, 6545, 9759, 26068, 2099, 102]"
1536755764441731072,Sanatan29487172,1536599352252108800,1536599352252108800,Abhishekkkk10,2022-06-14 17:01:40,I sport Nupur Sharma,0,0,0,sport nupur sharma,"[('Nupur Sharma', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 4368, 16371, 5311, 14654, 102]"
1536693618500456448,HagwanRam,1536599352252108800,1536599352252108800,Abhishekkkk10,2022-06-14 12:54:43,"#StandWithSaadAnsari #StandWithAfreenFathima #StandWithZubair
Jay shree Zubair",0,0,0,standwithsaadansari standwithafreenfathima standwithzubair jay shree zubair,"[('#StandWithSaadAnsari #', 'MONEY'), ('Jay shree', 'PERSON'), ('Zubair', 'GPE')]",0.0,"[101, 3233, 24415, 3736, 26335, 22740, 3233, 24415, 10354, 28029, 27753, 16369, 3233, 24415, 9759, 26068, 2099, 6108, 14021, 9910, 16950, 26068, 2099, 102]"
1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,1530783154729934848,0,None,2022-05-29 05:28:39,"Mumbai Police files case against Nupur Sharma for her remarks on Prophet Muhammad on a complaint filed by Raza Academy

Raza Academy ",1100,609,23,mumbai police files case nupur sharma remarks prophet muhammad complaint filed raza academy raza academy,"[('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('Nupur Sharma', 'PERSON'), ('Prophet Muhammad', 'PERSON'), ('Raza Academy', 'ORG')]",-0.3,"[101, 8955, 2610, 6764, 2553, 16371, 5311, 14654, 12629, 12168, 7187, 12087, 6406, 10958, 4143, 2914, 10958, 4143, 2914, 102]"
1530846112721928192,harshagujaratan,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-29 09:38:49,"Shame on.whom ?? 
Raza academy or Mumbai police",12,0,2,shame onwhom raza academy mumbai police,"[('Raza', 'PERSON'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE')]",0.0,"[101, 9467, 2006, 2860, 23393, 10958, 4143, 2914, 8955, 2610, 102]"
1530859139550785537,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-29 10:30:35,One is worst than the other ,5,0,0,worst,"[('One', 'CARDINAL')]",-0.5625,"[101, 5409, 102]"
1530843750314180608,sanjoychakra,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-29 09:29:26,Pl follow back.,1,1,1,pl follow,[],0.0,"[101, 20228, 3582, 102]"
1530795207729369088,rise_up_hindu,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-29 06:16:32,"@SecBlinken
 ,
@POTUS
 this is the real picture of muslims in india.
@SecBlinken
 dont try to impose US  style freedom in india.Why did u impose a president whom many americans did not vote for.First rectify ur this style of freedom.",6,2,0,secblinken potus real picture muslims india secblinken dont try impose style freedom indiawhy did u impose president americans did vote forfirst rectify ur style freedom,"[('@POTUS\n ', 'PERSON'), ('muslims', 'NORP'), ('india', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('india', 'GPE'), ('americans', 'NORP'), ('First', 'ORDINAL')]",0.35,"[101, 10819, 16558, 19839, 2368, 8962, 2271, 2613, 3861, 7486, 2634, 10819, 16558, 19839, 2368, 2123, 2102, 3046, 17607, 2806, 4071, 2634, 2860, 10536, 2106, 1057, 17607, 2343, 4841, 2106, 3789, 2005, 8873, 12096, 28667, 27351, 24471, 2806, 4071, 102]"
1530799048831078400,IndiaFi75227536,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-29 06:31:48,Muslim league party rules Maharashtra!,2,0,1,muslim league party rules maharashtra,"[('Muslim league party', 'ORG'), ('Maharashtra', 'NORP')]",0.0,"[101, 5152, 2223, 2283, 3513, 12434, 102]"
1530957795553468416,sonali_mehta25,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-29 17:02:36,Hindu orgs should file multiple complaints for blasphemy when Shivling and other god/godess are being disrespected,1,0,0,hindu orgs file multiple complaints blasphemy shivling godgodess disrespected,"[('Hindu', 'NORP')]",-0.0625,"[101, 7560, 8917, 2015, 5371, 3674, 10821, 1038, 8523, 8458, 26662, 11895, 2615, 2989, 2643, 3995, 6155, 2015, 4487, 21338, 2229, 5051, 10985, 102]"
1531389260187566080,JayKc15,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-30 21:37:06,If there rasool were rangila what can be expected from the followers,0,0,0,rasool rangila expected followers,[],-0.1,"[101, 20710, 13669, 8369, 11733, 3517, 8771, 102]"
1531104128553799680,indianityfirst,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-30 02:44:05,"Maharashtra is ruled by the brotherhood government 

Brotherhood of UrbanNaxals, Terrorists, MahaCorruptBandhan parties, Bollywood Mafia & their SoldMedia is the biggest threat to our nation. 

Patriotic Indians should reject them in every possible form",0,0,0,maharashtra ruled brotherhood government brotherhood urbannaxals terrorists mahacorruptbandhan parties bollywood mafia soldmedia biggest threat nation patriotic indians reject possible form,"[('Maharashtra', 'ORG'), ('Brotherhood of UrbanNaxals', 'ORG'), ('MahaCorruptBandhan', 'PRODUCT'), ('Bollywood Mafia &', 'ORG'), ('SoldMedia', 'ORG'), ('Patriotic Indians', 'NORP')]",0.0,"[101, 12434, 5451, 12865, 2231, 12865, 3923, 2532, 18684, 4877, 15554, 24404, 27108, 21531, 2102, 12733, 4819, 4243, 16046, 13897, 2853, 16969, 5221, 5081, 3842, 14314, 6505, 15454, 2825, 2433, 102]"
1530886777472331777,HoiPoll0i,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-29 12:20:24,A terrorist organization which is not even registered with the charity commission. All their operations should b stopped ASAP!,0,0,0,terrorist organization registered charity commission operations b stopped asap,"[('ASAP', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 9452, 3029, 5068, 5952, 3222, 3136, 1038, 3030, 17306, 2361, 102]"
1531092646294261761,transcendnada,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-30 01:58:27,Everyone in Raza academy must be arrested ! We come to know if another antihindu anti India organisation,0,0,0,raza academy arrested come know antihindu anti india organisation,"[('Raza', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]",0.0,"[101, 10958, 4143, 2914, 4727, 2272, 2113, 3424, 10606, 8566, 3424, 2634, 5502, 102]"
1531320848212078592,KVD60149055,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-30 17:05:15,"Hindus were lenient forgiving then and they are still
.. Hindus paid a huge price then and they are still paying",0,0,0,hindus lenient forgiving hindus paid huge price paying,"[('Hindus', 'NORP'), ('Hindus', 'NORP')]",0.44999999999999996,"[101, 18221, 18798, 11638, 2005, 23795, 18221, 3825, 4121, 3976, 7079, 102]"
1530988962520571904,MantySatam,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-29 19:06:27,This is a new low for Mumbai Police. Raza academy rioters had abused women police during the 2012 Azad maidan riots.,0,0,0,new low mumbai police raza academy rioters abused women police 2012 azad maidan riots,"[('Mumbai Police', 'ORG'), ('Raza academy', 'ORG'), ('2012', 'DATE')]",0.06818181818181818,"[101, 2047, 2659, 8955, 2610, 10958, 4143, 2914, 11421, 2545, 16999, 2308, 2610, 2262, 17207, 4215, 10850, 2319, 12925, 102]"
1531198222143733760,MayurShinde4,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-30 08:57:59,"@BJP4Maharashtra
 and 
@Devendra_Office
 - This is on you for not acting on Raza Academy in your tenure!",0,0,0,bjp4maharashtra devendraoffice acting raza academy tenure,"[('Raza Academy', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 24954, 2549, 25687, 5400, 4095, 6494, 16475, 19524, 7245, 6610, 3772, 10958, 4143, 2914, 7470, 102]"
1531197922112585729,MayurShinde4,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-30 08:56:47,"What can you expect in #MahaVikasAghadi - https://maharashtratimes.com/maharashtra/mumbai-news/hanuman-chalisa-row-sharad-pawar-targets-raj-thackeray/articleshow/91212413.cms…
Its Pawar politics. Raza Academcy riots also happened during last NCP govt.",0,0,0,expect mahavikasaghadi pawar politics raza academcy riots happened ncp govt,"[('#', 'CARDINAL'), ('Raza Academcy', 'PERSON'), ('NCP', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 5987, 24404, 13309, 16782, 5603, 17190, 22195, 2906, 4331, 10958, 4143, 9353, 9648, 12458, 2100, 12925, 3047, 13316, 2361, 22410, 102]"
1530808570467561473,pvnn021,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-29 07:09:38,What is stopping her from filling FIR??,0,0,0,stopping filling fir,"[('FIR', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 7458, 8110, 21554, 102]"
1530826346472955904,Yasser412434621,1530783154729934848,1530783154729934848,VlKAS_PR0NAM0,2022-05-29 08:20:17,MVA is anti-national govt.,0,0,0,mva antinational govt,"[('MVA', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 19842, 2050, 3424, 25434, 22410, 102]"
1533967915791159296,ashajadeja325,1533967915791159296,0,None,2022-06-07 00:23:45,With what moral face is Qatar complaining about Nupur Sharma quoting something from a Hadith? It did not censure or scold or even tap on the wrist of MFHusain as he vandalized Indian goddesses held sacred by over a billion Hindus.,1700,609,59,moral face qatar complaining nupur sharma quoting hadith did censure scold tap wrist mfhusain vandalized indian goddesses held sacred billion hindus,"[('Qatar', 'GPE'), ('Nupur Sharma', 'PERSON'), ('Hadith', 'PERSON'), ('MFHusain', 'ORG'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('over a billion', 'MONEY'), ('Hindus', 'NORP')]",0.0,"[101, 7191, 2227, 12577, 17949, 16371, 5311, 14654, 27394, 2018, 8939, 2106, 8292, 3619, 5397, 8040, 11614, 11112, 7223, 1049, 2546, 9825, 8113, 3158, 9305, 3550, 2796, 7804, 2229, 2218, 6730, 4551, 18221, 102]"
