id,speaker_nm,conversation_id,reply_to_nm,timestamp,text,likes,shares,num_comments,cleaned_text,named_entities,sentiment,tokens,date,extracted_entities,content_category,enhanced_hate_score,virality_score,spike_day,engagement_rank,hate_intensity,hate_keywords_count,reply_chain_depth,spike_cause,spike_top_entities,spike_external_cause,contextual_relevance,is_reply,user_influence,mention_count,hashtag_count,url_count,conversation_size,conversation_centrality
1339230232088367105,07f9ebe35e2ea9babe6c54f49f8209b7087cb9db95781878e1a88c891a994a91,1339230232088367105,,2020-12-16 15:25:43,"BLM-antifa in Seattle have set up another autonomous zone at Cal Anderson Park in the Capital Hill neighborhood. This is the same area they made CHAZ during the summer months. Video by 
@choeshow
:",5200,2700,1400,blmantifa seattle set autonomous zone cal anderson park capital hill neighborhood area chaz summer months video choeshow,"made chaz, ('Capital Hill', seattle, @choeshow, 'LOC'), ('Cal Anderson Park', chaz summer, area made, chaz, ('the summer months', video, this, months video, cal anderson park, park capital, autonomous zone, hill neighborhood, another autonomous, anderson park, ('Seattle', cal anderson, neighborhood area, capital hill, zone cal, video choeshow, 'FAC'), 'DATE')], [('BLM-antifa', 'GPE'), 'ORG')",0.2,"[101, 1038, 12624, 3775, 7011, 5862, 2275, 8392, 4224, 10250, 5143, 2380, 3007, 2940, 5101, 2181, 15775, 2480, 2621, 2706, 2678, 16480, 9953, 5004, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('BLM-antifa'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Seattle'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('Cal Anderson Park'"", "" 'FAC')"", "" ('Capital Hill'"", "" 'LOC')"", "" ('the summer months'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'made chaz', 'seattle', '@choeshow', 'chaz summer', 'area made', 'chaz', 'video', 'this', 'months video', 'cal anderson park', 'park capital', 'autonomous zone', 'hill neighborhood', 'another autonomous', 'anderson park', 'cal anderson', 'neighborhood area', 'capital hill', 'zone cal', 'video choeshow']",social,0.2,1.0,0,0.9822443181818182,0.2,1,0,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,0,0.6725382210780655,1,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339230948488073219,e5c8cf542fd661dadca05a1f8830e2a4a0d6f9c1286ea7223606ebb003d5d578,1339230232088367105,07f9ebe35e2ea9babe6c54f49f8209b7087cb9db95781878e1a88c891a994a91,2020-12-16 15:28:34,"At some point it seems as if we could just start tweeting out videos of landfills and Haitian ghettos and say ""another autonomous zone has erupted in ___"" and they'd be totally believable.",113,2,1,point just start tweeting videos landfills haitian ghettos say autonomous zone erupted theyd totally believable,"seems could, could start, tweeting videos, totally believable, [('Haitian', ___, point seems, zone erupted, videos landfills, start tweeting, haitian, erupted totally, landfills haitian, haitian ghettos, autonomous zone, another autonomous, ghettos say, say another, 'NORP')]",0.45,"[101, 2391, 2074, 2707, 1056, 28394, 3436, 6876, 28382, 2015, 21404, 17276, 2015, 2360, 8392, 4224, 12591, 2027, 2094, 6135, 19337, 2666, 12423, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('Haitian'"", "" 'NORP')]"", 'totally believable', 'haitian', 'say another', 'seems could', 'could start', 'tweeting videos', 'another autonomous', 'erupted totally', 'landfills haitian', '___', 'point seems', 'haitian ghettos', 'zone erupted', 'autonomous zone', 'ghettos say', 'videos landfills', 'start tweeting']",general,0.2,0.121,0,0.8835227272727273,0.2,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.04915462882349645,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339451172659322882,d96eaa7a69102de1eb3a8cc95728da1d48f7a656fd4e3fabae67566b8bdbffa6,1339230232088367105,07f9ebe35e2ea9babe6c54f49f8209b7087cb9db95781878e1a88c891a994a91,2020-12-17 06:03:40,"Hay 
@KathrynTewson
 they’re lying again",13,0,1,hay kathryntewson theyre lying,"[], @kathryntewson, hay kathryntewson, kathryntewson lying, hay",0.0,"[101, 10974, 20484, 2618, 9333, 2239, 2027, 2890, 4688, 102]",2020-12-17,"['[]', 'hay kathryntewson', 'hay', 'kathryntewson lying', '@kathryntewson']",general,0.2,0.015,1,0.7613636363636364,0.2,1,1,activity_spike,"[](10), 'PERSON')](5), trump(4), 'FAC')(3), 'ORG')(3)","Guardian correlation: How many times has Trump lost the election ahahahaha | First Dog on the Moon (score: 2, strength: medium)",general,1,0.006126123463859629,1,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339236439620349957,f6fe7c9f3e038dd0e30b860e84ab9ce0a354ad8759961f4264ef4089ace00abd,1339230232088367105,07f9ebe35e2ea9babe6c54f49f8209b7087cb9db95781878e1a88c891a994a91,2020-12-16 15:50:23,"This is what we have to look forward to in the Harris/Biden administration. By the time the sympathizers wake up, it’ll be too late.",87,5,2,look forward harrisbiden administration time sympathizers wake itll late,"this, harris, sympathizers wake, biden, time sympathizers, look forward, 'PERSON')], administration time, wake late, [('Biden', war, forward administration",-0.3,"[101, 2298, 2830, 5671, 17062, 2368, 3447, 2051, 25353, 8737, 25457, 16750, 5256, 2009, 3363, 2397, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('Biden'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'this', 'harris', 'sympathizers wake', 'biden', 'time sympathizers', 'look forward', 'administration time', 'wake late', 'war', 'forward administration']",international,0.2,0.106,0,0.8806818181818182,0.2,1,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.04326252595340024,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339231536642629632,4301e6dfa497e26dbb03cb70e31d28d4dcd56d9c723c0c9998219b7671cbf955,1339230232088367105,07f9ebe35e2ea9babe6c54f49f8209b7087cb9db95781878e1a88c891a994a91,2020-12-16 15:30:54,1 time my kid put a note on the door”don’t come in”. I took the door off for a year. That what you do when children throw tantrums. Also you would think with all those collective people together they could come up with a system to clean that place up. Come on man!,74,3,10,1 time kid note doordont come took door year children throw tantrums think collective people come clean place come man,"[('1', clean place, come system, ('a year', took door, door come, also would, door year, people together, kid put, time kid, also, system clean, note door, place come, that, tantrums also, think collective, together could, collective people, come man, year children, 'CARDINAL'), 'DATE')]",0.4583333333333333,"[101, 1015, 2051, 4845, 3602, 2341, 5280, 2102, 2272, 2165, 2341, 2095, 2336, 5466, 9092, 24456, 2015, 2228, 7268, 2111, 2272, 4550, 2173, 2272, 2158, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('1'"", "" 'CARDINAL')"", "" ('a year'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'clean place', 'come system', 'took door', 'door come', 'also would', 'door year', 'people together', 'kid put', 'time kid', 'also', 'system clean', 'note door', 'place come', 'that', 'tantrums also', 'think collective', 'together could', 'collective people', 'come man', 'year children']",general,0.15000000000000002,0.103,0,0.8792613636363636,0.15000000000000002,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0423565705567675,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339231959927631873,9e1cf83f1acf96ab273f701aeffa81e258f5eb75376eb1bcfe0dc1eea12b53c0,1339230232088367105,07f9ebe35e2ea9babe6c54f49f8209b7087cb9db95781878e1a88c891a994a91,2020-12-16 15:32:35,Andy cuts the video and calls it a CHAZ when it's a homeless encampment.  Not surprising. Gotta get those Ngo Simps fird up right?,50,1,34,andy cuts video calls chaz homeless encampment surprising gotta ngo simps fird right,"andy, 'GPE')], fird right, not, gotta, calls chaz, simps fird, cuts video, get ngo, video calls, 'PERSON'), encampment surprising, ('Ngo Simps', got get, [('Andy', surprising got, homeless encampment, andy cuts, chaz homeless, simps, ngo simps",-0.0321428571428571,"[101, 5557, 7659, 2678, 4455, 15775, 2480, 11573, 4372, 26468, 3672, 11341, 10657, 17895, 21934, 4523, 21554, 2094, 2157, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('Andy'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Ngo Simps'"", "" 'GPE')]"", 'not', 'cuts video', 'get ngo', 'andy', 'gotta', 'video calls', 'fird right', 'calls chaz', 'encampment surprising', 'surprising got', 'homeless encampment', 'andy cuts', 'chaz homeless', 'simps fird', 'got get', 'simps', 'ngo simps']",general,0.1,0.121,0,0.8835227272727273,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.05075506900634902,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339234000162844674,75898f79711754df33250afa635e6c5a5b094aa3aa36254dbe99eac16299b639,1339230232088367105,07f9ebe35e2ea9babe6c54f49f8209b7087cb9db95781878e1a88c891a994a91,2020-12-16 15:40:42,"I totally support this. As long as we get to build an additional wall around them and never let them come out. Once their supplies diminish, it would only be a matter of time before the problem would resolve itself.",14,0,1,totally support long build additional wall let come supplies diminish matter time problem resolve,"[], time problem, around never, let come, would resolve, never let, come supplies, build additional, once, get build, supplies diminish, support long, problem would, totally support, long get, diminish would, wall around, would matter, matter time, additional wall",-0.0166666666666666,"[101, 6135, 2490, 2146, 3857, 3176, 2813, 2292, 2272, 6067, 11737, 5498, 4095, 3043, 2051, 3291, 10663, 102]",2020-12-16,"['[]', 'let come', 'around never', 'time problem', 'would resolve', 'never let', 'come supplies', 'build additional', 'once', 'get build', 'supplies diminish', 'support long', 'problem would', 'totally support', 'long get', 'diminish would', 'wall around', 'would matter', 'matter time', 'additional wall']",general,0.30000000000000004,0.016,0,0.7649147727272727,0.30000000000000004,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.006531208037263921,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339313377177460743,c1dfdf3aa7092b8ba47fdc6cd49edf9561d09799136c21867578b06b2cc784b8,1339230232088367105,07f9ebe35e2ea9babe6c54f49f8209b7087cb9db95781878e1a88c891a994a91,2020-12-16 20:56:07,Wait antifa is a myth! BLM is a multi-billion dollar organization they wouldn't live like this!! Would they? This is what the left has given birth too. How in the world did 81 million people vote for this?,10,1,8,wait antifa myth blm multibillion dollar organization wouldnt live like left given birth world did 81 million people vote,"vote, ('81 million', 'CARDINAL')], how, would live, million people, birth world, left given, [('BLM', 'MONEY'), dollar organization, organization would, wait, myth blm, wait antifa, given birth, this, people vote, would left, like would, world million, antifa myth, live like, ('multi-billion dollar', would, 'ORG')",0.1065340909090909,"[101, 3524, 3424, 7011, 10661, 1038, 13728, 4800, 24457, 3258, 7922, 3029, 2876, 2102, 2444, 2066, 2187, 2445, 4182, 2088, 2106, 6282, 2454, 2111, 3789, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('BLM'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('multi-billion dollar'"", "" 'MONEY')"", "" ('81 million'"", "" 'CARDINAL')]"", 'vote', 'how', 'would live', 'million people', 'birth world', 'left given', 'dollar organization', 'organization would', 'wait', 'myth blm', 'wait antifa', 'given birth', 'this', 'people vote', 'would left', 'like would', 'world million', 'antifa myth', 'live like', 'would']",politics,0.35,0.029,0,0.8096590909090909,0.35,1,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.01219106182047749,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339231336867966980,96354f80deab70e6e022faa66d4c21be4130af9bcc569890c33d17f01e4d046f,1339230232088367105,07f9ebe35e2ea9babe6c54f49f8209b7087cb9db95781878e1a88c891a994a91,2020-12-16 15:30:07,It’s really wonderful what they’ve been able to build,9,0,1,really wonderful theyve able build,"wonderful able, able build, really wonderful, []",0.75,"[101, 2428, 6919, 2027, 3726, 2583, 3857, 102]",2020-12-16,"['[]', 'wonderful able', 'able build', 'really wonderful']",general,0.1,0.011,0,0.7088068181818182,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.004505785170242464,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339342589951176718,3307cc064e814e9b09ef12592ba7733dfcc338ebeb8be88bd6f58ec58f19d2af,1339230232088367105,07f9ebe35e2ea9babe6c54f49f8209b7087cb9db95781878e1a88c891a994a91,2020-12-16 22:52:11,"Wow, Seattle is starting to look like a third world country. WOW.",5,1,1,wow seattle starting look like world country wow,"look like, third world, country wow, [('Seattle', seattle starting, starting look, world country, like third, 'GPE'), ('WOW', wow, 'ORG')], seattle, wow seattle",0.05,"[101, 10166, 5862, 3225, 2298, 2066, 2088, 2406, 10166, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('Seattle'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('WOW'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'look like', 'third world', 'country wow', 'seattle starting', 'starting look', 'world country', 'like third', 'wow', 'seattle', 'wow seattle']",general,0.0,0.01,0,0.6910511363636364,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0041454708862291405,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339345626119671809,90e95061d5e7eda0d4e583aded0d5bd8837ba6eaee95e6818137a2b11209c1fe,1339230232088367105,07f9ebe35e2ea9babe6c54f49f8209b7087cb9db95781878e1a88c891a994a91,2020-12-16 23:04:15,"I’ve said it before and will again. I have no more sympathy for the folks living there. If they won’t band together to stop this, so be it.",7,0,3,ive said sympathy folks living wont band stop,"living band, [], folks living, together stop, said sympathy, band together, sympathy folks",-0.25,"[101, 4921, 2063, 2056, 11883, 12455, 2542, 2180, 2102, 2316, 2644, 102]",2020-12-16,"['[]', 'living band', 'folks living', 'together stop', 'said sympathy', 'band together', 'sympathy folks']",general,0.0,0.013,0,0.7372159090909091,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.005415664042641564,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339232994905743360,556436ae3e6e5b0fe82ca0d655254b38fd6df608a130b0e0e65455d08775b189,1339230232088367105,07f9ebe35e2ea9babe6c54f49f8209b7087cb9db95781878e1a88c891a994a91,2020-12-16 15:36:42,"Keep the faith, Trump’s hellfire is about to rain down on the anarcho-communists and the deep state.",4,1,2,faith trumps hellfire rain anarchocommunists deep state,"hellfire rain, deep state, rain deep, keep, keep faith, 'ORG')], faith trump, trump hellfire, [('Trump', trump",-0.0777777777777777,"[101, 4752, 8398, 2015, 3109, 10273, 4542, 9617, 11140, 24163, 7382, 19496, 12837, 2784, 2110, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'faith trump', 'trump', 'hellfire rain', 'deep state', 'keep', 'trump hellfire', 'rain deep', 'keep faith']",politics,0.0,0.011,0,0.7088068181818182,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.00460041032242869,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1337813537482223618,65807fa478cffb9bd0fb47d29754ff669e744e746639ef8ebe85eb26a36fb9b4,1337813537482223618,,2020-12-12 17:36:17,"WATCH: Trump supporters gather in Washington, D.C. on Saturday.",589,302,441,watch trump supporters gather washington dc saturday,"[('Washington', watch trump, washington, watch, d.c., 'DATE')], trump supporters, 'GPE'), ('D.C.', ('Saturday', saturday, gather washington, washington saturday, supporters gather, trump",0.0,"[101, 3422, 8398, 6793, 8587, 2899, 5887, 5095, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Washington'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('D.C.'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('Saturday'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'watch trump', 'washington', 'watch', 'd.c.', 'trump supporters', 'saturday', 'gather washington', 'washington saturday', 'supporters gather', 'trump']",politics,0.0,1.0,1,0.9822443181818182,0.0,0,0,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,0,0.5951184406178321,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337814925301919744,d68c069e1e83fed486cf3f7061cba08aad0264c5c1f453acdc49ab9f658a4a4f,1337813537482223618,65807fa478cffb9bd0fb47d29754ff669e744e746639ef8ebe85eb26a36fb9b4,2020-12-12 17:41:48,Imagine if women turned out in support of Trump? It might look like this.,30,6,0,imagine women turned support trump look like,"look like, trump might, turned support, might look, women turned, imagine women, support trump, 'ORG')], imagine, [('Trump', trump",0.0,"[101, 5674, 2308, 2357, 2490, 8398, 2298, 2066, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'look like', 'trump might', 'turned support', 'might look', 'women turned', 'imagine women', 'support trump', 'imagine', 'trump']",politics,0.0,0.048,1,0.8387784090909091,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.019712681259751792,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337813689378861056,3d79f3447f1dbe581c42a5509fc266f894c9e1183b63db8ec375d8763d8632cd,1337813537482223618,65807fa478cffb9bd0fb47d29754ff669e744e746639ef8ebe85eb26a36fb9b4,2020-12-12 17:36:53,Is this Egypt? Cause that looks like a river of denial,48,0,6,egypt cause looks like river denial,"egypt, looks like, [('Egypt', egypt cause, like river, cause looks, 'GPE')], cause, river denial",0.0,"[101, 5279, 3426, 3504, 2066, 2314, 14920, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Egypt'"", "" 'GPE')]"", 'egypt', 'looks like', 'egypt cause', 'cause looks', 'cause', 'river denial', 'like river']",general,0.0,0.06,1,0.859375,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.024604203581029035,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337818431907880961,6fd6248fa3a67e477697b0a68aeb9a131a9c9fe3143729c464b11345e8ae9f09,1337813537482223618,65807fa478cffb9bd0fb47d29754ff669e744e746639ef8ebe85eb26a36fb9b4,2020-12-12 17:55:44,How did they scrape up the gas money?,25,1,0,did scrape gas money,"gas money, scrape gas, how, []",0.0,"[101, 2106, 26988, 3806, 2769, 102]",2020-12-12,"['[]', 'gas money', 'scrape gas', 'how']",general,0.0,0.028,1,0.8068181818181818,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.011387138344711127,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337813722144837632,456255708069f2dc82f9f2e637c79c111e9ae0eb162b437160e7e019d5308ced,1337813537482223618,65807fa478cffb9bd0fb47d29754ff669e744e746639ef8ebe85eb26a36fb9b4,2020-12-12 17:37:01,Who cares what they do,26,0,1,cares,"who, []",0.0,"[101, 14977, 102]",2020-12-12,"['[]', 'who']",general,0.0,0.028,1,0.8068181818181818,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.011392222918115417,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337815027437473794,f1671c54ef2a76948cf44857e08d86ad296328ee7f1a9086528013caaded7427,1337813537482223618,65807fa478cffb9bd0fb47d29754ff669e744e746639ef8ebe85eb26a36fb9b4,2020-12-12 17:42:12,Maybe more of them should have voted in the election. It’s tough to carry a candidate with approval in the low 40’s over the finish line.,12,1,2,maybe voted election tough carry candidate approval low 40s finish line,"vote, voted election, maybe, candidate approval, 'CARDINAL')], approval low, candidate, low finish, election tough, maybe voted, finish line, election, [('40', tough carry, carry candidate",0.037037037037037,"[101, 2672, 5444, 2602, 7823, 4287, 4018, 6226, 2659, 2871, 2015, 3926, 2240, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('40'"", "" 'CARDINAL')]"", 'vote', 'voted election', 'maybe', 'candidate approval', 'approval low', 'candidate', 'low finish', 'election tough', 'maybe voted', 'finish line', 'election', 'tough carry', 'carry candidate']",politics,0.0,0.019,1,0.7819602272727273,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.00784108690966302,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337814119072886784,0c71d1838e23d58ffbf0bd97558af5bc7b60de1a3e687ad5a72cc8ef35d04c61,1337813537482223618,65807fa478cffb9bd0fb47d29754ff669e744e746639ef8ebe85eb26a36fb9b4,2020-12-12 17:38:36,"If Trump was the patriot he claims to be, he would quash this foolishness, admit he has lost fair and square, concede the election and tell his sycophants to go home.   Election is over, but oh now....he cant do that.",12,0,5,trump patriot claims quash foolishness admit lost fair square concede election tell sycophants home election oh nowhe,"square concede, tell sycophants, claims would, fair square, election cant, trump patriot, election, [('Trump', trump, election tell, patriot claims, lost fair, sycophants home, if trump, home election, admit lost, foolishness admit, quash foolishness, concede election, 'PERSON')], would quash, riot",0.7,"[101, 8398, 16419, 4447, 24209, 11823, 13219, 2791, 6449, 2439, 4189, 2675, 9530, 22119, 2602, 2425, 25353, 3597, 21890, 7666, 2188, 2602, 2821, 2085, 5369, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Trump'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'square concede', 'tell sycophants', 'claims would', 'fair square', 'election cant', 'trump patriot', 'election', 'trump', 'election tell', 'patriot claims', 'lost fair', 'sycophants home', 'if trump', 'home election', 'admit lost', 'foolishness admit', 'quash foolishness', 'concede election', 'would quash', 'riot']",politics,0.0,0.022,1,0.7876420454545454,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.005171304075679287,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337814154921431040,8ab2b6e4b24ad8bc200eba8aee8095385d0c608aa783e6d40430eeca1a60c6e1,1337813537482223618,65807fa478cffb9bd0fb47d29754ff669e744e746639ef8ebe85eb26a36fb9b4,2020-12-12 17:38:44,WOW That crowd is almost as big as his Inaugeration,12,0,0,wow crowd big inaugeration,"that, almost big, crowd almost, inaugeration, wow crowd, crowd, big inaugeration, [('WOW', ('Inaugeration', 'FAC')], 'ORG')",0.05,"[101, 10166, 4306, 2502, 27118, 22890, 8156, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('WOW'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Inaugeration'"", "" 'FAC')]"", 'that', 'almost big', 'crowd almost', 'wow crowd', 'crowd', 'big inaugeration', 'inaugeration']",protest,0.0,0.012,1,0.7237215909090909,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.004861014880851497,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337816652361199618,13cd35e644350b1b2d6699b292d293653a125830638b7b27c0ae5a26c6030a47,1337813537482223618,65807fa478cffb9bd0fb47d29754ff669e744e746639ef8ebe85eb26a36fb9b4,2020-12-12 17:48:40,How come he had 71 million votes and can only get a crowd of around a thousand like this in Washington? Something fishy - this shows the true cult of Trump ... which really is pretty small!,8,2,0,come 71 million votes crowd thousand like washington fishy shows true cult trump really pretty small,"vote, come million, pretty small, washington something, how, cult trump, something, trump really, really pretty, thousand like, ('Washington', true cult, fishy shows, 'ORG')], trump, million votes, votes get, crowd around, crowd, around thousand, [('71 million', washington, like washington, ('Trump', 'CARDINAL'), 'GPE'), ('around a thousand'",0.071875,"[101, 2272, 6390, 2454, 4494, 4306, 4595, 2066, 2899, 3869, 2100, 3065, 2995, 8754, 8398, 2428, 3492, 2235, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('71 million'"", "" 'CARDINAL')"", "" ('around a thousand'"", "" 'CARDINAL')"", "" ('Washington'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'vote', 'come million', 'pretty small', 'washington something', 'how', 'cult trump', 'something', 'trump really', 'thousand like', 'really pretty', 'true cult', 'fishy shows', 'trump', 'million votes', 'votes get', 'crowd around', 'crowd', 'around thousand', 'washington', 'like washington']",politics,0.15000000000000002,0.014,1,0.7514204545454546,0.15000000000000002,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.005760724606442016,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337813634639155201,df443970ccb01ec6d4b581afbd659e8250587b52c7fd28ddc2d4dc918be4886f,1337813537482223618,65807fa478cffb9bd0fb47d29754ff669e744e746639ef8ebe85eb26a36fb9b4,2020-12-12 17:36:40,"Am I the only one hoping to watch the Secret Service carry that Orange Clown out on January 20th? 
#ITSOVER",10,0,2,hoping watch secret service carry orange clown january 20th itsover,"('January 20th', watch secret, clown january, #itsover, ('ITSOVER', 'LOC'), carry orange, january itsover, ('Orange Clown', [('the Secret Service', january, one hoping, service carry, 'DATE'), hoping watch, orange clown, 'PERSON')], secret service, 'ORG')",-0.1333333333333333,"[101, 5327, 3422, 3595, 2326, 4287, 4589, 15912, 2254, 3983, 2049, 7840, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('the Secret Service'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Orange Clown'"", "" 'LOC')"", "" ('January 20th'"", "" 'DATE')"", "" ('ITSOVER'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'one hoping', 'orange clown', 'service carry', 'january itsover', 'watch secret', 'clown january', '#itsover', 'secret service', 'hoping watch', 'january', 'carry orange']",general,0.0,0.014,1,0.7514204545454546,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.005770893753250598,0,1,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1345179662880624641,f2cff1b2acb9ffe35a3315f1d24e27f9d7cd065b34670be3905c5406cf9b115a,1345179662880624641,,2021-01-02 01:26:38,"NEW YEAR’S EVE DESTRUCTION: Capitol Hill biz owners and neighbors are fed up with black bloc marchers wrecking the city. The owner of Cafe Argento says they’re being targeted for just trying to improve the neighborhood.

Story 6pm 
@komonews
 

#seattle #CalAndersonPark",271,112,56,new years eve destruction capitol hill biz owners neighbors fed black bloc marchers wrecking city owner cafe argento says theyre targeted just trying improve neighborhood story 6pm komonews seattle calandersonpark,"the, 'CARDINAL')], marchers wrecking, wrecking city, #seattle, story, argento says, calandersonpark, march, destruction capitol, owners neighbors, ('#', @komonews, hill biz, year, seattle calandersonpark, story komonews, fed black, neighborhood story, improve neighborhood, ('Cafe Argento', new year, year eve, [('Capitol Hill', ('6pm', 'TIME'), 'ORG')",-0.0151515151515151,"[101, 2047, 2086, 6574, 6215, 9424, 2940, 12170, 2480, 5608, 10638, 7349, 2304, 15984, 28791, 2869, 12006, 2075, 2103, 3954, 7668, 23157, 2080, 2758, 2027, 2890, 9416, 2074, 2667, 5335, 5101, 2466, 1020, 9737, 12849, 8202, 7974, 2015, 5862, 10250, 12243, 3385, 14432, 102]",2021-01-02,"[""[('Capitol Hill'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Cafe Argento'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('6pm'"", "" 'TIME')"", "" ('#'"", "" 'CARDINAL')]"", 'the', 'marchers wrecking', 'wrecking city', '#seattle', 'story', 'argento says', 'calandersonpark', 'march', 'destruction capitol', 'owners neighbors', '@komonews', 'hill biz', 'year', 'seattle calandersonpark', 'story komonews', 'fed black', 'neighborhood story', 'improve neighborhood', 'new year', 'year eve']",protest,0.0,0.719,0,0.9573863636363636,0.0,0,0,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,0,0.2990619530060084,1,2,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345186143931797505,a38d2d42a88284836e2c9db2de4ef2e73617130d269de2b2b18302dcf8aebdd2,1345179662880624641,f2cff1b2acb9ffe35a3315f1d24e27f9d7cd065b34670be3905c5406cf9b115a,2021-01-02 01:52:23,"Well, when you catch and release these idiots night after night, this is what happens. Maybe try voting next time for a candidate without a “D” next to their name. This will never end.",68,3,4,catch release idiots night night happens maybe try voting time candidate d end,"try voting, without next, voting next, candidate without, happens maybe, candidate, maybe try, maybe, [('night', release idiots, catch release, well, this, name never, idiots night, next name, well catch, night night, never end, time candidate, 'TIME')], next time",-0.2666666666666666,"[101, 4608, 2713, 28781, 2305, 2305, 6433, 2672, 3046, 6830, 2051, 4018, 1040, 2203, 102]",2021-01-02,"[""[('night'"", "" 'TIME')]"", 'try voting', 'without next', 'voting next', 'candidate without', 'happens maybe', 'candidate', 'maybe try', 'maybe', 'release idiots', 'catch release', 'well', 'this', 'name never', 'idiots night', 'next name', 'well catch', 'night night', 'never end', 'time candidate', 'next time']",politics,0.30000000000000004,0.085,0,0.8735795454545454,0.30000000000000004,1,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0347659190587187,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345182726584844290,85a3c396cadc956c9e0c779bb8436644cb49734e5ff7aea37ecf4ee292871458,1345179662880624641,f2cff1b2acb9ffe35a3315f1d24e27f9d7cd065b34670be3905c5406cf9b115a,2021-01-02 01:38:48,Why bother trying to improve the neighborhood. Open in a place that will appreciate your efforts,43,0,1,bother trying improve neighborhood open place appreciate efforts,"why, open place, [], neighborhood open, open, bother trying, place appreciate, appreciate efforts, trying improve, improve neighborhood",0.0,"[101, 8572, 2667, 5335, 5101, 2330, 2173, 9120, 4073, 102]",2021-01-02,"['[]', 'why', 'open place', 'neighborhood open', 'open', 'bother trying', 'place appreciate', 'appreciate efforts', 'trying improve', 'improve neighborhood']",general,0.0,0.045,0,0.8338068181818182,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.018278660665988367,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345180938653732870,bf8c2e816d8abe2c0f6695a87cb03faaf5f0a433dff6fd0d520440095a4d3f67,1345179662880624641,f2cff1b2acb9ffe35a3315f1d24e27f9d7cd065b34670be3905c5406cf9b115a,2021-01-02 01:31:42,"Smashing up another LGBT POC owned small business. 

It feels like the gay bars/clubs/even coffee shops are targeted more then anyone else. 
Look what happened to QueerBar & Neighbors.",14,0,2,smashing lgbt poc owned small business feels like gay barsclubseven coffee shops targeted look happened queerbar neighbors,"lgbt poc, neighbors, feels like, poc owned, owned small, look happened, queerbar, lgbt, anyone else, 'ORG')], ('QueerBar & Neighbors', queerbar neighbors, smashing, happened queerbar, coffee shops, business feels, gay coffee, else look, targeted anyone, smashing another, shops targeted, look, [('LGBT POC', 'ORG')",0.2222222222222222,"[101, 21105, 12010, 13433, 2278, 3079, 2235, 2449, 5683, 2066, 5637, 6963, 20464, 12083, 3366, 8159, 4157, 7340, 9416, 2298, 3047, 19483, 8237, 10638, 102]",2021-01-02,"[""[('LGBT POC'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('QueerBar & Neighbors'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'lgbt poc', 'neighbors', 'feels like', 'poc owned', 'owned small', 'look happened', 'queerbar', 'lgbt', 'anyone else', 'queerbar neighbors', 'smashing', 'happened queerbar', 'coffee shops', 'business feels', 'gay coffee', 'else look', 'targeted anyone', 'smashing another', 'shops targeted', 'look']",general,0.1,0.018,0,0.7762784090909091,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0073912320468677625,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345181731200983041,30f147af3e6d2ce4bbabaf8276e6435962fc6ffde37e04769a8128cc596f34ad,1345179662880624641,f2cff1b2acb9ffe35a3315f1d24e27f9d7cd065b34670be3905c5406cf9b115a,2021-01-02 01:34:51,It is never ok to destroy someone else’s property.  If you do not like a business don’t go there.,9,0,0,ok destroy elses property like business dont,"[], destroy someone, property like, like business, never destroy, else property, someone else",-0.225,"[101, 7929, 6033, 2842, 2015, 3200, 2066, 2449, 2123, 2102, 102]",2021-01-02,"['[]', 'destroy someone', 'property like', 'like business', 'never destroy', 'else property', 'someone else']",general,0.1,0.009,0,0.6725852272727273,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.003645761160638622,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345195592004194305,75f10b047d7fd03f769e2a19f8e32cd2166457088d3d19b501107897863ffec9,1345179662880624641,f2cff1b2acb9ffe35a3315f1d24e27f9d7cd065b34670be3905c5406cf9b115a,2021-01-02 02:29:56,The coming backlash will be severe.,9,0,1,coming backlash severe,"the, coming backlash, backlash severe, []",0.0,"[101, 2746, 25748, 5729, 102]",2021-01-02,"['[]', 'backlash severe', 'coming backlash', 'the']",general,0.0,0.011,0,0.7088068181818182,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.004505785170242464,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345235076913782784,4fb656e3e4e34f79f63ae2f32ef2624899b309b97ae9457b18f48dcff33ef1dc,1345179662880624641,f2cff1b2acb9ffe35a3315f1d24e27f9d7cd065b34670be3905c5406cf9b115a,2021-01-02 05:06:50,You should ask all these fed up residents and business owners who they have been voting for over the last 10-15 years....,9,0,1,ask fed residents business owners voting 1015 years,"voting last, [('the last', owners voting, ask fed, 'DATE')], 'DATE'), last years, business owners, residents business, fed residents, ('10-15 years', you",0.0,"[101, 3198, 7349, 3901, 2449, 5608, 6830, 7886, 2629, 2086, 102]",2021-01-02,"[""[('the last'"", "" 'DATE')"", "" ('10-15 years'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'voting last', 'owners voting', 'ask fed', 'last years', 'business owners', 'residents business', 'fed residents', 'you']",general,0.1,0.011,0,0.7088068181818182,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.004505785170242464,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345211225475571713,b236ece3ba572f0e4d5e8c581ff5414042f1a2dc13e277be7b46f8745b47fb7a,1345179662880624641,f2cff1b2acb9ffe35a3315f1d24e27f9d7cd065b34670be3905c5406cf9b115a,2021-01-02 03:32:03,You voted them into power.,4,0,0,voted power,"vote, you, [], voted power",0.0,"[101, 5444, 2373, 102]",2021-01-02,"['[]', 'vote', 'voted power', 'you']",politics,0.0,0.004,0,0.5568181818181818,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0016203382936171656,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345185595891404800,2bd7216880482b37e8dca3bf4ae8e8df2f2bb3c0913c8a2cbb941ad1f5b2dafa,1345179662880624641,f2cff1b2acb9ffe35a3315f1d24e27f9d7cd065b34670be3905c5406cf9b115a,2021-01-02 01:50:13,"Congrats, Jeff Bezos is now that much richer.",3,0,0,congrats jeff bezos richer,"jeff bezos, [('Congrats', congrats, 'NORP'), bezos much, much richer, 'PERSON')], ('Jeff Bezos', congrats jeff",0.2,"[101, 26478, 8609, 2015, 5076, 2022, 28370, 26108, 102]",2021-01-02,"[""[('Congrats'"", "" 'NORP')"", "" ('Jeff Bezos'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'jeff bezos', 'congrats', 'bezos much', 'much richer', 'congrats jeff']",general,0.2,0.003,0,0.5035511363636364,0.2,1,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0012152537202128743,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345401572898050050,c0fe608646facba8594812cd59c7a1539c1bb50a272288bbc092fe0df91752cd,1345179662880624641,f2cff1b2acb9ffe35a3315f1d24e27f9d7cd065b34670be3905c5406cf9b115a,2021-01-02 16:08:25,These people are so destructive. If they could only put their energy into something positive and constructive.,3,0,0,people destructive energy positive constructive,"people destructive, put energy, something positive, [], could put, destructive could, positive constructive, these, energy something",-0.1242424242424242,"[101, 2111, 15615, 2943, 3893, 26157, 102]",2021-01-02,"['[]', 'people destructive', 'put energy', 'something positive', 'could put', 'destructive could', 'positive constructive', 'these', 'energy something']",general,0.2,0.003,0,0.5035511363636364,0.2,1,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0012152537202128743,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345182925621317639,05ec97a709df99c95e9a3839a4e37928d7a91a84abdb04a675b29cdc426fff8c,1345179662880624641,f2cff1b2acb9ffe35a3315f1d24e27f9d7cd065b34670be3905c5406cf9b115a,2021-01-02 01:39:36,Time for him to buy a gun.,2,0,0,time buy gun,"time, time buy, [], buy gun",0.0,"[101, 2051, 4965, 3282, 102]",2021-01-02,"['[]', 'time', 'time buy', 'buy gun']",general,0.0,0.002,0,0.4169034090909091,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0008101691468085828,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345201642224943105,eb8249a505bcba5efc4f38ebc7aa9e792ba336e0f2c158cfd429460c0a0e1c42,1345179662880624641,f2cff1b2acb9ffe35a3315f1d24e27f9d7cd065b34670be3905c5406cf9b115a,2021-01-02 02:53:58,"Too bad.
Why don't they ask their stupid fellow citizens to stop voting for far-left appeasers of this cancerous ideology?
And if their fellow citizens aren't interested in safety, amenity, economic prosperity etc. then get the hell out of these rotten far-left hellholes!",1,0,0,bad dont ask stupid fellow citizens stop voting farleft appeasers cancerous ideology fellow citizens arent interested safety amenity economic prosperity hell rotten farleft hellholes,"get hell, [], amenity economic, citizen, citizens interested, safety amenity, why, stop voting, interested safety, economic prosperity, appeasers cancerous, ask stupid, bad ask, rotten hellholes, citizens stop, voting appeasers, cancerous ideology, too, stupid fellow, ideology fellow, etc get",-0.2499999999999999,"[101, 2919, 2123, 2102, 3198, 5236, 3507, 4480, 2644, 6830, 2521, 2571, 6199, 10439, 19500, 2869, 4456, 3560, 13165, 3507, 4480, 4995, 2102, 4699, 3808, 2572, 20693, 3171, 14165, 3109, 11083, 2521, 2571, 6199, 3109, 19990, 102]",2021-01-02,"['[]', 'get hell', 'amenity economic', 'citizen', 'citizens interested', 'safety amenity', 'why', 'stop voting', 'interested safety', 'economic prosperity', 'appeasers cancerous', 'ask stupid', 'bad ask', 'rotten hellholes', 'citizens stop', 'voting appeasers', 'cancerous ideology', 'too', 'stupid fellow', 'ideology fellow', 'etc get']",immigration,0.45,0.001,0,0.30610795454545453,0.45,2,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339624669750681600,74a2655eccdfd3d33b2efc40ec7cbb82761bf628b679997f0b25068a169f74eb,1339624669750681600,,2020-12-17 17:33:04,"Today, our frontline workers received their first dose of the COVID-19 vaccine at Kaiser Permanente in Capitol Hill. These vaccinations will save lives & protect our first responders, their patients, and their families. 

There is reason to have hope. 

#GetVaccinatedDC, #DCHOPE",154,38,10,today frontline workers received dose covid19 vaccine kaiser permanente capitol hill vaccinations save lives protect responders patients families reason hope getvaccinateddc dchope,"('COVID-19', received first, [('Today', these, hope getvaccinateddc, there, ('DCHOPE', reason hope, vaccinations save, lives protect, hill vaccinations, ('Capitol Hill', kaiser permanente, dose vaccine, 'ORDINAL'), permanente capitol, vaccine kaiser, protect first, ('Kaiser Permanente', getvaccinateddc dchope, ('first', patients families, 'DATE'), save lives, workers received, #dchope, responders patients, families reason, 'FAC'), 'PERSON')], 'ORG')",0.25,"[101, 2651, 2392, 4179, 3667, 2363, 13004, 2522, 17258, 16147, 17404, 15676, 4568, 2063, 9424, 2940, 12436, 14693, 9323, 2015, 3828, 3268, 4047, 6869, 2545, 5022, 2945, 3114, 3246, 2131, 24887, 28748, 3064, 16409, 5887, 26441, 102]",2020-12-17,"[""[('Today'"", "" 'DATE')"", "" ('first'"", "" 'ORDINAL')"", "" ('COVID-19'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Kaiser Permanente'"", "" 'FAC')"", "" ('Capitol Hill'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('first'"", "" 'ORDINAL')"", "" ('DCHOPE'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'received first', 'there', 'these', 'hope getvaccinateddc', 'reason hope', 'vaccinations save', 'lives protect', 'hill vaccinations', 'kaiser permanente', 'dose vaccine', 'permanente capitol', 'vaccine kaiser', 'protect first', 'getvaccinateddc dchope', 'patients families', 'save lives', 'workers received', '#dchope', 'responders patients', 'families reason']",general,0.0,0.288,1,0.9105113636363636,0.0,0,0,activity_spike,"[](10), 'PERSON')](5), trump(4), 'FAC')(3), 'ORG')(3)","Guardian correlation: How many times has Trump lost the election ahahahaha | First Dog on the Moon (score: 2, strength: medium)",general,0,0.11886417676524526,0,2,0,3,0.16666666666666666
1341245162442375168,27b7abf5c23fb2ed00c8a578f0bf2b401403fded4320926469b6cb149ffb6a18,1339624669750681600,74a2655eccdfd3d33b2efc40ec7cbb82761bf628b679997f0b25068a169f74eb,2020-12-22 04:52:20,"Why is the Director of Health, Dr. LaQuandra Nesbitt, always so  unhappy?",1,0,0,director health dr laquandra nesbitt unhappy,"nesbitt, health laquandra, always unhappy, why, health, nesbitt always, director, 'PERSON')], director health, laquandra nesbitt, [('LaQuandra Nesbitt'",-0.6,"[101, 2472, 2740, 2852, 2474, 16211, 17670, 24524, 16313, 2102, 12511, 102]",2020-12-22,"[""[('LaQuandra Nesbitt'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'nesbitt', 'health laquandra', 'always unhappy', 'why', 'nesbitt always', 'laquandra nesbitt', 'director', 'director health', 'health']",general,0.1,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.1,0,1,activity_spike,"nesbitt(1), health laquandra(1), always unhappy(1), why(1), health(1)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,3,0.16666666666666666
1339677807740383234,7c0b6d832e90199f035b6da54925ba827a98b54cae08d9eabea4023398ed3dce,1339624669750681600,74a2655eccdfd3d33b2efc40ec7cbb82761bf628b679997f0b25068a169f74eb,2020-12-17 21:04:14,Thank you for the update Madam Mayor,0,0,1,thank update madam mayor,"[('Madam', thank update, 'PERSON')], update madam, madam mayor, thank",0.0,"[101, 4067, 10651, 21658, 3664, 102]",2020-12-17,"[""[('Madam'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'thank update', 'madam mayor', 'update madam', 'thank']",general,0.0,0.002,1,0.4169034090909091,0.0,0,1,activity_spike,"[](10), 'PERSON')](5), trump(4), 'FAC')(3), 'ORG')(3)","Guardian correlation: How many times has Trump lost the election ahahahaha | First Dog on the Moon (score: 2, strength: medium)",general,1,0.0008600240096038416,0,0,0,3,0.16666666666666666
1346148068773789697,8e7af6eeb427f32793662d13debb9d29525ce4f02116759d091f329b1310310b,1346148068773789697,,2021-01-04 17:34:44,"At least a dozen GOP senators are vowing to challenge President-elect Joe Biden’s election victory on Wednesday.

Some have cited baseless conspiracy theories about the election as disputes over the results split the Republican party on Capitol Hill.",4,6,6,dozen gop senators vowing challenge presidentelect joe bidens election victory wednesday cited baseless conspiracy theories election disputes results split republican party capitol hill,"wednesday, biden, joe biden, ('the Republican party', results split, challenge joe, victory wednesday, ('Wednesday', cited baseless, vowing challenge, [('At least a dozen', theories election, gop, election disputes, conspiracy theories, some, ('Capitol Hill', election, 'ORG')], dozen gop, ('GOP', 'PERSON'), split republican, president, ('Joe Biden’s', 'DATE'), disputes results, baseless conspiracy, republican, 'CARDINAL'), 'ORG')",-0.3,"[101, 6474, 2175, 2361, 10153, 19076, 2075, 4119, 2343, 12260, 6593, 3533, 7226, 6132, 2602, 3377, 9317, 6563, 14040, 7971, 9714, 8106, 2602, 11936, 3463, 3975, 3951, 2283, 9424, 2940, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('At least a dozen'"", "" 'CARDINAL')"", "" ('GOP'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Joe Biden’s'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Wednesday'"", "" 'DATE')"", "" ('the Republican party'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Capitol Hill'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'wednesday', 'biden', 'joe biden', 'results split', 'challenge joe', 'victory wednesday', 'cited baseless', 'vowing challenge', 'theories election', 'gop', 'election disputes', 'conspiracy theories', 'some', 'election', 'dozen gop', 'split republican', 'president', 'disputes results', 'baseless conspiracy', 'republican']",politics,0.1,0.034,1,0.8160511363636364,0.1,0,0,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,0,0.11672430940038128,0,0,0,5,0.2777777777777778
1346148970440118274,a03c84e886cd856676b0b135d158b3d566969fbe8ebdcbc3130d7bb229f07ea1,1346148068773789697,8e7af6eeb427f32793662d13debb9d29525ce4f02116759d091f329b1310310b,2021-01-04 17:38:19,cBSnews  M$M,1,0,0,cbsnews mm,[],0.0,"[101, 6568, 2638, 9333, 3461, 102]",2021-01-04,['[]'],general,0.0,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,5,0.2777777777777778
1346183164989992960,99b162c0618450ab650f8c9cfd3e1c02fa7b8ffec067381cce74e7ab177dccc3,1346148068773789697,8e7af6eeb427f32793662d13debb9d29525ce4f02116759d091f329b1310310b,2021-01-04 19:54:12,Is this the seditious twelve ,1,0,0,seditious,"[('twelve', seditious twelve, 'CARDINAL')]",0.0,"[101, 7367, 23194, 6313, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('twelve'"", "" 'CARDINAL')]"", 'seditious twelve']",general,0.0,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,5,0.2777777777777778
1346150649780719617,fb6ffd3642ff907e94044206079ba3b187d119b805b95e57fa87f1825af3c0f4,1346148068773789697,8e7af6eeb427f32793662d13debb9d29525ce4f02116759d091f329b1310310b,2021-01-04 17:44:59,"They know that it won’t go anywhere, but their objections are going to be rejected by the Senate when it comes to a vote. It’s about their future political ambitions.",0,0,0,know wont objections going rejected senate comes vote future political ambitions,"vote, rejected senate, going rejected, political, vote future, objections going, know anywhere, political ambitions, anywhere objections, senate comes, comes vote, 'ORG')], senate, [('Senate', they, future political",0.0,"[101, 2113, 2180, 2102, 17304, 2183, 5837, 4001, 3310, 3789, 2925, 2576, 19509, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Senate'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'going rejected', 'rejected senate', 'vote', 'political', 'vote future', 'objections going', 'political ambitions', 'anywhere objections', 'senate comes', 'comes vote', 'senate', 'future political', 'they', 'know anywhere']",politics,0.0,0.0,1,0.12428977272727272,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0,0,0,0,5,0.2777777777777778
1346153959619231746,41c69bbc9427f818a3b3dcc56447bc12a0e33704e2c0f53a8454127df31a4016,1346148068773789697,8e7af6eeb427f32793662d13debb9d29525ce4f02116759d091f329b1310310b,2021-01-04 17:58:08,"Why describe it as “baseless conspiracy theories” when there is video evidence showing suitcases of ballots being drawn under a covered table after the Republican poll watchers were told to go home.
These tens of thousands of ballots were then processed between 10.35 pm and1.00am",0,0,0,baseless conspiracy theories video evidence showing suitcases ballots drawn covered table republican poll watchers told home tens thousands ballots processed 1035 pm and100am,"'NORP'), ballots drawn, table republican, ballots processed, video evidence, these, suitcases ballots, told home, why, [('Republican', ('These tens of thousands', evidence showing, conspiracy theories, showing suitcases, poll watchers, covered table, baseless conspiracy, watchers told, republican, republican poll, home tens, thousands ballots, tens thousands, 'CARDINAL'), ('10.35 pm', 'TIME')]",0.0,"[101, 14040, 7971, 9714, 8106, 2678, 3350, 4760, 15940, 2015, 17069, 4567, 3139, 2795, 3951, 8554, 3422, 2545, 2409, 2188, 15295, 5190, 17069, 13995, 9800, 2629, 7610, 1998, 18613, 3286, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Republican'"", "" 'NORP')"", "" ('These tens of thousands'"", "" 'CARDINAL')"", "" ('10.35 pm'"", "" 'TIME')]"", 'ballots drawn', 'table republican', 'ballots processed', 'video evidence', 'these', 'suitcases ballots', 'told home', 'why', 'evidence showing', 'conspiracy theories', 'showing suitcases', 'poll watchers', 'covered table', 'baseless conspiracy', 'watchers told', 'republican', 'republican poll', 'home tens', 'thousands ballots', 'tens thousands']",politics,0.1,0.0,1,0.12428977272727272,0.1,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0,0,0,0,5,0.2777777777777778
1335507416331390976,0511c7cc808268a5bf20f33df0ce466dfc5384444859dbdd521530328eba3801,1335507416331390976,,2020-12-06 08:52:35,"OLYMPIA, WA: Shots were fired earlier today outside of the Washington State Capitol during a clash between Antifa Militants and Patriots. The Olympia Police Department has the man in custody and is investigating.

*Warning*—Video Via BL Ranch on YT",211,84,27,olympia wa shots fired earlier today outside washington state capitol clash antifa militants patriots olympia police department man custody investigating warningvideo bl ranch yt,"patriots, washington state capitol, ranch, ('Capitol', warning via, ('Antifa Militants', shots fired, olympia police, ('The Olympia Police Department', 'GPE')], today outside, capitol clash, the olympia police department, ('Washington State', shots, fired earlier, olympia shots, ('YT', police, antifa militants, state capitol, ('Patriots', warning, patriots olympia, police department, custody investigating, clash antifa, 'GPE'), 'TIME'), [('earlier today', 'ORG')",0.0,"[101, 17096, 11333, 7171, 5045, 3041, 2651, 2648, 2899, 2110, 9424, 13249, 3424, 7011, 17671, 11579, 17096, 2610, 2533, 2158, 9968, 11538, 5432, 17258, 8780, 1038, 2140, 8086, 1061, 2102, 102]",2020-12-06,"[""[('earlier today'"", "" 'TIME')"", "" ('Washington State'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('Capitol'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Antifa Militants'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Patriots'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('The Olympia Police Department'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('YT'"", "" 'GPE')]"", 'patriots', 'washington state capitol', 'ranch', 'warning via', 'shots fired', 'olympia police', 'today outside', 'capitol clash', 'the olympia police department', 'shots', 'fired earlier', 'olympia shots', 'police', 'antifa militants', 'state capitol', 'warning', 'patriots olympia', 'police department', 'custody investigating', 'clash antifa']",protest,0.6000000000000001,0.517,0,0.9488636363636364,0.6000000000000001,3,0,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,0,0.12456864965572008,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1335507418411745283,0511c7cc808268a5bf20f33df0ce466dfc5384444859dbdd521530328eba3801,1335507416331390976,0511c7cc808268a5bf20f33df0ce466dfc5384444859dbdd521530328eba3801,2020-12-06 08:52:35,"Statement from 
@OlyPD
:",34,7,4,statement olypd,"statement olypd, @olypd, [], statement",0.0,"[101, 4861, 19330, 22571, 2094, 102]",2020-12-06,"['[]', 'statement olypd', '@olypd', 'statement']",general,0.0,0.063,0,0.8607954545454546,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.12456864965572008,1,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1338299732918063105,d9feda8711f54694b341337dc64c86ccbfdc1e806f267ccd4064660056762927,1335507416331390976,0511c7cc808268a5bf20f33df0ce466dfc5384444859dbdd521530328eba3801,2020-12-14 01:48:15,"If anyone actually saw this incident in Olympia this weekend, please contact Washington Gun Law today at 425.765.0487 immediately.",0,0,0,actually saw incident olympia weekend contact washington gun law today 4257650487 immediately,"'WORK_OF_ART'), washington gun, ('this weekend', gun law, ('Washington Gun Law', today immediately, contact washington, washington gun law, [('Olympia', please contact, 'DATE'), olympia, incident olympia, anyone actually, olympia weekend, actually saw, law today, ('today', 'DATE')], 'GPE'), weekend please, saw incident",0.0,"[101, 2941, 2387, 5043, 17096, 5353, 3967, 2899, 3282, 2375, 2651, 23285, 2581, 26187, 2692, 18139, 2581, 3202, 102]",2020-12-14,"[""[('Olympia'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('this weekend'"", "" 'DATE')"", "" ('Washington Gun Law'"", "" 'WORK_OF_ART')"", "" ('today'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'washington gun law', 'law today', 'actually saw', 'please contact', 'today immediately', 'washington gun', 'olympia', 'gun law', 'incident olympia', 'anyone actually', 'weekend please', 'olympia weekend', 'contact washington', 'saw incident']",general,0.1,0.0,0,0.12428977272727272,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1335749559448973316,8720db4160a58c561accdef917d6ffd5d1d169af934469929aa832ea9191edc9,1335507416331390976,0511c7cc808268a5bf20f33df0ce466dfc5384444859dbdd521530328eba3801,2020-12-07 00:54:46,https://facebook.com/112779115408517/posts/4108502765836112/?d=n…. It was trump follower who was arrested. So much for “law and order”.,7,0,3,trump follower arrested law order,"[], trump follower, https trump, follower arrested, much law, arrest, arrested much, law order, trump",0.2,"[101, 8398, 22399, 4727, 2375, 2344, 102]",2020-12-07,"['[]', 'trump follower', 'trump', 'follower arrested', 'much law', 'arrest', 'arrested much', 'law order', 'https trump']",politics,0.1,0.013,0,0.7372159090909091,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.005415664042641564,0,0,1,11,0.6111111111111112
1335564467149524992,bebe29d1f4560646b841d528a904b5f520cae165f1065e35ea3049fcbcc6b697,1335507416331390976,0511c7cc808268a5bf20f33df0ce466dfc5384444859dbdd521530328eba3801,2020-12-06 12:39:17,Looks like the guy in the bright yellow was defending him self this video I hope help him,5,0,2,looks like guy bright yellow defending self video hope help,"guy bright, looks like, [], bright yellow, yellow defending, self video, hope help, video hope, looks, defending self, like guy",0.35,"[101, 3504, 2066, 3124, 4408, 3756, 6984, 2969, 2678, 3246, 2393, 102]",2020-12-06,"['[]', 'guy bright', 'looks like', 'bright yellow', 'yellow defending', 'self video', 'hope help', 'video hope', 'looks', 'defending self', 'like guy']",general,0.0,0.009,0,0.6725852272727273,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.00374547088622914,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1335598262099746818,6e3ff0dd445eae21e6345d6322a0e696e4606e2d46deeb12d63b5defc5bea26a,1335507416331390976,0511c7cc808268a5bf20f33df0ce466dfc5384444859dbdd521530328eba3801,2020-12-06 14:53:34,"Oly PD doing the typical, ignore attacks by the violent left and arrest their victims who defend themselves, routine.

I refuse to believe this is the will of the people. We need voter ID reform so elected officials have to care about the average citizen again",5,0,1,oly pd doing typical ignore attacks violent left arrest victims defend routine refuse believe people need voter id reform elected officials care average citizen,"vote, routine refuse, officials care, left arrest, believe people, citizen, victim, defend routine, attacks violent, victims defend, need voter, violent left, attack, oly, 'ORG')], refuse believe, arrest, voter reform, elected officials, ignore attacks, oly typical, [('Oly PD'",-0.2333333333333333,"[101, 19330, 2100, 22851, 2725, 5171, 8568, 4491, 6355, 2187, 6545, 5694, 6985, 9410, 10214, 2903, 2111, 2342, 14303, 8909, 5290, 2700, 4584, 2729, 2779, 6926, 102]",2020-12-06,"[""[('Oly PD'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'vote', 'routine refuse', 'officials care', 'left arrest', 'believe people', 'citizen', 'victim', 'defend routine', 'attacks violent', 'victims defend', 'need voter', 'violent left', 'attack', 'oly', 'refuse believe', 'arrest', 'voter reform', 'elected officials', 'ignore attacks', 'oly typical']",crime,0.2,0.007,0,0.6392045454545454,0.2,1,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.002885446876625299,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1337930542348718083,6c327fd5c5b4c83a9cf00ac74710c041de8b6020490379e1eefcb11d0ac499b1,1335507416331390976,0511c7cc808268a5bf20f33df0ce466dfc5384444859dbdd521530328eba3801,2020-12-13 01:21:13,There is no such thing as an Antifa militant! Do you actually know what Antifa means??? Idiot!,3,0,0,thing antifa militant actually know antifa means idiot,"antifa militant, 'NORP'), ('Antifa', idiot, antifa means, ('Idiot', thing antifa, militant actually, actually know, 'PERSON')], know antifa, means idiot, [('Antifa', there, antifa, 'ORG')",-0.3333333333333333,"[101, 2518, 3424, 7011, 16830, 2941, 2113, 3424, 7011, 2965, 10041, 102]",2020-12-13,"[""[('Antifa'"", "" 'NORP')"", "" ('Antifa'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Idiot'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'antifa militant', 'idiot', 'antifa means', 'thing antifa', 'militant actually', 'actually know', 'know antifa', 'means idiot', 'there', 'antifa']",general,0.8,0.003,0,0.5035511363636364,0.8,3,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0012152537202128743,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1336086725458726912,d6c3b412aadfd0a3841c7d3fb764b3facd85d9c4deea6d65fca8c5dd86a62d1b,1335507416331390976,0511c7cc808268a5bf20f33df0ce466dfc5384444859dbdd521530328eba3801,2020-12-07 23:14:33,Antifa would always show up to Patriots peaceful rallies to start trouble.,1,0,0,antifa patriots peaceful rallies start trouble,"patriots, peaceful, show patriots, peaceful rallies, would always, riot, rallies start, always show, patriots peaceful, start trouble, 'ORG'), 'ORG')], [('Antifa', antifa would, antifa, ('Patriots'",0.0249999999999999,"[101, 3424, 7011, 11579, 9379, 22867, 2707, 4390, 102]",2020-12-07,"[""[('Antifa'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Patriots'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'patriots', 'peaceful', 'show patriots', 'peaceful rallies', 'riot', 'rallies start', 'always show', 'patriots peaceful', 'start trouble', 'antifa would', 'antifa', 'would always']",protest,0.6000000000000001,0.001,0,0.30610795454545453,0.6000000000000001,2,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1337923429308100608,413d4ae5dff3251171721a8b321c5795d1e1cb68582017f9fc183f12fd805333,1335507416331390976,0511c7cc808268a5bf20f33df0ce466dfc5384444859dbdd521530328eba3801,2020-12-13 00:52:57,Just say trump supporter shot multiple times at anti trump supporters..and was hogtied and carried off. Hope he rots!!,1,0,0,just say trump supporter shot multiple times anti trump supportersand hogtied carried hope rots,"carried hope, [], hope rots, times anti, anti trump, trump supporter, say trump, shot multiple, trump supporters, hope, hogtied carried, just, supporters hogtied, supporter shot, multiple times, trump",0.0,"[101, 2074, 2360, 8398, 10129, 2915, 3674, 2335, 3424, 8398, 6793, 5685, 27589, 9515, 2094, 3344, 3246, 18672, 2015, 102]",2020-12-13,"['[]', 'carried hope', 'times anti', 'anti trump', 'hope rots', 'trump', 'trump supporter', 'say trump', 'shot multiple', 'trump supporters', 'hope', 'hogtied carried', 'just', 'multiple times', 'supporter shot', 'supporters hogtied']",politics,0.1,0.001,0,0.30610795454545453,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1337929123918979074,5c4e870d494a412b6d9912eb9e0a948a1da8c6142b021e69972254ebdd6d30fd,1335507416331390976,0511c7cc808268a5bf20f33df0ce466dfc5384444859dbdd521530328eba3801,2020-12-13 01:15:35,Stop those criminal white supremacy gangs. Those proud boys need to stop their violence.,1,0,0,stop criminal white supremacy gangs proud boys need stop violence,"need stop, white supremacy, supremacy gangs, [], gangs proud, proud boys, those, criminal, stop, stop criminal, criminal white, stop violence, violence, boys need",0.1333333333333333,"[101, 2644, 4735, 2317, 22006, 18542, 7098, 3337, 2342, 2644, 4808, 102]",2020-12-13,"['[]', 'need stop', 'white supremacy', 'supremacy gangs', 'gangs proud', 'proud boys', 'those', 'criminal', 'stop', 'stop criminal', 'criminal white', 'stop violence', 'violence', 'boys need']",crime,0.4,0.001,0,0.30610795454545453,0.4,2,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1337929493420380161,96e318428acb3f1c8651436485eb2df35b2d0bd62ce0a44c9ba86d83747101c2,1335507416331390976,0511c7cc808268a5bf20f33df0ce466dfc5384444859dbdd521530328eba3801,2020-12-13 01:17:03,lol you aren’t a reporter. You are a joke. The labels you have chosen show that you aren’t a real reporter.,1,0,0,lol arent reporter joke labels chosen arent real reporter,"lol reporter, reporter joke, show real, [], the, real reporter, joke labels, chosen show, you, labels chosen",0.5,"[101, 8840, 2140, 4995, 2102, 6398, 8257, 10873, 4217, 4995, 2102, 2613, 6398, 102]",2020-12-13,"['[]', 'lol reporter', 'reporter joke', 'the', 'show real', 'labels chosen', 'real reporter', 'joke labels', 'chosen show', 'you']",general,0.0,0.001,0,0.30610795454545453,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1346193314727518211,c94085391948815135d57ef09ccd6da02d5f0de0c73334a1e279866aaadbf35e,1346193314727518211,,2021-01-04 20:34:31,"NEW ALBUM OUT NOW
“Banana Peel On Capitol Hill”
LINK: https://dywanethomasjr.bandcamp.com/album/banana-peel-on-capitol-hill…

“Yesterday the world was buried alive”

Stanks ya for listening to whateva the fyuck I be doing... ",22,8,0,new album banana peel capitol hill link yesterday world buried alive stanks ya listening whateva fyuck doing,"'WORK_OF_ART'), alive stanks, album, yesterday world, link https, world buried, album banana, banana peel on capitol hill, whateva fyuck, listening whateva, [('Banana Peel On Capitol Hill', banana peel, stanks, stanks listening, peel capitol, new album, buried alive, new, ('Yesterday', hill link, https yesterday, 'DATE')], yesterday, capitol hill",0.1181818181818181,"[101, 2047, 2201, 15212, 14113, 9424, 2940, 4957, 7483, 2088, 3950, 4142, 9761, 5705, 8038, 5962, 2054, 13331, 1042, 10513, 3600, 2725, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Banana Peel On Capitol Hill'"", "" 'WORK_OF_ART')"", "" ('Yesterday'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'alive stanks', 'album', 'yesterday world', 'link https', 'world buried', 'album banana', 'banana peel on capitol hill', 'whateva fyuck', 'listening whateva', 'banana peel', 'stanks', 'stanks listening', 'peel capitol', 'new album', 'buried alive', 'new', 'hill link', 'https yesterday', 'yesterday', 'capitol hill']",general,0.2,0.046,1,0.8352272727272727,0.2,1,0,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,0,0.018992052691725145,0,0,1,1,0.05555555555555555
1337770272963825665,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,1337770272963825665,,2020-12-12 14:44:22,"Worth noting that because there’s a few separate rally points (I misspelled this as “tally” in my first tweet of this thread, sorry) some people are already marching east toward the Capitol / rally point on national mall from Freedom Plaza.",119,18,8,worth noting theres separate rally points misspelled tally tweet thread sorry people marching east capitol rally point national mall freedom plaza,"('Capitol', sorry people, thread sorry, misspelled tally, tweet thread, national mall, capitol rally, march, noting separate, worth, tally first, first tweet, people already, capitol, toward capitol, points misspelled, marching east, already marching, 'ORDINAL'), rally point, separate rally, mall freedom, ('Freedom Plaza', [('first', 'LOC')], 'ORG')",-0.0375,"[101, 4276, 9073, 2045, 2015, 3584, 8320, 2685, 3335, 11880, 3709, 19552, 1056, 28394, 2102, 11689, 3374, 2111, 10998, 2264, 9424, 8320, 2391, 2120, 6670, 4071, 8232, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('first'"", "" 'ORDINAL')"", "" ('Capitol'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Freedom Plaza'"", "" 'LOC')]"", 'sorry people', 'thread sorry', 'misspelled tally', 'tweet thread', 'national mall', 'capitol rally', 'march', 'noting separate', 'worth', 'tally first', 'first tweet', 'people already', 'capitol', 'toward capitol', 'points misspelled', 'marching east', 'already marching', 'rally point', 'separate rally', 'mall freedom']",protest,0.2,0.189,1,0.8941761363636364,0.2,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,0,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337769536674820101,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,1337770272963825665,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,2020-12-12 14:41:26,"The “Trump Unity Bridge” is parked right now and playing “God Bless America” at 11th and Penn, between Harry’s Bar and the Trump hotel.",98,31,13,trump unity bridge parked right playing god bless america 11th penn harrys bar trump hotel,"penn harry, trump unity bridge, 'WORK_OF_ART'), the, america penn, trump unity, bridge parked, harry bar, penn, playing god, ('Penn', ('Harry’s Bar', bless america, bar trump, right playing, 'ORG')], 'ORDINAL'), parked right, trump, trump hotel, bar, ('11th', 'PERSON'), god bless america, unity bridge, god bless, [('Trump Unity Bridge', ('Trump', harry",0.2857142857142857,"[101, 8398, 8499, 2958, 9083, 2157, 2652, 2643, 19994, 2637, 6252, 9502, 4302, 2015, 3347, 8398, 3309, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Trump Unity Bridge'"", "" 'WORK_OF_ART')"", "" ('11th'"", "" 'ORDINAL')"", "" ('Penn'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Harry’s Bar'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'penn harry', 'trump unity bridge', 'the', 'america penn', 'trump unity', 'bridge parked', 'harry bar', 'playing god', 'penn', 'bless america', 'bar trump', 'right playing', 'parked right', 'trump', 'trump hotel', 'bar', 'god bless america', 'unity bridge', 'god bless', 'harry']",politics,0.0,0.217,1,0.8977272727272727,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337770272963825665,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,1337770272963825665,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,2020-12-12 14:44:22,"Worth noting that because there’s a few separate rally points (I misspelled this as “tally” in my first tweet of this thread, sorry) some people are already marching east toward the Capitol / rally point on national mall from Freedom Plaza.",119,18,8,worth noting theres separate rally points misspelled tally tweet thread sorry people marching east capitol rally point national mall freedom plaza,"('Capitol', sorry people, thread sorry, misspelled tally, tweet thread, national mall, capitol rally, march, noting separate, worth, tally first, first tweet, people already, capitol, toward capitol, points misspelled, marching east, already marching, 'ORDINAL'), rally point, separate rally, mall freedom, ('Freedom Plaza', [('first', 'LOC')], 'ORG')",-0.0375,"[101, 4276, 9073, 2045, 2015, 3584, 8320, 2685, 3335, 11880, 3709, 19552, 1056, 28394, 2102, 11689, 3374, 2111, 10998, 2264, 9424, 8320, 2391, 2120, 6670, 4071, 8232, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('first'"", "" 'ORDINAL')"", "" ('Capitol'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Freedom Plaza'"", "" 'LOC')]"", 'sorry people', 'thread sorry', 'misspelled tally', 'tweet thread', 'national mall', 'capitol rally', 'march', 'noting separate', 'worth', 'tally first', 'first tweet', 'people already', 'capitol', 'toward capitol', 'points misspelled', 'marching east', 'already marching', 'rally point', 'separate rally', 'mall freedom']",protest,0.2,0.189,1,0.8941761363636364,0.2,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337775819918348288,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,1337770272963825665,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,2020-12-12 15:06:24,"Chants of “Fuck antifa!”

Livestreaming momentarily.",153,27,19,chants fuck antifa livestreaming momentarily,"livestreaming momentarily, [], chants fuck, fuck antifa, chants, fuck, antifa livestreaming, livestreaming",-0.5,"[101, 29534, 6616, 3424, 7011, 3268, 25379, 2075, 16032, 102]",2020-12-12,"['[]', 'livestreaming momentarily', 'chants fuck', 'fuck antifa', 'chants', 'fuck', 'antifa livestreaming', 'livestreaming']",general,0.25,0.272,1,0.9076704545454546,0.25,1,2,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337801700619522049,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,1337770272963825665,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,2020-12-12 16:49:15,I livestreamed for about an hour before connection died due to too many people.,97,7,10,livestreamed hour connection died people,"many people, hour connection, died due, connection died, [('about an hour', 'TIME')], due many, livestreamed hour",0.1875,"[101, 3268, 25379, 2098, 3178, 4434, 2351, 2111, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('about an hour'"", "" 'TIME')]"", 'many people', 'hour connection', 'died due', 'connection died', 'due many', 'livestreamed hour']",general,0.2,0.138,1,0.8892045454545454,0.2,1,2,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337812463132217346,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,1337770272963825665,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,2020-12-12 17:32:01,"Trump supporters wave as Marine One flies overhead, presumably carrying the president.",158,41,22,trump supporters wave marine flies overhead presumably carrying president,"overhead presumably, wave marine, trump, one flies, trump supporters, marine one, president, supporters wave, flies overhead, 'ORG')], presumably carrying, carrying president, [('Marine One'",0.0,"[101, 8398, 6793, 4400, 3884, 10029, 8964, 10712, 4755, 2343, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Marine One'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'overhead presumably', 'wave marine', 'one flies', 'trump supporters', 'marine one', 'president', 'supporters wave', 'flies overhead', 'presumably carrying', 'carrying president', 'trump']",politics,0.0,0.325,1,0.9190340909090909,0.0,0,2,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337813883407446021,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,1337770272963825665,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,2020-12-12 17:37:39,"Something challenging out here is they there’s multiple different rallies. Several blocks away from the March for Trump based at Freedom Plaza is the “Jericho March”, framed as a prayer rally for Trump. Apparently General Flynn just spoke here.",151,45,17,challenging theres multiple different rallies blocks away march trump based freedom plaza jericho march framed prayer rally trump apparently general flynn just spoke,"trump apparently, challenging multiple, different rallies, something, rallies several, march framed, several, march, trump based, flynn spoke, blocks away, apparently general flynn, ('Flynn', something challenging, prayer rally, apparently general, trump, ('Freedom Plaza', march trump, 'DATE'), several blocks, rally trump, general flynn, ('Trump', 'FAC'), [('March', 'PERSON')], 'ORG')",0.11,"[101, 10368, 2045, 2015, 3674, 2367, 22867, 5991, 2185, 2233, 8398, 2241, 4071, 8232, 17309, 2233, 10366, 7083, 8320, 8398, 4593, 2236, 13259, 2074, 3764, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('March'"", "" 'DATE')"", "" ('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Freedom Plaza'"", "" 'FAC')"", "" ('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Flynn'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'trump apparently', 'challenging multiple', 'different rallies', 'something', 'rallies several', 'march framed', 'several', 'march', 'trump based', 'flynn spoke', 'blocks away', 'apparently general flynn', 'something challenging', 'prayer rally', 'apparently general', 'trump', 'march trump', 'several blocks', 'rally trump', 'general flynn']",politics,0.1,0.32,1,0.9176136363636364,0.1,0,2,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337826194209828865,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,1337770272963825665,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,2020-12-12 18:26:34,"At the #JerichoMarch, Stop the Steal founder 
@ali
 lays out that their last hope after the electoral college is that a senator will join Rep. Mo Brooks in blocking Jan 6 certification of Biden win.

If none do, “we will burn the Republican Party down and make something new.”",225,137,46,jerichomarch stop steal founder ali lays hope electoral college senator join rep mo brooks blocking jan 6 certification biden win burn republican party make new,"make something, last hope, none burn, biden, lays last, electoral college, college senator, certification biden, march, #jerichomarch, hope electoral, ali lays, ('Steal', @ali, ('Jan 6', jan, something new, burn republican, stop, brooks blocking, 'ORG')], steal founder, founder ali, 'PERSON'), ('Biden', 'DATE'), ('Mo Brooks', ('the Republican Party', [('JerichoMarch', 'ORG')",0.1952020202020202,"[101, 17309, 7849, 2818, 2644, 8954, 3910, 4862, 19764, 3246, 6092, 2267, 5205, 3693, 16360, 9587, 8379, 10851, 5553, 1020, 10618, 7226, 2368, 2663, 6402, 3951, 2283, 2191, 2047, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('JerichoMarch'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Steal'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Mo Brooks'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Jan 6'"", "" 'DATE')"", "" ('Biden'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('the Republican Party'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'make something', 'last hope', 'none burn', 'biden', 'lays last', 'electoral college', 'college senator', 'certification biden', 'march', '#jerichomarch', 'hope electoral', 'ali lays', '@ali', 'jan', 'something new', 'burn republican', 'stop', 'brooks blocking', 'steal founder', 'founder ali']",politics,0.2,0.728,1,0.9602272727272727,0.2,1,2,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,1,1,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337827287161589761,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,1337770272963825665,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,2020-12-12 18:30:55,"Alex Jones also spoke, promising that “we will never recognize” Joe Biden.

Cheers erupted when he declared that “Joe Biden is a globalist, and Joe Biden will be removed one way or another.”",203,157,58,alex jones spoke promising recognize joe biden cheers erupted declared joe biden globalist joe biden removed way,"way another, 'CARDINAL')], biden, joe biden, jones also, alex jones, [('Alex Jones', jones, ('Joe Biden', also spoke, cheers erupted, alex, cheers, declared joe, 'PERSON'), removed one, one way, promising never, biden removed, recognize joe, biden globalist, spoke promising, never recognize, erupted declared, ('one'",0.2,"[101, 4074, 3557, 3764, 10015, 6807, 3533, 7226, 2368, 21250, 12591, 4161, 3533, 7226, 2368, 3795, 2923, 3533, 7226, 2368, 3718, 2126, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Alex Jones'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Joe Biden'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Joe Biden'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Joe Biden'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('one'"", "" 'CARDINAL')]"", 'way another', 'biden', 'joe biden', 'jones also', 'alex jones', 'jones', 'also spoke', 'cheers erupted', 'alex', 'cheers', 'declared joe', 'removed one', 'one way', 'promising never', 'biden removed', 'recognize joe', 'biden globalist', 'spoke promising', 'never recognize', 'erupted declared']",politics,0.1,0.79,1,0.9616477272727273,0.1,0,2,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337836729542336515,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,1337770272963825665,3519a0d92302124ced93df4fcb5fa8f6ba3cbb3f04656ff28a8cfbcf03a9d0b5,2020-12-12 19:08:26,General Flynn just spoke as well at Freedom Plaza. He leaves encouraging Trump supporters not to give up and instead “fight like a Flynn!”,146,58,53,general flynn just spoke freedom plaza leaves encouraging trump supporters instead fight like flynn,"encouraging trump, plaza leaves, trump supporters, fight like, well freedom, flynn spoke, ('Flynn', like flynn, spoke well, give instead, trump, flynn, 'PERSON'), ('Freedom Plaza', leaves encouraging, general flynn, instead fight, ('Trump', 'FAC'), freedom plaza, 'PERSON')], supporters give, [('Flynn'",0.0625,"[101, 2236, 13259, 2074, 3764, 4071, 8232, 3727, 11434, 8398, 6793, 2612, 2954, 2066, 13259, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Flynn'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Freedom Plaza'"", "" 'FAC')"", "" ('Trump'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Flynn'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'general flynn', 'instead fight', 'flynn', 'encouraging trump', 'leaves encouraging', 'give instead', 'plaza leaves', 'freedom plaza', 'trump supporters', 'fight like', 'well freedom', 'spoke well', 'supporters give', 'flynn spoke', 'like flynn', 'trump']",politics,0.25,0.426,1,0.9367897727272727,0.25,1,2,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: 'I won't vote next time': could Georgia Republicans' doubts cost them the runoffs? (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1346153540763459584,7b96efbe20fe7bbcbb0f19d574de98799a53cdbe068de3c5ae61fc65d2a5182f,1346153540763459584,,2021-01-04 17:56:29,Astonishing new evidence of a desperate President Donald Dickhead Trump caught on tape trying to steal the election exposes the depth of his corruption and makes his Republican Capitol Hill allies complicit in his bid to thwart the will of voters.,4,2,2,astonishing new evidence desperate president donald dickhead trump caught tape trying steal election exposes depth corruption makes republican capitol hill allies complicit bid thwart voters,"vote, 'NORP'), caught tape, desperate president, thwart voters, president donald dickhead trump, republican capitol hill, evidence desperate, republican capitol, donald dickhead trump, trying steal, astonishing new, astonishing, makes republican, complicit bid, [('Donald Dickhead Trump', election, ('Capitol Hill', 'ORG')], election exposes, new evidence, trump caught, donald dickhead, trump, 'PERSON'), ('Republican'",0.0121212121212121,"[101, 26137, 2047, 3350, 7143, 2343, 6221, 5980, 4974, 8398, 3236, 6823, 2667, 8954, 2602, 14451, 2015, 5995, 7897, 3084, 3951, 9424, 2940, 6956, 4012, 24759, 28775, 2102, 7226, 16215, 18367, 7206, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Donald Dickhead Trump'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Republican'"", "" 'NORP')"", "" ('Capitol Hill'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'vote', 'caught tape', 'desperate president', 'thwart voters', 'president donald dickhead trump', 'republican capitol hill', 'evidence desperate', 'republican capitol', 'donald dickhead trump', 'trying steal', 'astonishing new', 'astonishing', 'makes republican', 'complicit bid', 'election', 'election exposes', 'new evidence', 'trump caught', 'donald dickhead', 'trump']",politics,0.7000000000000001,0.014,1,0.7514204545454546,0.7000000000000001,3,0,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,0,0.0035204583416363735,0,0,0,3,0.16666666666666666
1346153544886358021,7b96efbe20fe7bbcbb0f19d574de98799a53cdbe068de3c5ae61fc65d2a5182f,1346153540763459584,7b96efbe20fe7bbcbb0f19d574de98799a53cdbe068de3c5ae61fc65d2a5182f,2021-01-04 17:56:30,"In a fresh abuse of power, Trump tried to bully a top Georgia GOP official into finding votes to overturn President-elect Joe Biden's win in the state. The staggering telephone call, audio of which was obtained by the Washington Post, amounted to the most serious threat yet.",0,0,1,fresh abuse power trump tried bully georgia gop official finding votes overturn presidentelect joe bidens win state staggering telephone audio obtained washington post amounted threat,"vote, the, biden, georgia gop, joe biden, bully top, win state, state staggering, official finding, call audio, washington post, obtained washington, threat yet, amounted serious, 'ORG')], threat, overturn joe, [('Trump', top georgia, (""Joe Biden's"", trump, fresh abuse, ('GOP', gop official, 'PERSON'), ('Georgia', ('the Washington Post', 'GPE'), 'ORG')",0.3533333333333334,"[101, 4840, 6905, 2373, 8398, 2699, 20716, 4108, 2175, 2361, 2880, 4531, 4494, 2058, 22299, 2343, 12260, 6593, 3533, 7226, 6132, 2663, 2110, 26233, 7026, 5746, 4663, 2899, 2695, 18779, 5081, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Georgia'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('GOP'"", "" 'ORG')"", ' (""Joe Biden\'s""', "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('the Washington Post'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'vote', 'the', 'biden', 'georgia gop', 'joe biden', 'bully top', 'win state', 'state staggering', 'official finding', 'call audio', 'washington post', 'obtained washington', 'threat yet', 'amounted serious', 'threat', 'overturn joe', 'top georgia', 'trump', 'fresh abuse', 'gop official']",politics,0.30000000000000004,0.002,1,0.4169034090909091,0.30000000000000004,1,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0035204583416363735,0,0,0,3,0.16666666666666666
1346154955846070272,eee75cbc14e727b5fe53cd38929a37ec4b7b6985143223d77effc829c35d6a3c,1346153540763459584,7b96efbe20fe7bbcbb0f19d574de98799a53cdbe068de3c5ae61fc65d2a5182f,2021-01-04 18:02:06,And UN is watching without any warning,1,0,0,watching warning,"watching without, and, 'ORG')], war, [('UN', without warning",0.0,"[101, 3666, 5432, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('UN'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'war', 'watching without', 'and', 'without warning']",international,0.2,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.2,1,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,3,0.16666666666666666
1346093123353649153,fce8c7adfde9516c9e8e327d449953b219c3d5feb8b9a252153ea0bc418c6ca1,1346093123353649153,,2021-01-04 13:56:24,"I drove by Capitol Hill this morning to see the construction underway for the Inauguration. The crowd will be very limited because of the deadly coronavirus pandemic. Sixteen days until 
@JoeBiden
 becomes President.",1800,141,83,drove capitol hill morning construction underway inauguration crowd limited deadly coronavirus pandemic sixteen days joebiden president,"limited deadly, sixteen, the, underway inauguration, biden, deadly coronavirus, construction underway, ('Inauguration', days joebiden, ('Sixteen days', drove capitol, morning see, see construction, president, [('Capitol Hill', sixteen days, crowd limited, ('this morning', crowd, inauguration crowd, joebiden becomes, pandemic sixteen, 'DATE')], capitol hill, @joebiden, 'TIME'), 'ORG')",-0.1464285714285714,"[101, 5225, 9424, 2940, 2851, 2810, 14128, 17331, 4306, 3132, 9252, 21887, 23350, 6090, 3207, 7712, 7032, 2420, 3533, 17062, 2368, 2343, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Capitol Hill'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('this morning'"", "" 'TIME')"", "" ('Inauguration'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Sixteen days'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'limited deadly', 'sixteen', 'the', 'underway inauguration', 'biden', 'deadly coronavirus', 'construction underway', 'days joebiden', 'drove capitol', 'morning see', 'see construction', 'president', 'sixteen days', 'crowd limited', 'crowd', 'inauguration crowd', 'joebiden becomes', 'pandemic sixteen', 'capitol hill', '@joebiden']",politics,0.2,1.0,1,0.9822443181818182,0.2,1,0,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,0,0.422597610278985,1,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346093420490723328,ded1d9e1cfb44fd89f6470448808c87333cddd093741f732790806d70956d98c,1346093123353649153,fce8c7adfde9516c9e8e327d449953b219c3d5feb8b9a252153ea0bc418c6ca1,2021-01-04 13:57:35,Surprised they don't have the BIG fences up around everything like they do Lafayette Park in anticipation of Jan 6th unrest.,2,0,0,surprised dont big fences like lafayette park anticipation jan 6th unrest,"[('Lafayette Park', like lafayette, surprised, everything like, jan unrest, lafayette park, 'FAC'), jan, around everything, fences around, 'DATE')], big fences, anticipation jan, ('Jan 6th', big, surprised big, park anticipation",0.05,"[101, 4527, 2123, 2102, 2502, 21549, 2066, 14425, 2380, 11162, 5553, 5351, 16591, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Lafayette Park'"", "" 'FAC')"", "" ('Jan 6th'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'like lafayette', 'surprised', 'everything like', 'jan unrest', 'lafayette park', 'jan', 'around everything', 'fences around', 'big fences', 'anticipation jan', 'big', 'surprised big', 'park anticipation']",general,0.1,0.002,1,0.4169034090909091,0.1,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0008101691468085828,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346093526174625792,275146888a0ffb24a315e4bf03f02c644bd422826931896d8443a1797e00b106,1346093123353649153,fce8c7adfde9516c9e8e327d449953b219c3d5feb8b9a252153ea0bc418c6ca1,2021-01-04 13:58:00,Let the count down begin,6,0,0,let count begin,"let, count begin, [], let count",-0.1555555555555555,"[101, 2292, 4175, 4088, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', 'let count', 'count begin', 'let']",general,0.0,0.006,1,0.6200284090909091,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0024305074404257485,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346095350050934784,c58255c425613a9d6fa9515992492d567005713ce3ccd7a7ae25ad19af07bef8,1346093123353649153,fce8c7adfde9516c9e8e327d449953b219c3d5feb8b9a252153ea0bc418c6ca1,2021-01-04 14:05:15,I hope there is a bullet proof glass surrounding the President and VP.  Trump is creating outrage that will lead to violence.,5,0,1,hope bullet proof glass surrounding president vp trump creating outrage lead violence,"lead violence, creating outrage, ('Trump', glass surrounding, trump creating, bullet proof, surrounding president, president, 'PERSON')], hope bullet, [('VP', proof glass, outrage lead, president trump, violence, 'ORG'), trump",0.0,"[101, 3246, 7960, 6947, 3221, 4193, 2343, 21210, 8398, 4526, 19006, 2599, 4808, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('VP'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Trump'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'lead violence', 'creating outrage', 'glass surrounding', 'trump creating', 'bullet proof', 'surrounding president', 'president', 'hope bullet', 'proof glass', 'outrage lead', 'president trump', 'violence', 'trump']",politics,0.2,0.007,1,0.6392045454545454,0.2,1,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.002885446876625299,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346093898041593856,317a76c31a2a73f954c690773dc6c2980e6f8d64fc44be2c5170d10978fc1b95,1346093123353649153,fce8c7adfde9516c9e8e327d449953b219c3d5feb8b9a252153ea0bc418c6ca1,2021-01-04 13:59:29,"We are watching. We can't wait
 ",3,0,0,watching wait,"watching wait, []",0.0,"[101, 3666, 3524, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', 'watching wait']",general,0.0,0.003,1,0.5035511363636364,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0012152537202128743,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346094233036460040,4dfa031b28faf866dd592dd1ba1137cf8e87b1235a9eb924db1c01000567e4f0,1346093123353649153,fce8c7adfde9516c9e8e327d449953b219c3d5feb8b9a252153ea0bc418c6ca1,2021-01-04 14:00:49,"Trump will tell the world that he had 100,000’s and Biden hardly any (fully ignoring Covid) and by that he ‘won’ the elections. Same claim that his rallies had a higher turn out equals winning.",2,0,0,trump tell world 100000s biden hardly fully ignoring covid won elections claim rallies higher turn equals winning,"ignoring covid, claim rallies, biden, world biden, covid, trump tell, ('100, fully ignoring, election, biden hardly, [('Trump', higher turn, trump, 'PERSON'), tell world, elections claim, ('Biden', equals winning, 000', ('Covid', turn equals, 'CARDINAL'), rallies higher, hardly fully, 'PERSON')], covid elections, same, 'ORG')",0.1145833333333333,"[101, 8398, 2425, 2088, 6694, 8889, 2015, 7226, 2368, 6684, 3929, 9217, 2522, 17258, 2180, 3864, 4366, 22867, 3020, 2735, 19635, 3045, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('100"", ""000'"", "" 'CARDINAL')"", "" ('Biden'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Covid'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'ignoring covid', 'claim rallies', 'biden', 'world biden', 'covid', 'trump tell', 'fully ignoring', 'election', 'biden hardly', 'higher turn', 'trump', 'same', 'tell world', 'elections claim', 'turn equals', 'rallies higher', 'hardly fully', 'covid elections', 'equals winning']",politics,0.1,0.002,1,0.4169034090909091,0.1,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0008101691468085828,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346095070253084673,454053982a9992e3c9bb14453ca9102461efbc4395f2216c6c26b62aacc7f078,1346093123353649153,fce8c7adfde9516c9e8e327d449953b219c3d5feb8b9a252153ea0bc418c6ca1,2021-01-04 14:04:08,Probably still be a larger crowd than the Giant Cheeto got...,2,0,0,probably larger crowd giant cheeto got,"crowd giant, giant cheeto, [], still larger, cheeto got, probably, probably still, crowd, larger crowd",0.0,"[101, 2763, 3469, 4306, 5016, 18178, 18903, 2288, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', 'crowd giant', 'giant cheeto', 'still larger', 'crowd', 'cheeto got', 'probably', 'probably still', 'larger crowd']",protest,0.0,0.002,1,0.4169034090909091,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0008101691468085828,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346108944725499904,28897ccace2ee481a93de526eb4b4e83f9b7fed2a7695ce965fa64c91813b0f7,1346093123353649153,fce8c7adfde9516c9e8e327d449953b219c3d5feb8b9a252153ea0bc418c6ca1,2021-01-04 14:59:16,"Biden does not have an issue with crowd size, like someone else! He is more concerned about citizens keeping safe, unlike someone else.... just saying ",2,0,0,biden does issue crowd size like concerned citizens keeping safe unlike just saying,"else concerned, unlike someone, else saying, biden, safe unlike, like someone, citizen, issue crowd, concerned citizens, citizens keeping, size like, crowd size, 'ORG')], [('Biden', keeping safe, crowd, someone else, biden issue",0.5,"[101, 7226, 2368, 2515, 3277, 4306, 2946, 2066, 4986, 4480, 4363, 3647, 4406, 2074, 3038, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Biden'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'else concerned', 'keeping safe', 'unlike someone', 'else saying', 'biden', 'safe unlike', 'citizen', 'issue crowd', 'concerned citizens', 'size like', 'crowd size', 'someone else', 'citizens keeping', 'crowd', 'like someone', 'biden issue']",politics,0.05,0.002,1,0.4169034090909091,0.05,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0008101691468085828,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346094500310118400,2ed32e6f832e050b035decb441fd8e707b1208b4845d24fd2fe0e2d43f286b11,1346093123353649153,fce8c7adfde9516c9e8e327d449953b219c3d5feb8b9a252153ea0bc418c6ca1,2021-01-04 14:01:52,Gotta see it! Thanks for sharing Wolf for the folks that can't attend.,1,0,0,gotta thanks sharing wolf folks attend,"[('Wolf', thanks, gotta, see thanks, wolf folks, wolf, thanks sharing, 'PERSON')], sharing wolf, got see, folks attend",0.2,"[101, 10657, 4283, 6631, 4702, 12455, 5463, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Wolf'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'thanks', 'gotta', 'see thanks', 'wolf folks', 'wolf', 'thanks sharing', 'sharing wolf', 'got see', 'folks attend']",general,0.05,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.05,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346096972453842944,38eba0a916bacf20c68cea615c90c99d254522a1bc0ce6f93f015414b6eacbdc,1346093123353649153,fce8c7adfde9516c9e8e327d449953b219c3d5feb8b9a252153ea0bc418c6ca1,2021-01-04 14:11:42,No the crowd will be limited because no one wants to see him. It's impossible for him to draw a crowd. And he will always be if he makes it an illegitimate President. Elected by fraudulent votes.,1,0,2,crowd limited wants impossible draw crowd makes illegitimate president elected fraudulent votes,"vote, [], wants see, elected fraudulent, limited one, draw crowd, illegitimate president, one wants, elected, impossible draw, president, makes illegitimate, always makes, crowd limited, crowd, crowd always, see impossible, and, president elected, fraudulent votes",-0.1793650793650793,"[101, 4306, 3132, 4122, 5263, 4009, 4306, 3084, 18102, 2343, 2700, 27105, 4494, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', 'vote', 'wants see', 'elected fraudulent', 'limited one', 'draw crowd', 'illegitimate president', 'one wants', 'elected', 'impossible draw', 'president', 'makes illegitimate', 'always makes', 'crowd limited', 'crowd', 'crowd always', 'see impossible', 'and', 'president elected', 'fraudulent votes']",politics,0.5,0.005,1,0.5930397727272727,0.5,2,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0021251325926119743,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346099754938339329,41520f978a2963d5ed4e4dbb46ac800950fca1327432c28f39d1180136a903c8,1346093123353649153,fce8c7adfde9516c9e8e327d449953b219c3d5feb8b9a252153ea0bc418c6ca1,2021-01-04 14:22:45,"@YoushayRizvi
 your homie",1,0,0,youshayrizvi homie,"@youshayrizvi, [], youshayrizvi homie",0.0,"[101, 2017, 7377, 12541, 10993, 5737, 7570, 9856, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', '@youshayrizvi', 'youshayrizvi homie']",general,0.0,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0004050845734042914,1,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346111763343765506,4ceff82f981bb2adcc9045e759996f03b2871269a7b740340ab53c746ec140fa,1346093123353649153,fce8c7adfde9516c9e8e327d449953b219c3d5feb8b9a252153ea0bc418c6ca1,2021-01-04 15:10:28,Yes. Was our longest walk. It is a large bldg,1,0,0,yes longest walk large bldg,"walk large, [], yes longest, yes, was, longest walk, large bldg",0.2142857142857142,"[101, 2748, 6493, 3328, 2312, 1038, 6392, 2290, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', 'walk large', 'yes longest', 'yes', 'was', 'longest walk', 'large bldg']",general,0.0,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346488949913636864,4d084278c5320693a10d2065d6b3982eac591bfefcd773befe776d82f6d3be9a,1346093123353649153,fce8c7adfde9516c9e8e327d449953b219c3d5feb8b9a252153ea0bc418c6ca1,2021-01-05 16:09:16,"Is their anyway to move up the Presidential inauguration? Trump is literally trying to kill our Democracy,  and the Republicans in Congress who know better are actually worse than he is. No one person can make a dent in this Democracy. Period!!!",1,0,0,presidential inauguration trump literally trying kill democracy republicans congress know better actually worse person make dent democracy period,"person make, 'NORP'), trying kill, better actually, one person, republicans congress, democracy, move presidential, dent democracy, democracy period, congress know, anyway move, actually worse, 'ORG')], democracy republicans, worse one, presidential inauguration, period, trump, trump literally, [('Republicans', congress, make dent, ('Congress'",-0.140625,"[101, 4883, 17331, 8398, 6719, 2667, 3102, 7072, 10643, 3519, 2113, 2488, 2941, 4788, 2711, 2191, 21418, 7072, 2558, 102]",2021-01-05,"[""[('Republicans'"", "" 'NORP')"", "" ('Congress'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'person make', 'trying kill', 'better actually', 'one person', 'republicans congress', 'democracy', 'move presidential', 'dent democracy', 'democracy period', 'congress know', 'anyway move', 'actually worse', 'democracy republicans', 'worse one', 'presidential inauguration', 'period', 'trump', 'trump literally', 'congress', 'make dent']",politics,0.45000000000000007,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.45000000000000007,1,1,activity_spike,"[](7), 'ORG')](4), 'PERSON')](4), trump(3), china(3)","Guardian correlation: All eyes on Georgia as vote for the Senate begins | First Thing (score: 3, strength: medium)",general,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346093647574360068,f11a3fc2d18cf826113fea49fa29437c8ae86c84947a8631f3e2decaf72a194d,1346093123353649153,fce8c7adfde9516c9e8e327d449953b219c3d5feb8b9a252153ea0bc418c6ca1,2021-01-04 13:58:29,Finally Trump will be able to claim a bigger crowd..,0,0,0,finally trump able claim bigger crowd,"claim bigger, finally trump, [], able claim, trump able, bigger crowd, crowd, trump",0.1666666666666666,"[101, 2633, 8398, 2583, 4366, 7046, 4306, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', 'claim bigger', 'finally trump', 'trump', 'trump able', 'bigger crowd', 'crowd', 'able claim']",politics,0.1,0.0,1,0.12428977272727272,0.1,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346093840621559808,df62e78f7589daf2d9b4281b1ebdb08d664d0213fb1449c1fd95c39da49fd3c1,1346093123353649153,fce8c7adfde9516c9e8e327d449953b219c3d5feb8b9a252153ea0bc418c6ca1,2021-01-04 13:59:15,Please let them lock down entry to the town... Or better yet... Do the inauguration online and make a huge party later...,0,0,0,let lock entry town better inauguration online make huge party later,"please, [], yet inauguration, party later, lock entry, huge party, inauguration online, town better, online make, better yet, entry town, please let, make huge, let lock",0.1861111111111111,"[101, 2292, 5843, 4443, 2237, 2488, 17331, 3784, 2191, 4121, 2283, 2101, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', 'yet inauguration', 'make huge', 'party later', 'lock entry', 'huge party', 'inauguration online', 'town better', 'online make', 'better yet', 'entry town', 'please let', 'please', 'let lock']",general,0.0,0.0,1,0.12428977272727272,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), trump(61), 'PERSON')(60)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
