id,speaker_nm,conversation_id,reply_to_id,reply_to_nm,timestamp,text,likes,shares,num_comments,cleaned_text,named_entities,sentiment,tokens,date,extracted_entities,content_category,enhanced_hate_score,virality_score,spike_day,engagement_rank,hate_intensity,hate_keywords_count,reply_chain_depth,spike_cause,spike_top_entities,spike_external_cause,contextual_relevance,is_reply,user_influence,mention_count,hashtag_count,url_count,conversation_size,conversation_centrality
1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,1339230232088367105,0,,2020-12-16 15:25:43,"BLM-antifa in Seattle have set up another autonomous zone at Cal Anderson Park in the Capital Hill neighborhood. This is the same area they made CHAZ during the summer months. Video by 
@choeshow
:",5200,2700,1400,blmantifa seattle set autonomous zone cal anderson park capital hill neighborhood area chaz summer months video choeshow,"set another, zone cal, area made, seattle, anderson park, 'ORG'), chaz, another autonomous, cal anderson park, made chaz, chaz summer, blm, neighborhood area, hill neighborhood, this, 'LOC'), [('BLM-antifa', 'DATE')], 'FAC'), ('Seattle', ('Capital Hill', capital hill, video, park capital, seattle set, video choeshow, ('the summer months', 'GPE'), months video, ('Cal Anderson Park'",0.2,"[101, 1038, 12624, 3775, 7011, 5862, 2275, 8392, 4224, 10250, 5143, 2380, 3007, 2940, 5101, 2181, 15775, 2480, 2621, 2706, 2678, 16480, 9953, 5004, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('BLM-antifa'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Seattle'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('Cal Anderson Park'"", "" 'FAC')"", "" ('Capital Hill'"", "" 'LOC')"", "" ('the summer months'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'set another', 'zone cal', 'area made', 'seattle', 'months video', 'anderson park', 'chaz', 'another autonomous', 'cal anderson park', 'made chaz', 'chaz summer', 'blm', 'neighborhood area', 'hill neighborhood', 'this', 'capital hill', 'video', 'park capital', 'seattle set', 'video choeshow']",social,0.2,1.0,0,0.9822443181818182,0.2,1,0,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,0,0.6725382210780655,1,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339230948488073219,Freakoutery,1339230232088367105,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 15:28:34,"At some point it seems as if we could just start tweeting out videos of landfills and Haitian ghettos and say ""another autonomous zone has erupted in ___"" and they'd be totally believable.",113,2,1,point just start tweeting videos landfills haitian ghettos say autonomous zone erupted theyd totally believable,"start tweeting, totally believable, videos landfills, haitian ghettos, seems could, could start, another autonomous, erupted totally, ___, ghettos say, landfills haitian, [('Haitian', say another, haitian, 'NORP')], zone erupted, tweeting videos, point seems, autonomous zone",0.45,"[101, 2391, 2074, 2707, 1056, 28394, 3436, 6876, 28382, 2015, 21404, 17276, 2015, 2360, 8392, 4224, 12591, 2027, 2094, 6135, 19337, 2666, 12423, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('Haitian'"", "" 'NORP')]"", 'start tweeting', 'seems could', 'could start', 'zone erupted', 'say another', 'tweeting videos', 'haitian', 'another autonomous', 'point seems', 'totally believable', 'erupted totally', '___', 'videos landfills', 'autonomous zone', 'ghettos say', 'landfills haitian', 'haitian ghettos']",general,0.2,0.121,0,0.8835227272727273,0.2,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.04915462882349645,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339451172659322882,DevinCow,1339230232088367105,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-17 06:03:40,"Hay 
@KathrynTewson
 they’re lying again",13,0,1,hay kathryntewson theyre lying,"@kathryntewson, hay kathryntewson, [], kathryntewson lying, hay",0.0,"[101, 10974, 20484, 2618, 9333, 2239, 2027, 2890, 4688, 102]",2020-12-17,"['[]', '@kathryntewson', 'hay kathryntewson', 'hay', 'kathryntewson lying']",general,0.2,0.015,1,0.7613636363636364,0.2,1,1,activity_spike,"[](10), 'PERSON')](5), trump(4), 'ORG')(3), 'FAC')(3)","Guardian correlation: How many times has Trump lost the election ahahahaha | First Dog on the Moon (score: 2, strength: medium)",general,1,0.006126123463859629,1,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339236439620349957,palindromemood,1339230232088367105,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 15:50:23,"This is what we have to look forward to in the Harris/Biden administration. By the time the sympathizers wake up, it’ll be too late.",87,5,2,look forward harrisbiden administration time sympathizers wake itll late,"time sympathizers, [('Biden', administration time, biden, wake late, look forward, this, 'PERSON')], forward administration, harris, war, sympathizers wake",-0.3,"[101, 2298, 2830, 5671, 17062, 2368, 3447, 2051, 25353, 8737, 25457, 16750, 5256, 2009, 3363, 2397, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('Biden'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'time sympathizers', 'administration time', 'harris', 'biden', 'wake late', 'this', 'forward administration', 'look forward', 'war', 'sympathizers wake']",international,0.2,0.106,0,0.8806818181818182,0.2,1,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.04326252595340024,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339231536642629632,kmcannistraci,1339230232088367105,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 15:30:54,1 time my kid put a note on the door”don’t come in”. I took the door off for a year. That what you do when children throw tantrums. Also you would think with all those collective people together they could come up with a system to clean that place up. Come on man!,74,3,10,1 time kid note doordont come took door year children throw tantrums think collective people come clean place come man,"collective people, come man, come, clean place, children throw, place come, year children, 'CARDINAL'), also, time kid, system clean, note door, that, door year, took door, people together, ('a year', come system, throw tantrums, kid put, put note, would think, 'DATE')], [('1'",0.4583333333333333,"[101, 1015, 2051, 4845, 3602, 2341, 5280, 2102, 2272, 2165, 2341, 2095, 2336, 5466, 9092, 24456, 2015, 2228, 7268, 2111, 2272, 4550, 2173, 2272, 2158, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('1'"", "" 'CARDINAL')"", "" ('a year'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'collective people', 'come man', 'come', 'clean place', 'children throw', 'place come', 'year children', 'also', 'time kid', 'system clean', 'note door', 'that', 'door year', 'took door', 'people together', 'come system', 'throw tantrums', 'kid put', 'put note', 'would think']",general,0.15000000000000002,0.103,0,0.8792613636363636,0.15000000000000002,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0423565705567675,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339231959927631873,skol_brian,1339230232088367105,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 15:32:35,Andy cuts the video and calls it a CHAZ when it's a homeless encampment.  Not surprising. Gotta get those Ngo Simps fird up right?,50,1,34,andy cuts video calls chaz homeless encampment surprising gotta ngo simps fird right,"surprising got, get ngo, gotta, andy, simps, homeless encampment, ('Ngo Simps', cuts video, andy cuts, got get, 'GPE')], ngo simps, calls chaz, fird right, simps fird, not, encampment surprising, [('Andy', chaz homeless, 'PERSON'), video calls",-0.0321428571428571,"[101, 5557, 7659, 2678, 4455, 15775, 2480, 11573, 4372, 26468, 3672, 11341, 10657, 17895, 21934, 4523, 21554, 2094, 2157, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('Andy'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Ngo Simps'"", "" 'GPE')]"", 'encampment surprising', 'surprising got', 'simps', 'cuts video', 'simps fird', 'homeless encampment', 'ngo simps', 'chaz homeless', 'calls chaz', 'fird right', 'got get', 'get ngo', 'gotta', 'not', 'andy cuts', 'andy', 'video calls']",general,0.1,0.121,0,0.8835227272727273,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.05075506900634902,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339234000162844674,St3veOlson,1339230232088367105,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 15:40:42,"I totally support this. As long as we get to build an additional wall around them and never let them come out. Once their supplies diminish, it would only be a matter of time before the problem would resolve itself.",14,0,1,totally support long build additional wall let come supplies diminish matter time problem resolve,"diminish would, around never, support long, build additional, matter time, problem would, additional wall, come supplies, would resolve, wall around, [], never let, long get, supplies diminish, would matter, time problem, get build, let come, once, totally support",-0.0166666666666666,"[101, 6135, 2490, 2146, 3857, 3176, 2813, 2292, 2272, 6067, 11737, 5498, 4095, 3043, 2051, 3291, 10663, 102]",2020-12-16,"['[]', 'diminish would', 'around never', 'support long', 'build additional', 'matter time', 'problem would', 'additional wall', 'come supplies', 'would resolve', 'wall around', 'never let', 'long get', 'supplies diminish', 'would matter', 'time problem', 'get build', 'let come', 'once', 'totally support']",general,0.30000000000000004,0.016,0,0.7649147727272727,0.30000000000000004,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.006531208037263921,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339313377177460743,ShraderKs,1339230232088367105,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 20:56:07,Wait antifa is a myth! BLM is a multi-billion dollar organization they wouldn't live like this!! Would they? This is what the left has given birth too. How in the world did 81 million people vote for this?,10,1,8,wait antifa myth blm multibillion dollar organization wouldnt live like left given birth world did 81 million people vote,"[('BLM', ('multi-billion dollar', world million, would live, people vote, 'MONEY'), 'CARDINAL')], myth blm, 'ORG'), would left, like would, left given, live like, blm, antifa myth, million people, birth world, blm dollar, this, wait antifa, wait, vote, given birth, would, ('81 million', organization would",0.1065340909090909,"[101, 3524, 3424, 7011, 10661, 1038, 13728, 4800, 24457, 3258, 7922, 3029, 2876, 2102, 2444, 2066, 2187, 2445, 4182, 2088, 2106, 6282, 2454, 2111, 3789, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('BLM'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('multi-billion dollar'"", "" 'MONEY')"", "" ('81 million'"", "" 'CARDINAL')]"", 'world million', 'would live', 'people vote', 'myth blm', 'would left', 'like would', 'left given', 'live like', 'blm', 'organization would', 'antifa myth', 'million people', 'birth world', 'blm dollar', 'this', 'wait antifa', 'wait', 'vote', 'given birth', 'would']",social,0.35,0.029,0,0.8096590909090909,0.35,1,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.01219106182047749,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339231336867966980,wilconorth_j,1339230232088367105,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 15:30:07,It’s really wonderful what they’ve been able to build,9,0,1,really wonderful theyve able build,"wonderful able, really wonderful, able build, []",0.75,"[101, 2428, 6919, 2027, 3726, 2583, 3857, 102]",2020-12-16,"['[]', 'wonderful able', 'able build', 'really wonderful']",general,0.1,0.011,0,0.7088068181818182,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.004505785170242464,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339342589951176718,Designsage,1339230232088367105,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 22:52:11,"Wow, Seattle is starting to look like a third world country. WOW.",5,1,1,wow seattle starting look like world country wow,"seattle starting, world country, country wow, starting look, look like, ('WOW', like third, wow seattle, wow, [('Seattle', 'GPE'), third world, 'ORG')], seattle",0.05,"[101, 10166, 5862, 3225, 2298, 2066, 2088, 2406, 10166, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('Seattle'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('WOW'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'world country', 'seattle', 'country wow', 'starting look', 'look like', 'like third', 'wow seattle', 'third world', 'wow', 'seattle starting']",general,0.0,0.01,0,0.6910511363636364,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0041454708862291405,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339345626119671809,OlCurt66,1339230232088367105,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 23:04:15,"I’ve said it before and will again. I have no more sympathy for the folks living there. If they won’t band together to stop this, so be it.",7,0,3,ive said sympathy folks living wont band stop,"sympathy folks, [], said sympathy, band together, folks living, together stop, living band",-0.25,"[101, 4921, 2063, 2056, 11883, 12455, 2542, 2180, 2102, 2316, 2644, 102]",2020-12-16,"['[]', 'sympathy folks', 'band together', 'living band', 'folks living', 'together stop', 'said sympathy']",general,0.0,0.013,0,0.7372159090909091,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.005415664042641564,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339232994905743360,EdwinHoward1144,1339230232088367105,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 15:36:42,"Keep the faith, Trump’s hellfire is about to rain down on the anarcho-communists and the deep state.",4,1,2,faith trumps hellfire rain anarchocommunists deep state,"trump hellfire, rain deep, faith trump, [('Trump', trump, deep state, hellfire rain, keep, 'ORG')], keep faith",-0.0777777777777777,"[101, 4752, 8398, 2015, 3109, 10273, 4542, 9617, 11140, 24163, 7382, 19496, 12837, 2784, 2110, 102]",2020-12-16,"[""[('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'trump hellfire', 'rain deep', 'trump', 'deep state', 'hellfire rain', 'keep faith', 'keep', 'faith trump']",politics,0.0,0.011,0,0.7088068181818182,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.00460041032242869,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1337813537482223618,thehill,1337813537482223618,0,,2020-12-12 17:36:17,"WATCH: Trump supporters gather in Washington, D.C. on Saturday.",589,302,441,watch trump supporters gather washington dc saturday,"saturday, washington saturday, gather washington, supporters gather, ('D.C.', trump, 'GPE'), watch, d.c., trump supporters, [('Washington', 'DATE')], washington, ('Saturday', watch trump",0.0,"[101, 3422, 8398, 6793, 8587, 2899, 5887, 5095, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Washington'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('D.C.'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('Saturday'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'saturday', 'washington saturday', 'gather washington', 'supporters gather', 'trump', 'watch', 'd.c.', 'trump supporters', 'watch trump', 'washington']",politics,0.0,1.0,1,0.9822443181818182,0.0,0,0,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,0,0.5951184406178321,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337814925301919744,wireframejames,1337813537482223618,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:41:48,Imagine if women turned out in support of Trump? It might look like this.,30,6,0,imagine women turned support trump look like,"imagine women, support trump, turned support, imagine, [('Trump', women turned, trump, might look, trump might, 'ORG')], look like",0.0,"[101, 5674, 2308, 2357, 2490, 8398, 2298, 2066, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'imagine women', 'support trump', 'turned support', 'women turned', 'trump', 'might look', 'trump might', 'look like', 'imagine']",politics,0.0,0.048,1,0.8387784090909091,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.019712681259751792,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337813689378861056,chin_dogg,1337813537482223618,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:36:53,Is this Egypt? Cause that looks like a river of denial,48,0,6,egypt cause looks like river denial,"river denial, cause looks, egypt, 'GPE')], looks like, [('Egypt', cause, egypt cause, like river",0.0,"[101, 5279, 3426, 3504, 2066, 2314, 14920, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Egypt'"", "" 'GPE')]"", 'river denial', 'cause looks', 'egypt', 'looks like', 'cause', 'egypt cause', 'like river']",general,0.0,0.06,1,0.859375,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.024604203581029035,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337818431907880961,JGaffneyUSN,1337813537482223618,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:55:44,How did they scrape up the gas money?,25,1,0,did scrape gas money,"scrape gas, [], how, gas money",0.0,"[101, 2106, 26988, 3806, 2769, 102]",2020-12-12,"['[]', 'scrape gas', 'how', 'gas money']",general,0.0,0.028,1,0.8068181818181818,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.011387138344711127,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337813722144837632,ElyseBurden,1337813537482223618,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:37:01,Who cares what they do,26,0,1,cares,"who, []",0.0,"[101, 14977, 102]",2020-12-12,"['[]', 'who']",general,0.0,0.028,1,0.8068181818181818,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.011392222918115417,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337815027437473794,BeingJWood,1337813537482223618,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:42:12,Maybe more of them should have voted in the election. It’s tough to carry a candidate with approval in the low 40’s over the finish line.,12,1,2,maybe voted election tough carry candidate approval low 40s finish line,"voted election, maybe voted, maybe, finish line, candidate approval, low finish, [('40', tough carry, carry candidate, approval low, election tough, election, 'CARDINAL')], candidate, vote",0.037037037037037,"[101, 2672, 5444, 2602, 7823, 4287, 4018, 6226, 2659, 2871, 2015, 3926, 2240, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('40'"", "" 'CARDINAL')]"", 'voted election', 'maybe voted', 'finish line', 'candidate approval', 'low finish', 'tough carry', 'carry candidate', 'approval low', 'election tough', 'election', 'maybe', 'candidate', 'vote']",politics,0.0,0.019,1,0.7819602272727273,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.00784108690966302,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337814119072886784,ezautoleasesale,1337813537482223618,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:38:36,"If Trump was the patriot he claims to be, he would quash this foolishness, admit he has lost fair and square, concede the election and tell his sycophants to go home.   Election is over, but oh now....he cant do that.",12,0,5,trump patriot claims quash foolishness admit lost fair square concede election tell sycophants home election oh nowhe,"concede election, quash foolishness, election, square concede, election tell, foolishness admit, lost fair, admit lost, 'PERSON')], riot, trump patriot, sycophants home, fair square, patriot claims, home election, trump, election cant, if trump, tell sycophants, [('Trump', would quash, claims would",0.7,"[101, 8398, 16419, 4447, 24209, 11823, 13219, 2791, 6449, 2439, 4189, 2675, 9530, 22119, 2602, 2425, 25353, 3597, 21890, 7666, 2188, 2602, 2821, 2085, 5369, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Trump'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'concede election', 'election', 'quash foolishness', 'square concede', 'election tell', 'foolishness admit', 'lost fair', 'admit lost', 'riot', 'trump patriot', 'sycophants home', 'fair square', 'patriot claims', 'home election', 'trump', 'election cant', 'if trump', 'tell sycophants', 'would quash', 'claims would']",politics,0.0,0.022,1,0.7876420454545454,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.005171304075679287,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337814154921431040,PaulStaebell,1337813537482223618,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:38:44,WOW That crowd is almost as big as his Inaugeration,12,0,0,wow crowd big inaugeration,"crowd almost, 'ORG'), that, 'FAC')], inaugeration, big inaugeration, almost big, wow crowd, crowd, [('WOW', ('Inaugeration'",0.05,"[101, 10166, 4306, 2502, 27118, 22890, 8156, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('WOW'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Inaugeration'"", "" 'FAC')]"", 'crowd almost', 'that', 'inaugeration', 'big inaugeration', 'almost big', 'wow crowd', 'crowd']",protest,0.0,0.012,1,0.7237215909090909,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.004861014880851497,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337816652361199618,DrJones03046447,1337813537482223618,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:48:40,How come he had 71 million votes and can only get a crowd of around a thousand like this in Washington? Something fishy - this shows the true cult of Trump ... which really is pretty small!,8,2,0,come 71 million votes crowd thousand like washington fishy shows true cult trump really pretty small,"something fishy, trump really, votes get, [('71 million', get crowd, true cult, 'CARDINAL'), thousand like, shows true, million votes, ('Washington', washington something, washington, crowd around, something, trump, like washington, cult trump, fishy shows, 'ORG')], pretty small, vote, ('around a thousand', how, around thousand, 'GPE'), ('Trump'",0.071875,"[101, 2272, 6390, 2454, 4494, 4306, 4595, 2066, 2899, 3869, 2100, 3065, 2995, 8754, 8398, 2428, 3492, 2235, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('71 million'"", "" 'CARDINAL')"", "" ('around a thousand'"", "" 'CARDINAL')"", "" ('Washington'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'something fishy', 'trump really', 'votes get', 'get crowd', 'true cult', 'thousand like', 'shows true', 'million votes', 'washington something', 'washington', 'crowd around', 'something', 'trump', 'like washington', 'cult trump', 'fishy shows', 'pretty small', 'vote', 'how', 'around thousand']",politics,0.15000000000000002,0.014,1,0.7514204545454546,0.15000000000000002,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.005760724606442016,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337813634639155201,GodSavesToday,1337813537482223618,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:36:40,"Am I the only one hoping to watch the Secret Service carry that Orange Clown out on January 20th? 
#ITSOVER",10,0,2,hoping watch secret service carry orange clown january 20th itsover,"orange clown, carry orange, ('Orange Clown', hoping watch, one hoping, 'DATE'), 'ORG'), [('the Secret Service', 'PERSON')], january itsover, ('ITSOVER', ('January 20th', 'LOC'), watch secret, clown january, secret service, january, service carry, #itsover",-0.1333333333333333,"[101, 5327, 3422, 3595, 2326, 4287, 4589, 15912, 2254, 3983, 2049, 7840, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('the Secret Service'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Orange Clown'"", "" 'LOC')"", "" ('January 20th'"", "" 'DATE')"", "" ('ITSOVER'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'watch secret', 'clown january', 'secret service', 'orange clown', 'january', 'one hoping', 'carry orange', 'january itsover', 'service carry', 'hoping watch', '#itsover']",general,0.0,0.014,1,0.7514204545454546,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.005770893753250598,0,1,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1345179662880624641,choeshow,1345179662880624641,0,,2021-01-02 01:26:38,"NEW YEAR’S EVE DESTRUCTION: Capitol Hill biz owners and neighbors are fed up with black bloc marchers wrecking the city. The owner of Cafe Argento says they’re being targeted for just trying to improve the neighborhood.

Story 6pm 
@komonews
 

#seattle #CalAndersonPark",271,112,56,new years eve destruction capitol hill biz owners neighbors fed black bloc marchers wrecking city owner cafe argento says theyre targeted just trying improve neighborhood story 6pm komonews seattle calandersonpark,"bloc marchers, #seattle, trying improve, city owner, biz owners, hill biz, @komonews, calandersonpark, says targeted, 'CARDINAL')], #calandersonpark, new year, eve destruction, 'ORG'), neighbors fed, 'TIME'), argento says, story komonews, owners neighbors, story, marchers wrecking, wrecking city, improve neighborhood, ('Cafe Argento', ('#', ('6pm', [('Capitol Hill'",-0.0151515151515151,"[101, 2047, 2086, 6574, 6215, 9424, 2940, 12170, 2480, 5608, 10638, 7349, 2304, 15984, 28791, 2869, 12006, 2075, 2103, 3954, 7668, 23157, 2080, 2758, 2027, 2890, 9416, 2074, 2667, 5335, 5101, 2466, 1020, 9737, 12849, 8202, 7974, 2015, 5862, 10250, 12243, 3385, 14432, 102]",2021-01-02,"[""[('Capitol Hill'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Cafe Argento'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('6pm'"", "" 'TIME')"", "" ('#'"", "" 'CARDINAL')]"", 'bloc marchers', '#seattle', 'trying improve', 'city owner', 'biz owners', 'hill biz', '@komonews', 'calandersonpark', 'says targeted', '#calandersonpark', 'new year', 'eve destruction', 'neighbors fed', 'argento says', 'story komonews', 'owners neighbors', 'story', 'marchers wrecking', 'wrecking city', 'improve neighborhood']",protest,0.0,0.719,0,0.9573863636363636,0.0,0,0,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,0,0.2990619530060084,1,2,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345186143931797505,flottum76lynn,1345179662880624641,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 01:52:23,"Well, when you catch and release these idiots night after night, this is what happens. Maybe try voting next time for a candidate without a “D” next to their name. This will never end.",68,3,4,catch release idiots night night happens maybe try voting time candidate d end,"night night, next time, candidate without, try voting, name never, maybe try, catch release, idiots night, candidate, night happens, well catch, without next, 'TIME')], release idiots, this, well, next name, never end, [('night', time candidate, voting next, happens maybe",-0.2666666666666666,"[101, 4608, 2713, 28781, 2305, 2305, 6433, 2672, 3046, 6830, 2051, 4018, 1040, 2203, 102]",2021-01-02,"[""[('night'"", "" 'TIME')]"", 'night night', 'next time', 'candidate without', 'happens maybe', 'try voting', 'name never', 'maybe try', 'catch release', 'idiots night', 'candidate', 'night happens', 'well catch', 'without next', 'release idiots', 'this', 'well', 'next name', 'never end', 'time candidate', 'voting next']",politics,0.30000000000000004,0.085,0,0.8735795454545454,0.30000000000000004,1,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0347659190587187,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345182726584844290,integrityiseve1,1345179662880624641,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 01:38:48,Why bother trying to improve the neighborhood. Open in a place that will appreciate your efforts,43,0,1,bother trying improve neighborhood open place appreciate efforts,"improve neighborhood, bother trying, [], open, trying improve, neighborhood open, place appreciate, appreciate efforts, open place, why",0.0,"[101, 8572, 2667, 5335, 5101, 2330, 2173, 9120, 4073, 102]",2021-01-02,"['[]', 'improve neighborhood', 'bother trying', 'open', 'trying improve', 'neighborhood open', 'place appreciate', 'appreciate efforts', 'open place', 'why']",general,0.0,0.045,0,0.8338068181818182,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.018278660665988367,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345180938653732870,ScreamingInSea,1345179662880624641,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 01:31:42,"Smashing up another LGBT POC owned small business. 

It feels like the gay bars/clubs/even coffee shops are targeted more then anyone else. 
Look what happened to QueerBar & Neighbors.",14,0,2,smashing lgbt poc owned small business feels like gay barsclubseven coffee shops targeted look happened queerbar neighbors,"smashing, lgbt, like gay, owned small, anyone else, else look, lgbt poc, poc owned, [('LGBT POC', 'ORG'), targeted anyone, look happened, feels like, another lgbt, look, gay coffee, shops targeted, ('QueerBar & Neighbors', neighbors, 'ORG')], happened queerbar, queerbar neighbors, queerbar, smashing another",0.2222222222222222,"[101, 21105, 12010, 13433, 2278, 3079, 2235, 2449, 5683, 2066, 5637, 6963, 20464, 12083, 3366, 8159, 4157, 7340, 9416, 2298, 3047, 19483, 8237, 10638, 102]",2021-01-02,"[""[('LGBT POC'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('QueerBar & Neighbors'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'smashing', 'lgbt', 'like gay', 'owned small', 'anyone else', 'else look', 'lgbt poc', 'poc owned', 'targeted anyone', 'look happened', 'feels like', 'another lgbt', 'look', 'gay coffee', 'shops targeted', 'neighbors', 'happened queerbar', 'queerbar neighbors', 'queerbar', 'smashing another']",general,0.1,0.018,0,0.7762784090909091,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0073912320468677625,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345181731200983041,RBtw33ts,1345179662880624641,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 01:34:51,It is never ok to destroy someone else’s property.  If you do not like a business don’t go there.,9,0,0,ok destroy elses property like business dont,"[], property like, destroy someone, never destroy, someone else, else property, like business",-0.225,"[101, 7929, 6033, 2842, 2015, 3200, 2066, 2449, 2123, 2102, 102]",2021-01-02,"['[]', 'property like', 'destroy someone', 'never destroy', 'someone else', 'else property', 'like business']",general,0.1,0.009,0,0.6725852272727273,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.003645761160638622,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345195592004194305,Chrismorama,1345179662880624641,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 02:29:56,The coming backlash will be severe.,9,0,1,coming backlash severe,"the, backlash severe, coming backlash, []",0.0,"[101, 2746, 25748, 5729, 102]",2021-01-02,"['[]', 'backlash severe', 'coming backlash', 'the']",general,0.0,0.011,0,0.7088068181818182,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.004505785170242464,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345235076913782784,cwgrl42632,1345179662880624641,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 05:06:50,You should ask all these fed up residents and business owners who they have been voting for over the last 10-15 years....,9,0,1,ask fed residents business owners voting 1015 years,"[('the last', residents business, fed residents, you, voting last, 'DATE')], last years, business owners, ('10-15 years', owners voting, 'DATE'), ask fed",0.0,"[101, 3198, 7349, 3901, 2449, 5608, 6830, 7886, 2629, 2086, 102]",2021-01-02,"[""[('the last'"", "" 'DATE')"", "" ('10-15 years'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'residents business', 'fed residents', 'you', 'voting last', 'business owners', 'owners voting', 'last years', 'ask fed']",general,0.1,0.011,0,0.7088068181818182,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.004505785170242464,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345211225475571713,LoneStarWhiz,1345179662880624641,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 03:32:03,You voted them into power.,4,0,0,voted power,"you, [], vote, voted power",0.0,"[101, 5444, 2373, 102]",2021-01-02,"['[]', 'you', 'vote', 'voted power']",politics,0.0,0.004,0,0.5568181818181818,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0016203382936171656,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345185595891404800,mchellshit,1345179662880624641,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 01:50:13,"Congrats, Jeff Bezos is now that much richer.",3,0,0,congrats jeff bezos richer,"congrats, bezos much, jeff bezos, much richer, [('Congrats', ('Jeff Bezos', 'PERSON')], 'NORP'), congrats jeff",0.2,"[101, 26478, 8609, 2015, 5076, 2022, 28370, 26108, 102]",2021-01-02,"[""[('Congrats'"", "" 'NORP')"", "" ('Jeff Bezos'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'congrats', 'bezos much', 'jeff bezos', 'much richer', 'congrats jeff']",general,0.2,0.003,0,0.5035511363636364,0.2,1,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0012152537202128743,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345401572898050050,lynstar_16,1345179662880624641,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 16:08:25,These people are so destructive. If they could only put their energy into something positive and constructive.,3,0,0,people destructive energy positive constructive,"[], put energy, these, energy something, could put, destructive could, something positive, positive constructive, people destructive",-0.1242424242424242,"[101, 2111, 15615, 2943, 3893, 26157, 102]",2021-01-02,"['[]', 'put energy', 'these', 'energy something', 'could put', 'destructive could', 'something positive', 'positive constructive', 'people destructive']",general,0.2,0.003,0,0.5035511363636364,0.2,1,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0012152537202128743,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345182925621317639,TheDigriz,1345179662880624641,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 01:39:36,Time for him to buy a gun.,2,0,0,time buy gun,"time buy, time, [], buy gun",0.0,"[101, 2051, 4965, 3282, 102]",2021-01-02,"['[]', 'time buy', 'time', 'buy gun']",general,0.0,0.002,0,0.4169034090909091,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0008101691468085828,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1345201642224943105,MikeHalston2,1345179662880624641,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 02:53:58,"Too bad.
Why don't they ask their stupid fellow citizens to stop voting for far-left appeasers of this cancerous ideology?
And if their fellow citizens aren't interested in safety, amenity, economic prosperity etc. then get the hell out of these rotten far-left hellholes!",1,0,0,bad dont ask stupid fellow citizens stop voting farleft appeasers cancerous ideology fellow citizens arent interested safety amenity economic prosperity hell rotten farleft hellholes,"stupid fellow, citizens stop, citizens interested, bad ask, voting appeasers, ask stupid, cancerous ideology, get hell, rotten hellholes, prosperity etc, fellow citizens, why, [], hell rotten, amenity economic, etc get, stop voting, ideology fellow, too, safety amenity, appeasers cancerous",-0.2499999999999999,"[101, 2919, 2123, 2102, 3198, 5236, 3507, 4480, 2644, 6830, 2521, 2571, 6199, 10439, 19500, 2869, 4456, 3560, 13165, 3507, 4480, 4995, 2102, 4699, 3808, 2572, 20693, 3171, 14165, 3109, 11083, 2521, 2571, 6199, 3109, 19990, 102]",2021-01-02,"['[]', 'stupid fellow', 'citizens stop', 'citizens interested', 'bad ask', 'voting appeasers', 'ask stupid', 'cancerous ideology', 'get hell', 'rotten hellholes', 'prosperity etc', 'fellow citizens', 'why', 'hell rotten', 'amenity economic', 'etc get', 'stop voting', 'ideology fellow', 'appeasers cancerous', 'too', 'safety amenity']",immigration,0.45,0.001,0,0.30610795454545453,0.45,2,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,12,0.6666666666666666
1339624669750681600,MayorBowser,1339624669750681600,0,,2020-12-17 17:33:04,"Today, our frontline workers received their first dose of the COVID-19 vaccine at Kaiser Permanente in Capitol Hill. These vaccinations will save lives & protect our first responders, their patients, and their families. 

There is reason to have hope. 

#GetVaccinatedDC, #DCHOPE",154,38,10,today frontline workers received dose covid19 vaccine kaiser permanente capitol hill vaccinations save lives protect responders patients families reason hope getvaccinateddc dchope,"permanente capitol, hill vaccinations, vaccine kaiser, ('Kaiser Permanente', today, kaiser permanente, patients families, dose vaccine, protect first, dchope, 'ORG'), reason hope, ('first', 'PERSON')], first responders, ('DCHOPE', ('COVID-19', save lives, getvaccinateddc, today frontline, workers received, first dose, 'FAC'), families reason, lives protect, #getvaccinateddc, frontline workers, ('Capitol Hill', [('Today', 'ORDINAL'), 'DATE')",0.25,"[101, 2651, 2392, 4179, 3667, 2363, 13004, 2522, 17258, 16147, 17404, 15676, 4568, 2063, 9424, 2940, 12436, 14693, 9323, 2015, 3828, 3268, 4047, 6869, 2545, 5022, 2945, 3114, 3246, 2131, 24887, 28748, 3064, 16409, 5887, 26441, 102]",2020-12-17,"[""[('Today'"", "" 'DATE')"", "" ('first'"", "" 'ORDINAL')"", "" ('COVID-19'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Kaiser Permanente'"", "" 'FAC')"", "" ('Capitol Hill'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('first'"", "" 'ORDINAL')"", "" ('DCHOPE'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'permanente capitol', 'hill vaccinations', 'vaccine kaiser', 'today', 'kaiser permanente', 'patients families', 'dose vaccine', 'protect first', 'dchope', 'reason hope', 'first responders', 'save lives', 'getvaccinateddc', 'today frontline', 'workers received', 'first dose', 'families reason', 'lives protect', '#getvaccinateddc', 'frontline workers']",general,0.0,0.288,1,0.9105113636363636,0.0,0,0,activity_spike,"[](10), 'PERSON')](5), trump(4), 'ORG')(3), 'FAC')(3)","Guardian correlation: How many times has Trump lost the election ahahahaha | First Dog on the Moon (score: 2, strength: medium)",general,0,0.11886417676524526,0,2,0,3,0.16666666666666666
1341245162442375168,ShorePoint888,1339624669750681600,1339624669750681600,MayorBowser,2020-12-22 04:52:20,"Why is the Director of Health, Dr. LaQuandra Nesbitt, always so  unhappy?",1,0,0,director health dr laquandra nesbitt unhappy,"director, nesbitt, health, director health, health laquandra, always unhappy, nesbitt always, 'PERSON')], laquandra nesbitt, why, [('LaQuandra Nesbitt'",-0.6,"[101, 2472, 2740, 2852, 2474, 16211, 17670, 24524, 16313, 2102, 12511, 102]",2020-12-22,"[""[('LaQuandra Nesbitt'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'director', 'nesbitt', 'health', 'director health', 'health laquandra', 'nesbitt always', 'always unhappy', 'laquandra nesbitt', 'why']",general,0.1,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.1,0,1,activity_spike,"director(1), nesbitt(1), health(1), director health(1), health laquandra(1)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,3,0.16666666666666666
1339677807740383234,2DeCee,1339624669750681600,1339624669750681600,MayorBowser,2020-12-17 21:04:14,Thank you for the update Madam Mayor,0,0,1,thank update madam mayor,"thank, update madam, 'PERSON')], madam mayor, [('Madam', thank update",0.0,"[101, 4067, 10651, 21658, 3664, 102]",2020-12-17,"[""[('Madam'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'update madam', 'madam mayor', 'thank', 'thank update']",general,0.0,0.002,1,0.4169034090909091,0.0,0,1,activity_spike,"[](10), 'PERSON')](5), trump(4), 'ORG')(3), 'FAC')(3)","Guardian correlation: How many times has Trump lost the election ahahahaha | First Dog on the Moon (score: 2, strength: medium)",general,1,0.0008600240096038416,0,0,0,3,0.16666666666666666
1346148068773789697,CBSEveningNews,1346148068773789697,0,,2021-01-04 17:34:44,"At least a dozen GOP senators are vowing to challenge President-elect Joe Biden’s election victory on Wednesday.

Some have cited baseless conspiracy theories about the election as disputes over the results split the Republican party on Capitol Hill.",4,6,6,dozen gop senators vowing challenge presidentelect joe bidens election victory wednesday cited baseless conspiracy theories election disputes results split republican party capitol hill,"('Joe Biden’s', wednesday, joe biden, dozen gop, some, republican party, election disputes, election, ('the Republican party', victory wednesday, republican, 'CARDINAL'), senators vowing, baseless conspiracy, 'ORG'), biden, cited baseless, results split, ('Wednesday', [('At least a dozen', vowing challenge, nato, ('GOP', challenge joe, conspiracy theories, president, party capitol, 'ORG')], ('Capitol Hill', 'PERSON'), 'DATE')",-0.3,"[101, 6474, 2175, 2361, 10153, 19076, 2075, 4119, 2343, 12260, 6593, 3533, 7226, 6132, 2602, 3377, 9317, 6563, 14040, 7971, 9714, 8106, 2602, 11936, 3463, 3975, 3951, 2283, 9424, 2940, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('At least a dozen'"", "" 'CARDINAL')"", "" ('GOP'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Joe Biden’s'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Wednesday'"", "" 'DATE')"", "" ('the Republican party'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Capitol Hill'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'wednesday', 'joe biden', 'dozen gop', 'some', 'republican party', 'election disputes', 'election', 'victory wednesday', 'republican', 'senators vowing', 'baseless conspiracy', 'biden', 'cited baseless', 'results split', 'vowing challenge', 'nato', 'challenge joe', 'conspiracy theories', 'president', 'party capitol']",politics,0.1,0.034,1,0.8160511363636364,0.1,0,0,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,0,0.11672430940038128,0,0,0,5,0.2777777777777778
1346148970440118274,airwest007,1346148068773789697,1346148068773789697,CBSEveningNews,2021-01-04 17:38:19,cBSnews  M$M,1,0,0,cbsnews mm,[],0.0,"[101, 6568, 2638, 9333, 3461, 102]",2021-01-04,['[]'],general,0.0,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,5,0.2777777777777778
1346183164989992960,tompach09234046,1346148068773789697,1346148068773789697,CBSEveningNews,2021-01-04 19:54:12,Is this the seditious twelve ,1,0,0,seditious,"[('twelve', seditious twelve, 'CARDINAL')]",0.0,"[101, 7367, 23194, 6313, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('twelve'"", "" 'CARDINAL')]"", 'seditious twelve']",general,0.0,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,5,0.2777777777777778
1346150649780719617,CapsHockey1974,1346148068773789697,1346148068773789697,CBSEveningNews,2021-01-04 17:44:59,"They know that it won’t go anywhere, but their objections are going to be rejected by the Senate when it comes to a vote. It’s about their future political ambitions.",0,0,0,know wont objections going rejected senate comes vote future political ambitions,"senate, rejected senate, going rejected, political, objections going, [('Senate', vote future, they, comes vote, future political, anywhere objections, senate comes, political ambitions, 'ORG')], vote, know anywhere",0.0,"[101, 2113, 2180, 2102, 17304, 2183, 5837, 4001, 3310, 3789, 2925, 2576, 19509, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Senate'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'senate', 'rejected senate', 'going rejected', 'political', 'objections going', 'vote future', 'they', 'comes vote', 'future political', 'anywhere objections', 'senate comes', 'political ambitions', 'vote', 'know anywhere']",politics,0.0,0.0,1,0.12428977272727272,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0,0,0,0,5,0.2777777777777778
1346153959619231746,choytdad,1346148068773789697,1346148068773789697,CBSEveningNews,2021-01-04 17:58:08,"Why describe it as “baseless conspiracy theories” when there is video evidence showing suitcases of ballots being drawn under a covered table after the Republican poll watchers were told to go home.
These tens of thousands of ballots were then processed between 10.35 pm and1.00am",0,0,0,baseless conspiracy theories video evidence showing suitcases ballots drawn covered table republican poll watchers told home tens thousands ballots processed 1035 pm and100am,"watchers told, evidence showing, theories video, ('10.35 pm', suitcases ballots, [('Republican', describe baseless, thousands ballots, told home, republican, 'CARDINAL'), baseless conspiracy, 'NORP'), drawn covered, why, covered table, 'TIME')], ('These tens of thousands', conspiracy theories, video evidence, republican poll, home tens, tens thousands, ballots processed, showing suitcases, these",0.0,"[101, 14040, 7971, 9714, 8106, 2678, 3350, 4760, 15940, 2015, 17069, 4567, 3139, 2795, 3951, 8554, 3422, 2545, 2409, 2188, 15295, 5190, 17069, 13995, 9800, 2629, 7610, 1998, 18613, 3286, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Republican'"", "" 'NORP')"", "" ('These tens of thousands'"", "" 'CARDINAL')"", "" ('10.35 pm'"", "" 'TIME')]"", 'watchers told', 'evidence showing', 'theories video', 'suitcases ballots', 'describe baseless', 'thousands ballots', 'told home', 'republican', 'baseless conspiracy', 'drawn covered', 'covered table', 'why', 'conspiracy theories', 'video evidence', 'republican poll', 'home tens', 'tens thousands', 'ballots processed', 'showing suitcases', 'these']",politics,0.1,0.0,1,0.12428977272727272,0.1,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0,0,0,0,5,0.2777777777777778
1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,1335507416331390976,0,,2020-12-06 08:52:35,"OLYMPIA, WA: Shots were fired earlier today outside of the Washington State Capitol during a clash between Antifa Militants and Patriots. The Olympia Police Department has the man in custody and is investigating.

*Warning*—Video Via BL Ranch on YT",211,84,27,olympia wa shots fired earlier today outside washington state capitol clash antifa militants patriots olympia police department man custody investigating warningvideo bl ranch yt,"shots, police department, ('The Olympia Police Department', patriots, earlier today, state capitol, via ranch, ('Antifa Militants', police, war, today outside, 'ORG'), patriots olympia, 'TIME'), fired earlier, shots fired, olympia, ('Patriots', video via, man custody, washington, olympia police, clash antifa, riot, antifa militants, ('YT', 'GPE')], ('Washington State', ('Capitol', [('earlier today', 'GPE')",0.0,"[101, 17096, 11333, 7171, 5045, 3041, 2651, 2648, 2899, 2110, 9424, 13249, 3424, 7011, 17671, 11579, 17096, 2610, 2533, 2158, 9968, 11538, 5432, 17258, 8780, 1038, 2140, 8086, 1061, 2102, 102]",2020-12-06,"[""[('earlier today'"", "" 'TIME')"", "" ('Washington State'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('Capitol'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Antifa Militants'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Patriots'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('The Olympia Police Department'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('YT'"", "" 'GPE')]"", 'shots', 'police department', 'patriots', 'earlier today', 'state capitol', 'via ranch', 'police', 'war', 'today outside', 'patriots olympia', 'fired earlier', 'shots fired', 'olympia', 'video via', 'man custody', 'washington', 'olympia police', 'clash antifa', 'riot', 'antifa militants']",protest,0.6000000000000001,0.517,0,0.9488636363636364,0.6000000000000001,3,0,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,0,0.12456864965572008,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1335507418411745283,KatieDaviscourt,1335507416331390976,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-06 08:52:35,"Statement from 
@OlyPD
:",34,7,4,statement olypd,"statement olypd, [], statement, @olypd",0.0,"[101, 4861, 19330, 22571, 2094, 102]",2020-12-06,"['[]', 'statement olypd', 'statement', '@olypd']",general,0.0,0.063,0,0.8607954545454546,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.12456864965572008,1,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1338299732918063105,GunWashington,1335507416331390976,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-14 01:48:15,"If anyone actually saw this incident in Olympia this weekend, please contact Washington Gun Law today at 425.765.0487 immediately.",0,0,0,actually saw incident olympia weekend contact washington gun law today 4257650487 immediately,"washington gun law, olympia weekend, please contact, ('this weekend', contact washington, anyone actually, washington gun, gun law, olympia, 'WORK_OF_ART'), [('Olympia', saw incident, ('Washington Gun Law', law today, 'DATE')], today immediately, weekend please, incident olympia, actually saw, ('today', 'GPE'), 'DATE')",0.0,"[101, 2941, 2387, 5043, 17096, 5353, 3967, 2899, 3282, 2375, 2651, 23285, 2581, 26187, 2692, 18139, 2581, 3202, 102]",2020-12-14,"[""[('Olympia'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('this weekend'"", "" 'DATE')"", "" ('Washington Gun Law'"", "" 'WORK_OF_ART')"", "" ('today'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'washington gun law', 'law today', 'olympia weekend', 'weekend please', 'please contact', 'saw incident', 'gun law', 'contact washington', 'olympia', 'incident olympia', 'anyone actually', 'washington gun', 'today immediately', 'actually saw']",general,0.1,0.0,0,0.12428977272727272,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1335749559448973316,ColleenAnderso2,1335507416331390976,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-07 00:54:46,https://facebook.com/112779115408517/posts/4108502765836112/?d=n…. It was trump follower who was arrested. So much for “law and order”.,7,0,3,trump follower arrested law order,"arrested much, [], law order, https trump, arrest, trump, follower arrested, much law, trump follower",0.2,"[101, 8398, 22399, 4727, 2375, 2344, 102]",2020-12-07,"['[]', 'arrested much', 'law order', 'https trump', 'arrest', 'trump', 'follower arrested', 'much law', 'trump follower']",politics,0.1,0.013,0,0.7372159090909091,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.005415664042641564,0,0,1,11,0.6111111111111112
1335564467149524992,WRB_BOB,1335507416331390976,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-06 12:39:17,Looks like the guy in the bright yellow was defending him self this video I hope help him,5,0,2,looks like guy bright yellow defending self video hope help,"video hope, defending self, [], guy bright, looks, hope help, looks like, self video, bright yellow, like guy, yellow defending",0.35,"[101, 3504, 2066, 3124, 4408, 3756, 6984, 2969, 2678, 3246, 2393, 102]",2020-12-06,"['[]', 'video hope', 'defending self', 'guy bright', 'looks', 'hope help', 'looks like', 'self video', 'bright yellow', 'like guy', 'yellow defending']",general,0.0,0.009,0,0.6725852272727273,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.00374547088622914,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1335598262099746818,Hydro_Sparky,1335507416331390976,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-06 14:53:34,"Oly PD doing the typical, ignore attacks by the violent left and arrest their victims who defend themselves, routine.

I refuse to believe this is the will of the people. We need voter ID reform so elected officials have to care about the average citizen again",5,0,1,oly pd doing typical ignore attacks violent left arrest victims defend routine refuse believe people need voter id reform elected officials care average citizen,"care average, arrest, violent left, left arrest, people need, refuse believe, voter reform, reform elected, routine refuse, attack, arrest victims, victims defend, oly typical, defend routine, [('Oly PD', attacks violent, officials care, average citizen, typical ignore, oly, 'ORG')], vote",-0.2333333333333333,"[101, 19330, 2100, 22851, 2725, 5171, 8568, 4491, 6355, 2187, 6545, 5694, 6985, 9410, 10214, 2903, 2111, 2342, 14303, 8909, 5290, 2700, 4584, 2729, 2779, 6926, 102]",2020-12-06,"[""[('Oly PD'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'care average', 'arrest', 'violent left', 'left arrest', 'people need', 'refuse believe', 'voter reform', 'reform elected', 'routine refuse', 'attack', 'arrest victims', 'victims defend', 'oly typical', 'defend routine', 'attacks violent', 'officials care', 'average citizen', 'typical ignore', 'oly', 'vote']",crime,0.2,0.007,0,0.6392045454545454,0.2,1,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.002885446876625299,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1337930542348718083,MegMadison13,1335507416331390976,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-13 01:21:13,There is no such thing as an Antifa militant! Do you actually know what Antifa means??? Idiot!,3,0,0,thing antifa militant actually know antifa means idiot,"antifa militant, ('Idiot', 'ORG'), antifa, antifa means, there, know antifa, thing antifa, actually know, means idiot, militant actually, [('Antifa', 'PERSON')], idiot, 'NORP'), ('Antifa'",-0.3333333333333333,"[101, 2518, 3424, 7011, 16830, 2941, 2113, 3424, 7011, 2965, 10041, 102]",2020-12-13,"[""[('Antifa'"", "" 'NORP')"", "" ('Antifa'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Idiot'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'antifa', 'antifa means', 'know antifa', 'thing antifa', 'actually know', 'means idiot', 'militant actually', 'there', 'idiot', 'antifa militant']",general,0.8,0.003,0,0.5035511363636364,0.8,3,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0012152537202128743,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1336086725458726912,AmazonFortress,1335507416331390976,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-07 23:14:33,Antifa would always show up to Patriots peaceful rallies to start trouble.,1,0,0,antifa patriots peaceful rallies start trouble,"peaceful, would always, patriots, show patriots, 'ORG'), antifa would, antifa, always show, start trouble, riot, [('Antifa', patriots peaceful, ('Patriots', rallies start, 'ORG')], peaceful rallies",0.0249999999999999,"[101, 3424, 7011, 11579, 9379, 22867, 2707, 4390, 102]",2020-12-07,"[""[('Antifa'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Patriots'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'patriots peaceful', 'peaceful', 'would always', 'patriots', 'show patriots', 'antifa would', 'antifa', 'start trouble', 'always show', 'rallies start', 'riot', 'peaceful rallies']",protest,0.6000000000000001,0.001,0,0.30610795454545453,0.6000000000000001,2,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1337923429308100608,hummingbirddab,1335507416331390976,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-13 00:52:57,Just say trump supporter shot multiple times at anti trump supporters..and was hogtied and carried off. Hope he rots!!,1,0,0,just say trump supporter shot multiple times anti trump supportersand hogtied carried hope rots,"supporter shot, [], shot multiple, times anti, carried hope, just, trump, multiple times, trump supporter, anti trump, trump supporters, supporters hogtied, hogtied carried, say trump, hope rots, hope",0.0,"[101, 2074, 2360, 8398, 10129, 2915, 3674, 2335, 3424, 8398, 6793, 5685, 27589, 9515, 2094, 3344, 3246, 18672, 2015, 102]",2020-12-13,"['[]', 'supporter shot', 'shot multiple', 'times anti', 'carried hope', 'just', 'trump', 'multiple times', 'anti trump', 'trump supporters', 'supporters hogtied', 'hope', 'say trump', 'hogtied carried', 'hope rots', 'trump supporter']",politics,0.1,0.001,0,0.30610795454545453,0.1,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1337929123918979074,KevinKennedy002,1335507416331390976,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-13 01:15:35,Stop those criminal white supremacy gangs. Those proud boys need to stop their violence.,1,0,0,stop criminal white supremacy gangs proud boys need stop violence,"boys need, supremacy gangs, stop violence, stop criminal, [], gangs proud, those, violence, criminal white, white supremacy, need stop, stop, proud boys, criminal",0.1333333333333333,"[101, 2644, 4735, 2317, 22006, 18542, 7098, 3337, 2342, 2644, 4808, 102]",2020-12-13,"['[]', 'boys need', 'supremacy gangs', 'stop violence', 'gangs proud', 'those', 'violence', 'criminal', 'criminal white', 'white supremacy', 'need stop', 'stop', 'proud boys', 'stop criminal']",crime,0.4,0.001,0,0.30610795454545453,0.4,2,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1337929493420380161,phoenixmacleod1,1335507416331390976,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-13 01:17:03,lol you aren’t a reporter. You are a joke. The labels you have chosen show that you aren’t a real reporter.,1,0,0,lol arent reporter joke labels chosen arent real reporter,"the, real reporter, [], you, reporter joke, lol reporter, labels chosen, chosen show, joke labels, show real",0.5,"[101, 8840, 2140, 4995, 2102, 6398, 8257, 10873, 4217, 4995, 2102, 2613, 6398, 102]",2020-12-13,"['[]', 'the', 'real reporter', 'you', 'reporter joke', 'lol reporter', 'labels chosen', 'chosen show', 'joke labels', 'show real']",general,0.0,0.001,0,0.30610795454545453,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,11,0.6111111111111112
1346193314727518211,MonoNeon,1346193314727518211,0,,2021-01-04 20:34:31,"NEW ALBUM OUT NOW
“Banana Peel On Capitol Hill”
LINK: https://dywanethomasjr.bandcamp.com/album/banana-peel-on-capitol-hill…

“Yesterday the world was buried alive”

Stanks ya for listening to whateva the fyuck I be doing... ",22,8,0,new album banana peel capitol hill link yesterday world buried alive stanks ya listening whateva fyuck doing,"buried alive, whateva fyuck, album, yesterday, ('Yesterday', peel capitol, https yesterday, listening whateva, hill link, [('Banana Peel On Capitol Hill', banana peel on capitol hill, new album, world buried, 'WORK_OF_ART'), album banana, yesterday world, 'DATE')], new, stanks listening, link https, stanks, capitol hill, alive stanks, banana peel",0.1181818181818181,"[101, 2047, 2201, 15212, 14113, 9424, 2940, 4957, 7483, 2088, 3950, 4142, 9761, 5705, 8038, 5962, 2054, 13331, 1042, 10513, 3600, 2725, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Banana Peel On Capitol Hill'"", "" 'WORK_OF_ART')"", "" ('Yesterday'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'buried alive', 'whateva fyuck', 'album', 'yesterday', 'peel capitol', 'listening whateva', 'https yesterday', 'hill link', 'banana peel on capitol hill', 'new album', 'world buried', 'album banana', 'yesterday world', 'new', 'stanks listening', 'link https', 'stanks', 'capitol hill', 'alive stanks', 'banana peel']",general,0.2,0.046,1,0.8352272727272727,0.2,1,0,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,0,0.018992052691725145,0,0,1,1,0.05555555555555555
1337770272963825665,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,0,,2020-12-12 14:44:22,"Worth noting that because there’s a few separate rally points (I misspelled this as “tally” in my first tweet of this thread, sorry) some people are already marching east toward the Capitol / rally point on national mall from Freedom Plaza.",119,18,8,worth noting theres separate rally points misspelled tally tweet thread sorry people marching east capitol rally point national mall freedom plaza,"freedom plaza, misspelled tally, rally, capitol, war, ('Freedom Plaza', national mall, 'ORG'), marching east, toward capitol, sorry people, people already, first tweet, point national, already marching, rally points, capitol rally, mall freedom, tally first, [('first', thread sorry, ('Capitol', points misspelled, 'LOC')], separate rally, 'ORDINAL')",-0.0375,"[101, 4276, 9073, 2045, 2015, 3584, 8320, 2685, 3335, 11880, 3709, 19552, 1056, 28394, 2102, 11689, 3374, 2111, 10998, 2264, 9424, 8320, 2391, 2120, 6670, 4071, 8232, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('first'"", "" 'ORDINAL')"", "" ('Capitol'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Freedom Plaza'"", "" 'LOC')]"", 'freedom plaza', 'misspelled tally', 'rally', 'capitol', 'war', 'national mall', 'marching east', 'toward capitol', 'sorry people', 'people already', 'first tweet', 'point national', 'already marching', 'rally points', 'capitol rally', 'mall freedom', 'tally first', 'thread sorry', 'points misspelled', 'separate rally']",protest,0.2,0.189,1,0.8941761363636364,0.2,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,0,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337769536674820101,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 14:41:26,"The “Trump Unity Bridge” is parked right now and playing “God Bless America” at 11th and Penn, between Harry’s Bar and the Trump hotel.",98,31,13,trump unity bridge parked right playing god bless america 11th penn harrys bar trump hotel,"('Penn', penn harry, god bless, bar, [('Trump Unity Bridge', parked right, penn, harry, 'WORK_OF_ART'), bless america, playing god, harry bar, right playing, trump, trump unity, bar trump, ('Harry’s Bar', 'ORG')], america, unity bridge, ('11th', the, god bless america, trump hotel, trump unity bridge, bridge parked, 'ORDINAL'), 'PERSON'), ('Trump'",0.2857142857142857,"[101, 8398, 8499, 2958, 9083, 2157, 2652, 2643, 19994, 2637, 6252, 9502, 4302, 2015, 3347, 8398, 3309, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Trump Unity Bridge'"", "" 'WORK_OF_ART')"", "" ('11th'"", "" 'ORDINAL')"", "" ('Penn'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Harry’s Bar'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'penn harry', 'god bless', 'bar', 'parked right', 'penn', 'harry', 'bless america', 'playing god', 'harry bar', 'right playing', 'trump', 'trump unity', 'bar trump', 'america', 'unity bridge', 'the', 'god bless america', 'trump hotel', 'trump unity bridge', 'bridge parked']",politics,0.0,0.217,1,0.8977272727272727,0.0,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337770272963825665,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 14:44:22,"Worth noting that because there’s a few separate rally points (I misspelled this as “tally” in my first tweet of this thread, sorry) some people are already marching east toward the Capitol / rally point on national mall from Freedom Plaza.",119,18,8,worth noting theres separate rally points misspelled tally tweet thread sorry people marching east capitol rally point national mall freedom plaza,"freedom plaza, misspelled tally, rally, capitol, war, ('Freedom Plaza', national mall, 'ORG'), marching east, toward capitol, sorry people, people already, first tweet, point national, already marching, rally points, capitol rally, mall freedom, tally first, [('first', thread sorry, ('Capitol', points misspelled, 'LOC')], separate rally, 'ORDINAL')",-0.0375,"[101, 4276, 9073, 2045, 2015, 3584, 8320, 2685, 3335, 11880, 3709, 19552, 1056, 28394, 2102, 11689, 3374, 2111, 10998, 2264, 9424, 8320, 2391, 2120, 6670, 4071, 8232, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('first'"", "" 'ORDINAL')"", "" ('Capitol'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Freedom Plaza'"", "" 'LOC')]"", 'freedom plaza', 'misspelled tally', 'rally', 'capitol', 'war', 'national mall', 'marching east', 'toward capitol', 'sorry people', 'people already', 'first tweet', 'point national', 'already marching', 'rally points', 'capitol rally', 'mall freedom', 'tally first', 'thread sorry', 'points misspelled', 'separate rally']",protest,0.2,0.189,1,0.8941761363636364,0.2,0,1,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337775819918348288,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 15:06:24,"Chants of “Fuck antifa!”

Livestreaming momentarily.",153,27,19,chants fuck antifa livestreaming momentarily,"livestreaming momentarily, [], antifa livestreaming, fuck antifa, chants fuck, livestreaming, fuck, chants",-0.5,"[101, 29534, 6616, 3424, 7011, 3268, 25379, 2075, 16032, 102]",2020-12-12,"['[]', 'livestreaming momentarily', 'antifa livestreaming', 'fuck antifa', 'chants fuck', 'livestreaming', 'fuck', 'chants']",general,0.25,0.272,1,0.9076704545454546,0.25,1,2,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337801700619522049,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 16:49:15,I livestreamed for about an hour before connection died due to too many people.,97,7,10,livestreamed hour connection died people,"due many, [('about an hour', 'TIME')], connection died, livestreamed hour, many people, hour connection, died due",0.1875,"[101, 3268, 25379, 2098, 3178, 4434, 2351, 2111, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('about an hour'"", "" 'TIME')]"", 'due many', 'connection died', 'livestreamed hour', 'many people', 'hour connection', 'died due']",general,0.2,0.138,1,0.8892045454545454,0.2,1,2,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337812463132217346,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 17:32:01,"Trump supporters wave as Marine One flies overhead, presumably carrying the president.",158,41,22,trump supporters wave marine flies overhead presumably carrying president,"wave marine, overhead presumably, one flies, [('Marine One', presumably carrying, marine one, trump, carrying president, trump supporters, supporters wave, president, flies overhead, 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 8398, 6793, 4400, 3884, 10029, 8964, 10712, 4755, 2343, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Marine One'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'wave marine', 'overhead presumably', 'one flies', 'president', 'presumably carrying', 'marine one', 'trump', 'carrying president', 'trump supporters', 'supporters wave', 'flies overhead']",politics,0.0,0.325,1,0.9190340909090909,0.0,0,2,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337813883407446021,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 17:37:39,"Something challenging out here is they there’s multiple different rallies. Several blocks away from the March for Trump based at Freedom Plaza is the “Jericho March”, framed as a prayer rally for Trump. Apparently General Flynn just spoke here.",151,45,17,challenging theres multiple different rallies blocks away march trump based freedom plaza jericho march framed prayer rally trump apparently general flynn just spoke,"prayer rally, freedom plaza, apparently general flynn, something challenging, different rallies, rally, framed prayer, trump apparently, ('Freedom Plaza', challenging multiple, 'ORG'), rallies several, 'PERSON')], [('March', general flynn, based freedom, something, jericho march, rally trump, trump, march framed, 'FAC'), several, multiple different, apparently general, ('Flynn', 'DATE'), ('Trump'",0.11,"[101, 10368, 2045, 2015, 3674, 2367, 22867, 5991, 2185, 2233, 8398, 2241, 4071, 8232, 17309, 2233, 10366, 7083, 8320, 8398, 4593, 2236, 13259, 2074, 3764, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('March'"", "" 'DATE')"", "" ('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Freedom Plaza'"", "" 'FAC')"", "" ('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Flynn'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'prayer rally', 'freedom plaza', 'apparently general flynn', 'something challenging', 'different rallies', 'rally', 'framed prayer', 'trump apparently', 'challenging multiple', 'rallies several', 'general flynn', 'based freedom', 'something', 'jericho march', 'rally trump', 'trump', 'march framed', 'several', 'multiple different', 'apparently general']",protest,0.1,0.32,1,0.9176136363636364,0.1,0,2,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337826194209828865,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 18:26:34,"At the #JerichoMarch, Stop the Steal founder 
@ali
 lays out that their last hope after the electoral college is that a senator will join Rep. Mo Brooks in blocking Jan 6 certification of Biden win.

If none do, “we will burn the Republican Party down and make something new.”",225,137,46,jerichomarch stop steal founder ali lays hope electoral college senator join rep mo brooks blocking jan 6 certification biden win burn republican party make new,"hope electoral, win none, [('JerichoMarch', #jerichomarch, certification biden, blocking jan, jan, republican party, college senator, biden win, jan certification, steal, make something, republican, rep, biden, 'ORG'), electoral college, ('Steal', ('Mo Brooks', last hope, steal founder, nato, ('the Republican Party', mo brooks, 'ORG')], ('Biden', 'PERSON'), ('Jan 6', 'DATE')",0.1952020202020202,"[101, 17309, 7849, 2818, 2644, 8954, 3910, 4862, 19764, 3246, 6092, 2267, 5205, 3693, 16360, 9587, 8379, 10851, 5553, 1020, 10618, 7226, 2368, 2663, 6402, 3951, 2283, 2191, 2047, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('JerichoMarch'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Steal'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Mo Brooks'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Jan 6'"", "" 'DATE')"", "" ('Biden'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('the Republican Party'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'hope electoral', 'win none', '#jerichomarch', 'certification biden', 'blocking jan', 'jan', 'republican party', 'college senator', 'biden win', 'jan certification', 'steal', 'make something', 'republican', 'rep', 'biden', 'electoral college', 'last hope', 'steal founder', 'nato', 'mo brooks']",politics,0.2,0.728,1,0.9602272727272727,0.2,1,2,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,1,1,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337827287161589761,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 18:30:55,"Alex Jones also spoke, promising that “we will never recognize” Joe Biden.

Cheers erupted when he declared that “Joe Biden is a globalist, and Joe Biden will be removed one way or another.”",203,157,58,alex jones spoke promising recognize joe biden cheers erupted declared joe biden globalist joe biden removed way,"biden globalist, jones also, spoke promising, joe biden, alex, 'CARDINAL')], recognize joe, erupted declared, ('one', biden cheers, removed one, one way, biden, never recognize, jones, globalist joe, also spoke, biden removed, alex jones, cheers, declared joe, promising never, [('Alex Jones', ('Joe Biden', 'PERSON')",0.2,"[101, 4074, 3557, 3764, 10015, 6807, 3533, 7226, 2368, 21250, 12591, 4161, 3533, 7226, 2368, 3795, 2923, 3533, 7226, 2368, 3718, 2126, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Alex Jones'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Joe Biden'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Joe Biden'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Joe Biden'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('one'"", "" 'CARDINAL')]"", 'biden globalist', 'jones also', 'spoke promising', 'joe biden', 'alex', 'erupted declared', 'recognize joe', 'biden cheers', 'removed one', 'one way', 'biden', 'never recognize', 'jones', 'globalist joe', 'also spoke', 'biden removed', 'alex jones', 'cheers', 'declared joe', 'promising never']",politics,0.1,0.79,1,0.9616477272727273,0.1,0,2,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1337836729542336515,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 19:08:26,General Flynn just spoke as well at Freedom Plaza. He leaves encouraging Trump supporters not to give up and instead “fight like a Flynn!”,146,58,53,general flynn just spoke freedom plaza leaves encouraging trump supporters instead fight like flynn,"freedom plaza, flynn, trump supporters, like flynn, plaza leaves, spoke well, ('Freedom Plaza', leaves encouraging, 'PERSON')], general flynn, trump, well freedom, encouraging trump, supporters give, 'FAC'), fight like, give instead, ('Flynn', flynn spoke, instead fight, [('Flynn', 'PERSON'), ('Trump'",0.0625,"[101, 2236, 13259, 2074, 3764, 4071, 8232, 3727, 11434, 8398, 6793, 2612, 2954, 2066, 13259, 102]",2020-12-12,"[""[('Flynn'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Freedom Plaza'"", "" 'FAC')"", "" ('Trump'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Flynn'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'general flynn', 'freedom plaza', 'fight like', 'give instead', 'flynn spoke', 'leaves encouraging', 'trump', 'flynn', 'well freedom', 'encouraging trump', 'trump supporters', 'supporters give', 'like flynn', 'instead fight', 'plaza leaves', 'spoke well']",politics,0.25,0.426,1,0.9367897727272727,0.25,1,2,viral_content,"trump(8), 'ORG')(6), 'ORG')](5), 'PERSON')](4), ('Trump'(4)","Guardian correlation: Trump loses another case challenging election results in latest legal rebuke (score: 5, strength: high)",politics,1,0.19882827794675037,0,0,0,10,0.5555555555555556
1346153540763459584,AreaFada1,1346153540763459584,0,,2021-01-04 17:56:29,Astonishing new evidence of a desperate President Donald Dickhead Trump caught on tape trying to steal the election exposes the depth of his corruption and makes his Republican Capitol Hill allies complicit in his bid to thwart the will of voters.,4,2,2,astonishing new evidence desperate president donald dickhead trump caught tape trying steal election exposes depth corruption makes republican capitol hill allies complicit bid thwart voters,"depth corruption, president donald dickhead trump, donald dickhead trump, desperate president, corruption makes, trying steal, ('Republican', election exposes, caught tape, election, complicit bid, exposes depth, war, republican, steal election, republican capitol hill, hill allies, astonishing, president donald, republican capitol, tape trying, 'NORP'), 'ORG')], ('Capitol Hill', [('Donald Dickhead Trump', 'PERSON')",0.0121212121212121,"[101, 26137, 2047, 3350, 7143, 2343, 6221, 5980, 4974, 8398, 3236, 6823, 2667, 8954, 2602, 14451, 2015, 5995, 7897, 3084, 3951, 9424, 2940, 6956, 4012, 24759, 28775, 2102, 7226, 16215, 18367, 7206, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Donald Dickhead Trump'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Republican'"", "" 'NORP')"", "" ('Capitol Hill'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'depth corruption', 'president donald dickhead trump', 'donald dickhead trump', 'desperate president', 'corruption makes', 'trying steal', 'election exposes', 'caught tape', 'election', 'complicit bid', 'exposes depth', 'war', 'republican', 'steal election', 'republican capitol hill', 'hill allies', 'astonishing', 'president donald', 'republican capitol', 'tape trying']",politics,0.7000000000000001,0.014,1,0.7514204545454546,0.7000000000000001,3,0,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,0,0.0035204583416363735,0,0,0,3,0.16666666666666666
1346153544886358021,AreaFada1,1346153540763459584,1346153540763459584,AreaFada1,2021-01-04 17:56:30,"In a fresh abuse of power, Trump tried to bully a top Georgia GOP official into finding votes to overturn President-elect Joe Biden's win in the state. The staggering telephone call, audio of which was obtained by the Washington Post, amounted to the most serious threat yet.",0,0,1,fresh abuse power trump tried bully georgia gop official finding votes overturn presidentelect joe bidens win state staggering telephone audio obtained washington post amounted threat,"post amounted, ('Georgia', overturn joe, joe biden, georgia, gop official, win state, threat, biden win, state staggering, top georgia, 'ORG'), biden, trump tried, finding votes, fresh abuse, power trump, bully top, ('the Washington Post', staggering telephone, trump, ('GOP', threat yet, president, 'ORG')], (""Joe Biden's"", [('Trump', 'GPE'), 'PERSON')",0.3533333333333334,"[101, 4840, 6905, 2373, 8398, 2699, 20716, 4108, 2175, 2361, 2880, 4531, 4494, 2058, 22299, 2343, 12260, 6593, 3533, 7226, 6132, 2663, 2110, 26233, 7026, 5746, 4663, 2899, 2695, 18779, 5081, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Georgia'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('GOP'"", "" 'ORG')"", ' (""Joe Biden\'s""', "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('the Washington Post'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'post amounted', 'overturn joe', 'joe biden', 'georgia', 'gop official', 'win state', 'threat', 'biden win', 'state staggering', 'top georgia', 'biden', 'trump tried', 'finding votes', 'fresh abuse', 'power trump', 'bully top', 'staggering telephone', 'trump', 'threat yet', 'president']",politics,0.30000000000000004,0.002,1,0.4169034090909091,0.30000000000000004,1,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0035204583416363735,0,0,0,3,0.16666666666666666
1346154955846070272,asktja,1346153540763459584,1346153540763459584,AreaFada1,2021-01-04 18:02:06,And UN is watching without any warning,1,0,0,watching warning,"watching without, without warning, [('UN', and, 'ORG')], war",0.0,"[101, 3666, 5432, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('UN'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'and', 'war', 'without warning', 'watching without']",international,0.2,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.2,1,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,3,0.16666666666666666
1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,1346093123353649153,0,,2021-01-04 13:56:24,"I drove by Capitol Hill this morning to see the construction underway for the Inauguration. The crowd will be very limited because of the deadly coronavirus pandemic. Sixteen days until 
@JoeBiden
 becomes President.",1800,141,83,drove capitol hill morning construction underway inauguration crowd limited deadly coronavirus pandemic sixteen days joebiden president,"crowd limited, joebiden becomes, inauguration, see construction, deadly coronavirus, 'ORG'), biden, 'TIME'), coronavirus pandemic, underway inauguration, sixteen days, pandemic sixteen, becomes president, president, 'DATE')], ('this morning', sixteen, construction underway, limited deadly, @joebiden, the, drove capitol, ('Sixteen days', morning see, capitol hill, [('Capitol Hill', ('Inauguration'",-0.1464285714285714,"[101, 5225, 9424, 2940, 2851, 2810, 14128, 17331, 4306, 3132, 9252, 21887, 23350, 6090, 3207, 7712, 7032, 2420, 3533, 17062, 2368, 2343, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Capitol Hill'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('this morning'"", "" 'TIME')"", "" ('Inauguration'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Sixteen days'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'crowd limited', 'joebiden becomes', 'inauguration', 'see construction', 'deadly coronavirus', 'biden', 'coronavirus pandemic', 'underway inauguration', 'sixteen days', 'pandemic sixteen', 'president', 'becomes president', 'sixteen', 'construction underway', 'limited deadly', '@joebiden', 'the', 'drove capitol', 'morning see', 'capitol hill']",politics,0.2,1.0,1,0.9822443181818182,0.2,1,0,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,0,0.422597610278985,1,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346093420490723328,azuna_eth,1346093123353649153,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 13:57:35,Surprised they don't have the BIG fences up around everything like they do Lafayette Park in anticipation of Jan 6th unrest.,2,0,0,surprised dont big fences like lafayette park anticipation jan 6th unrest,"lafayette park, around everything, 'FAC'), ('Jan 6th', surprised, jan unrest, big fences, surprised big, big, jan, anticipation jan, fences around, 'DATE')], [('Lafayette Park', park anticipation, like lafayette, everything like",0.05,"[101, 4527, 2123, 2102, 2502, 21549, 2066, 14425, 2380, 11162, 5553, 5351, 16591, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Lafayette Park'"", "" 'FAC')"", "" ('Jan 6th'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'lafayette park', 'around everything', 'surprised', 'jan unrest', 'big fences', 'surprised big', 'big', 'jan', 'anticipation jan', 'fences around', 'park anticipation', 'like lafayette', 'everything like']",general,0.1,0.002,1,0.4169034090909091,0.1,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0008101691468085828,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346093526174625792,auntjody1976,1346093123353649153,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 13:58:00,Let the count down begin,6,0,0,let count begin,"count begin, let count, [], let",-0.1555555555555555,"[101, 2292, 4175, 4088, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', 'count begin', 'let count', 'let']",general,0.0,0.006,1,0.6200284090909091,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0024305074404257485,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346095350050934784,DocDavePerez,1346093123353649153,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 14:05:15,I hope there is a bullet proof glass surrounding the President and VP.  Trump is creating outrage that will lead to violence.,5,0,1,hope bullet proof glass surrounding president vp trump creating outrage lead violence,"glass surrounding, surrounding president, trump creating, violence, president, 'ORG'), [('VP', proof glass, hope bullet, trump, president trump, creating outrage, outrage lead, 'PERSON')], bullet proof, lead violence, ('Trump'",0.0,"[101, 3246, 7960, 6947, 3221, 4193, 2343, 21210, 8398, 4526, 19006, 2599, 4808, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('VP'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Trump'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'glass surrounding', 'outrage lead', 'surrounding president', 'trump creating', 'violence', 'proof glass', 'hope bullet', 'trump', 'president trump', 'creating outrage', 'president', 'bullet proof', 'lead violence']",politics,0.2,0.007,1,0.6392045454545454,0.2,1,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.002885446876625299,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346093898041593856,KathyCalder6,1346093123353649153,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 13:59:29,"We are watching. We can't wait
 ",3,0,0,watching wait,"[], watching wait",0.0,"[101, 3666, 3524, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', 'watching wait']",general,0.0,0.003,1,0.5035511363636364,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0012152537202128743,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346094233036460040,Dolpff,1346093123353649153,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 14:00:49,"Trump will tell the world that he had 100,000’s and Biden hardly any (fully ignoring Covid) and by that he ‘won’ the elections. Same claim that his rallies had a higher turn out equals winning.",2,0,0,trump tell world 100000s biden hardly fully ignoring covid won elections claim rallies higher turn equals winning,"fully ignoring, biden hardly, turn equals, covid, election, same, claim rallies, trump tell, 'CARDINAL'), ignoring covid, elections claim, biden, 'ORG'), 000', 'PERSON')], ('100, rallies higher, tell world, higher turn, equals winning, trump, world biden, covid elections, hardly fully, ('Biden', ('Covid', [('Trump', 'PERSON')",0.1145833333333333,"[101, 8398, 2425, 2088, 6694, 8889, 2015, 7226, 2368, 6684, 3929, 9217, 2522, 17258, 2180, 3864, 4366, 22867, 3020, 2735, 19635, 3045, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Trump'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('100"", ""000'"", "" 'CARDINAL')"", "" ('Biden'"", "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('Covid'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'fully ignoring', 'biden hardly', 'turn equals', 'covid', 'election', 'same', 'claim rallies', 'trump tell', 'ignoring covid', 'elections claim', 'biden', 'rallies higher', 'tell world', 'higher turn', 'equals winning', 'trump', 'world biden', 'covid elections', 'hardly fully']",politics,0.1,0.002,1,0.4169034090909091,0.1,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0008101691468085828,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346095070253084673,kevbateson,1346093123353649153,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 14:04:08,Probably still be a larger crowd than the Giant Cheeto got...,2,0,0,probably larger crowd giant cheeto got,"probably still, [], giant cheeto, still larger, crowd giant, larger crowd, cheeto got, crowd, probably",0.0,"[101, 2763, 3469, 4306, 5016, 18178, 18903, 2288, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', 'probably still', 'giant cheeto', 'still larger', 'crowd giant', 'larger crowd', 'cheeto got', 'crowd', 'probably']",protest,0.0,0.002,1,0.4169034090909091,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0008101691468085828,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346108944725499904,sandybrowne7,1346093123353649153,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 14:59:16,"Biden does not have an issue with crowd size, like someone else! He is more concerned about citizens keeping safe, unlike someone else.... just saying ",2,0,0,biden does issue crowd size like concerned citizens keeping safe unlike just saying,"keeping safe, [('Biden', like someone, crowd size, biden issue, biden, issue crowd, unlike someone, concerned citizens, someone else, citizens keeping, size like, else concerned, safe unlike, crowd, else saying, citizen, 'ORG')]",0.5,"[101, 7226, 2368, 2515, 3277, 4306, 2946, 2066, 4986, 4480, 4363, 3647, 4406, 2074, 3038, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Biden'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'keeping safe', 'like someone', 'crowd', 'biden issue', 'biden', 'issue crowd', 'unlike someone', 'concerned citizens', 'someone else', 'citizens keeping', 'size like', 'else concerned', 'safe unlike', 'crowd size', 'else saying', 'citizen']",politics,0.05,0.002,1,0.4169034090909091,0.05,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0008101691468085828,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346094500310118400,gapch1964,1346093123353649153,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 14:01:52,Gotta see it! Thanks for sharing Wolf for the folks that can't attend.,1,0,0,gotta thanks sharing wolf folks attend,"thanks, see thanks, got see, sharing wolf, [('Wolf', folks attend, wolf, wolf folks, 'PERSON')], gotta, thanks sharing",0.2,"[101, 10657, 4283, 6631, 4702, 12455, 5463, 102]",2021-01-04,"[""[('Wolf'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'thanks', 'see thanks', 'got see', 'sharing wolf', 'folks attend', 'wolf', 'wolf folks', 'gotta', 'thanks sharing']",general,0.05,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.05,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346096972453842944,Luv2Fly737,1346093123353649153,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 14:11:42,No the crowd will be limited because no one wants to see him. It's impossible for him to draw a crowd. And he will always be if he makes it an illegitimate President. Elected by fraudulent votes.,1,0,2,crowd limited wants impossible draw crowd makes illegitimate president elected fraudulent votes,"fraudulent votes, limited one, crowd limited, wants see, crowd, elected, one wants, crowd always, president elected, [], impossible draw, president, see impossible, elected fraudulent, always makes, vote, draw crowd, illegitimate president, makes illegitimate, and",-0.1793650793650793,"[101, 4306, 3132, 4122, 5263, 4009, 4306, 3084, 18102, 2343, 2700, 27105, 4494, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', 'fraudulent votes', 'limited one', 'crowd limited', 'wants see', 'elected', 'one wants', 'crowd always', 'president elected', 'impossible draw', 'president', 'see impossible', 'elected fraudulent', 'and', 'always makes', 'vote', 'draw crowd', 'illegitimate president', 'makes illegitimate', 'crowd']",politics,0.5,0.005,1,0.5930397727272727,0.5,2,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0021251325926119743,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346099754938339329,sawacapital,1346093123353649153,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 14:22:45,"@YoushayRizvi
 your homie",1,0,0,youshayrizvi homie,"@youshayrizvi, [], youshayrizvi homie",0.0,"[101, 2017, 7377, 12541, 10993, 5737, 7570, 9856, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', '@youshayrizvi', 'youshayrizvi homie']",general,0.0,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0004050845734042914,1,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346111763343765506,dhusker73,1346093123353649153,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 15:10:28,Yes. Was our longest walk. It is a large bldg,1,0,0,yes longest walk large bldg,"[], was, large bldg, yes longest, yes, longest walk, walk large",0.2142857142857142,"[101, 2748, 6493, 3328, 2312, 1038, 6392, 2290, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', 'was', 'large bldg', 'yes longest', 'yes', 'longest walk', 'walk large']",general,0.0,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346488949913636864,playmaker761900,1346093123353649153,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-05 16:09:16,"Is their anyway to move up the Presidential inauguration? Trump is literally trying to kill our Democracy,  and the Republicans in Congress who know better are actually worse than he is. No one person can make a dent in this Democracy. Period!!!",1,0,0,presidential inauguration trump literally trying kill democracy republicans congress know better actually worse person make dent democracy period,"person make, rally, period, worse one, anyway move, inauguration trump, kill democracy, trump literally, republican, move presidential, presidential inauguration, trying kill, one person, literally trying, presidential, [('Republicans', dent democracy, 'NORP'), better actually, ('Congress', democracy, actually worse, trump, 'ORG')]",-0.140625,"[101, 4883, 17331, 8398, 6719, 2667, 3102, 7072, 10643, 3519, 2113, 2488, 2941, 4788, 2711, 2191, 21418, 7072, 2558, 102]",2021-01-05,"[""[('Republicans'"", "" 'NORP')"", "" ('Congress'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'person make', 'rally', 'period', 'worse one', 'anyway move', 'inauguration trump', 'kill democracy', 'trump literally', 'republican', 'move presidential', 'presidential inauguration', 'trying kill', 'one person', 'literally trying', 'presidential', 'dent democracy', 'better actually', 'democracy', 'actually worse', 'trump']",politics,0.45000000000000007,0.001,1,0.30610795454545453,0.45000000000000007,1,1,activity_spike,"[](7), 'ORG')](4), 'PERSON')](4), trump(3), china(3)","Guardian correlation: China 'misled world' on Hong Kong security law, says Dominic Raab (score: 3, strength: medium)",general,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346093647574360068,1948_allan,1346093123353649153,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 13:58:29,Finally Trump will be able to claim a bigger crowd..,0,0,0,finally trump able claim bigger crowd,"trump able, [], finally trump, trump, able claim, claim bigger, crowd, bigger crowd",0.1666666666666666,"[101, 2633, 8398, 2583, 4366, 7046, 4306, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', 'trump able', 'finally trump', 'trump', 'able claim', 'claim bigger', 'crowd', 'bigger crowd']",politics,0.1,0.0,1,0.12428977272727272,0.1,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334
1346093840621559808,KaMiSt72,1346093123353649153,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 13:59:15,Please let them lock down entry to the town... Or better yet... Do the inauguration online and make a huge party later...,0,0,0,let lock entry town better inauguration online make huge party later,"lock entry, [], town better, let lock, please let, yet inauguration, please, entry town, inauguration online, make huge, party later, huge party, better yet, online make",0.1861111111111111,"[101, 2292, 5843, 4443, 2237, 2488, 17331, 3784, 2191, 4121, 2283, 2101, 102]",2021-01-04,"['[]', 'lock entry', 'town better', 'let lock', 'please let', 'party later', 'please', 'entry town', 'inauguration online', 'make huge', 'yet inauguration', 'huge party', 'better yet', 'online make']",general,0.0,0.0,1,0.12428977272727272,0.0,0,1,volume_spike_viral_content,"'ORG')(103), [](101), 'ORG')](87), 'PERSON')(60), trump(54)",Nothing significant - no contextually relevant news found for general spike,no_correlation,1,0.0,0,0,0,15,0.8333333333333334

(Photo: An American flag waves in front of the Supreme Court building on Capitol Hill in Washington, D.C. via AP) #OANN",1400,139,41,good morning tune america news latest photo american flag waves supreme court building capitol hill washington dc ap oann,"('AP', one america news, oann, d.c., waves front, tune, front supreme, an american, ('D.C.', 'ORG'), good, 'TIME'), 'GPE'), ('Washington', court building, 'PERSON')], 'NORP'), ('American', washington, building capitol, hill washington, america news, tune one, ('the Supreme Court', via oann, latest photo, photo, morning tune, ('One America News', washington via, supreme court, ('Capitol Hill', ('OANN', [('morning'",0.5,"[101, 2204, 2851, 8694, 2637, 2739, 6745, 6302, 2137, 5210, 5975, 4259, 2457, 2311, 9424, 2940, 2899, 5887, 9706, 1051, 11639, 102]",2020-12-08,"[""[('morning'"", "" 'TIME')"", "" ('One America News'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('American'"", "" 'NORP')"", "" ('the Supreme Court'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Capitol Hill'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('Washington'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('D.C.'"", "" 'GPE')"", "" ('AP'"", "" 'ORG')"", "" ('OANN'"", "" 'PERSON')]"", 'one america news', 'oann', 'd.c.', 'waves front', 'tune', 'front supreme', 'an american', 'good', 'court building', 'washington', 'building capitol', 'hill washington', 'america news', 'tune one', 'via oann', 'latest photo', 'photo', 'morning tune', 'washington via', 'supreme court']",general,0.1,1.0,0,0.9822443181818182,0.1,0,0,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,0,0.4332078860492369,0,1,0,13,0.7222222222222222
1336314342355197954,lorealcancer,1336314253318344704,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:19:01,"And now, the end is near
As you face the final curtain
Your friends, They'll say it clear
They'll state your case of which I'm certain
You've lived a life of lies
You've grifted the conman's highway
But more, much more than this
Be on your MF’ing way
We did it our way",3,1,1,end near face final curtain friends theyll say clear theyll state case im certain youve lived life lies youve grifted conmans highway mfing way did way,"certain lived, but, your, end near, conman highway, grifted conman, final curtain, lies grifted, [('MF’ing', say clear, face final, ing way, you, clear state, life lies, case certain, they, lived life, way way, 'DATE')], near face, curtain friends",0.2357142857142856,"[101, 2203, 2379, 2227, 2345, 11002, 2814, 2027, 3363, 2360, 3154, 2027, 3363, 2110, 2553, 10047, 3056, 2017, 3726, 2973, 2166, 3658, 2017, 3726, 24665, 10128, 3064, 9530, 15154, 3307, 1049, 16294, 2290, 2126, 2106, 2126, 102]",2020-12-08,"[""[('MF’ing'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'certain lived', 'but', 'your', 'end near', 'conman highway', 'grifted conman', 'final curtain', 'lies grifted', 'say clear', 'face final', 'ing way', 'you', 'clear state', 'life lies', 'case certain', 'they', 'lived life', 'way way', 'near face', 'curtain friends']",general,0.0,0.008,0,0.65625,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.003335301739420557,0,0,0,13,0.7222222222222222
1336315084310630400,joe66872785,1336314253318344704,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:21:58,Breaking News: Biden has won Georgia Again for the FOURTH TIme!!! ,2,0,0,breaking news biden won georgia fourth time,"georgia again, news biden, [('Georgia Again', fourth time, breaking news, biden, fourth, biden georgia, 'ORG')], georgia fourth",0.0,"[101, 4911, 2739, 7226, 2368, 2180, 4108, 2959, 2051, 102]",2020-12-08,"[""[('Georgia Again'"", "" 'ORG')]"", 'georgia again', 'news biden', 'breaking news', 'biden', 'fourth', 'biden georgia', 'fourth time', 'georgia fourth']",politics,0.15,0.002,0,0.4169034090909091,0.15,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0008101691468085828,0,0,0,13,0.7222222222222222
1336322966062125062,fishersfolly,1336314253318344704,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:53:17,Tune in for today's dose of lies hate and fear-mongering.,2,0,0,tune todays dose lies hate fearmongering,"[('today', today dose, tune, tune today, 'DATE')], dose lies, lies hate",-0.8,"[101, 8694, 2651, 2015, 13004, 3658, 5223, 3571, 8202, 4590, 2075, 102]",2020-12-08,"[""[('today'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'today dose', 'tune today', 'tune', 'dose lies', 'lies hate']",general,0.2,0.002,0,0.4169034090909091,0.2,1,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0008101691468085828,0,0,0,13,0.7222222222222222
1336324222163927042,jennybiz,1336314253318344704,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:58:16,Praying for America! ,2,0,0,praying america,"praying america, praying, [], america",0.0,"[101, 14488, 2637, 102]",2020-12-08,"['[]', 'praying', 'praying america', 'america']",general,0.05,0.002,0,0.4169034090909091,0.05,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0008101691468085828,0,0,0,13,0.7222222222222222
1336314787622432770,4yearsNoTrophy,1336314253318344704,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:20:47,Just a reminder that trump still lost the election ,1,0,0,just reminder trump lost election,"trump still, [], just, trump, reminder trump, lost election, election, still lost",0.0,"[101, 2074, 14764, 8398, 2439, 2602, 102]",2020-12-08,"['[]', 'trump still', 'just', 'trump', 'reminder trump', 'lost election', 'election', 'still lost']",politics,0.0,0.001,0,0.30610795454545453,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0004050845734042914,0,0,0,13,0.7222222222222222
1336314407492739072,notinabluemoon,1336314253318344704,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:19:16,How do I sign up?,0,0,0,sign,"[], how",0.0,"[101, 3696, 102]",2020-12-08,"['[]', 'how']",general,0.0,0.0,0,0.12428977272727272,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0,0,0,0,13,0.7222222222222222
1336314430448136197,Barbara67475620,1336314253318344704,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:19:22,Will Alito's hearing be live streamed today?,0,0,1,alitos hearing live streamed today,"[(""Will Alito's"", will alito, alito, live streamed, alito hearing, ('today', 'DATE')], streamed today, 'PERSON'), hearing live",0.1363636363636363,"[101, 4862, 13122, 4994, 2444, 18498, 2651, 102]",2020-12-08,"['[(""Will Alito\'s""', "" 'PERSON')"", "" ('today'"", "" 'DATE')]"", 'will alito', 'alito', 'live streamed', 'alito hearing', 'streamed today', 'hearing live']",general,0.0,0.002,0,0.4169034090909091,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0008600240096038416,0,0,0,13,0.7222222222222222
1336314740415623168,NRio888,1336314253318344704,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:20:36, should be bigger than that one,0,0,1,bigger,"[('one', bigger one, 'CARDINAL')]",0.0,"[101, 7046, 102]",2020-12-08,"[""[('one'"", "" 'CARDINAL')]"", 'bigger one']",general,0.0,0.002,0,0.4169034090909091,0.0,0,1,normal_activity,,no_spike,none,1,0.0008600240096038416,0,0,0,13,0.7222222222222222
1336317831642673153,PhillinaLewis,1336314253318344704,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:32:53,"Thank you Texas!
